<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfFeedItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into Romanian - Upwork</title>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into Romanian. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Two basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: Romanian ( bilingual is preferred: Romanian and English)
2. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to Romanian.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Film Dubbing,                     Music,                     Poetry,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English Romanian            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into French - Upwork</title>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into French. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Two basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: French ( bilingual is preferred: French and English)
2. The translators should be French natives who can speak standard French.
3. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to French.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Christian Theology,                     Editing,                     Music,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English French            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Deep Barry White type voice for series of short audio ads and video voice over - Upwork</title>
    <description>Looking for a very deep, Barry white style talent for a series of short audio ads and video voice overs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This will be an ongoing project with possible additional milestones after the initial batch.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A script and basic outline will be provided for each piece created.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Each audio ad will be no longer than 30 seconds and the video overs no longer than 15 seconds. The initial contract is for 4 separate ads, each with it&amp;#039;s own milestone.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The entire initial project (including all 4 milestones) is $120, or $30 each.Budget: $120
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Voice Talent
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 23:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for strong Nodejs/API and Angular5x  Developers – Agency Preferred - Upwork</title>
    <description>We are looking to establish a long term relationship with an Upwork Agency and hire 1-2 members as dedicated resources. We do not require a Project Manager for day to day activities and are happy to communicate directly with the developers, however we would like to know there is a manager available for escalations and oversight. We would ask that a standard start time be maintained so we can schedule some overlap (we prefer morning hours of CST timezone) to review work and discuss tasks.
**Your Responsibilities Will Include:
-	development, migration and updates to a large content management system that manages a lot of retail and mall content
-	work collaboratively in Slack together as a group. Your team will interface with myself, our project managers, and our development team on a regular basis and the ability to quickly respond in chat is very important
-	have regular starting hours with some overlap of CST timezone and consistently starting work at that time
-	tracking your time per task with notes for our records
Our goal is that you will be a part of our team and we will work together on this cool platform and others for months and years to come.
** About the CMS System:
You will be working purely on the data side of the CMS and not the front-end website. We inject data from a few sources, we expose APIs and webservices to other systems which consume our data either for processing or sending to the other system which manages the actual website and mobile application. We have about 2 months of work in our backlog and we would like to bring on skilled professionals to work with us on getting this stuff done. As part of the onboarding and development we will be working on documentation and diagramming the system. We feel that having new developers work on this will also help them learn the system and how it works so that when they develop on it, it will make sense to them.
** Technologies You Should be Familiar With:
We have put together a list of specific skills that would be involved in our application and for the new team members to be responsible for. It&amp;#039;s not critical that you are 100% experts at all the areas listed below but you need to be proficient in larger applications built in a MEAN stack which utilize a lot of AWS services. 
Servers
1.	Ubuntu 
2.	Windows Server 2016
App/ languages
1.	Back-end
a.	Nodejs 6
2.	Front-end
a.	Bootstrap 
b.	Angular 1
c.	Jquery
3.	NGINX configuration - performance and security
4.	Python - for processing data, lambdas, or general script stuff like image resizing in batches
5.	Javascript ES6
Database languages
1.	Mongodb - what version 3
2.	Redis - version 2+
AWS specific things like 
1.	S3 - read and write, setup, ACL generation, compression, proper headers
2.	Lambdas ** Key knowledge area
3.	SNS
4.	SQS 
5.	etc...
Integrations
1.	SSO - okta, Auth0
2.	CI tools like&amp;hellip;
3.	Airbrake or similar
4.	Keymetrics or similar - Server Metrics, alerts, etc..
5.	Slack integration 
6.	Webhooks - creating, processing, debuggingPosted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Amazon S3,                     Amazon Web Services,                     AngularJS,                     Auth0,                     AWS Lambda,                     JavaScript,                     Linux System Administration,                     MEAN Stack Administration,                     MongoDB,                     Redis            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Wanted:	Bada$$	Virtual Assistant	with	Real	Estate Experience - Upwork</title>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m	a	looking	for	a	full-time	VA	to	help	with	my	real	estate	business.		
**	Responsibilities	Include	**	
Screening	buyer	&amp;amp;amp;	seller	leads	daily
Addressing,	stamping,	and	stuffing	batches	of	100	mailers	on	a	regular	basis
Running	comparable	sales	and	determining	value
Understanding	my	buying	criteria	&amp;amp;amp;	recommending	a	course	of	action
Receiving	inbound	calls	and	making	outbound	calls	(I&amp;rsquo;ll	provide	the	call	script)
Coordinating	paperwork	and	closings
**	Must	Have	**
Hawk-like	attention	to	detail
Dog-like	dependability
Ox-like	work	ethic
Cat-like	reflexes
Please	respond	with	your	availability,	samples	of	past	work,	and	favorite	&amp;lsquo;80s	movie.Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Internet Research,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a Copywriter For Scripts (For Video Ads) - Upwork</title>
    <description>Hello Copywriters!
We&amp;#039;re looking for simple scripts to be created for video ads in a &amp;amp;quot;testimonial&amp;amp;quot; format that is pushing people to an advertorial. We need a good 30 to 60 second long scripts that will be persuasive and comes off as authentic.
We have a supplement product and we have a girl who is already a video actress who will be recording herself using a selfie-type video.
This is how we&amp;#039;re going to push people to read (her) article, which is an advertorial that gives a review of the product.
I have an example to show you what we&amp;#039;ve done in the past that have worked, and we&amp;#039;d like more quality, persuasive scripts.
This will be continuous, every week or so we&amp;#039;d come up with a good batch of 5 scripts or so.
If this is something that interests you, I&amp;#039;d love to hear back!Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Copywriting
Skills:        Copywriting,                     Sales Writing,                     Scriptwriting            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 20:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into French - Upwork</title>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into French. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Two basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: French ( bilingual is preferred: French and English)
2. The translators should be French natives who can speak standard French.
3. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to French.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Christian Theology,                     Editing,                     Music,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English French            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 19:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>ETL in AWS - Upwork</title>
    <description>Hi Freelancers
I need to create an ETL workflow like this: Scraper (I&amp;#039;m using parse hub and Octoparse) -&amp;amp;gt; S3 -&amp;amp;gt; Lambda for Batch processing -&amp;amp;gt; Amazon Comprehend -&amp;amp;gt; Elasticsearch -&amp;amp;gt; Kibana
Job Specifics:
1) S3 -&amp;amp;gt; Lambda -&amp;amp;gt; Comprehend. After csv data is loaded in S3, batch process the data using Lambda to Amazon Comprehend. Here I need a script to format data in the correct format, Example. The date is in this format: on June 3, 2018, Also some columns are in text format. See attached file of example scrapping output. 
The script should be reusable and easy to modify to create other similar jobs. 
2) Amazon Comprehend NPL: Here I need to extract keywords and Entities for each line, I need to create a Bag of words for keywords phrases and entities using Kibana. 
3) Amazon Comprehend to Elasticsearch: Data from Comprehend should be sent to a new index. Each ETL pipeline should have its own Index.
4) Elastic Search Kibana: Here we need you to install ES, Kibana using AWS, Install SearchGuard Free plugin for access and authenticationBudget: $100
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon EC2,                     AWS Lambda,                     Elasticsearch,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Python            Country: Ecuadorclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 19:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer needed to create node based sync utility for (SFDC) Salesforce Dot Com. - Upwork</title>
    <description>Summary: 
We need to execute an SFDC batch job, download the results, and log them to the console. We will use 2 NodeJS scripts. The first script (Invoker) will initiate the SFDC batch job to query all accounts in the SFDC instance that have a specific custom field set. The second script (Downloader) will check if the batch job succeeded, and if it did, download the results and log them to the console.
Requirements:
&amp;bull;	The NodeJS scripts should use ES 2017, Babel and Node version 8.11.4. 
&amp;bull;	The scripts should assume that they will log in as an SFDC user with access to the SFDC instance. 
&amp;bull;	The username, password, and SFDC instance should be parameters in the function being called.
&amp;bull;	The field the Invoker will use for filtering should be a parameter on the function.
Link to video that shows the process of running a batch job in SF
https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/19gjo1tQLkG5JbCP_aLM207M1Jepiby5h?usp=sharing
From what is described in the video link above, we are basically looking to turn that into a scriptable process via node.
We already have a code baseline to start from. The baseline code is a complete compilable node project with linting/babel already setup ready to go.
We have a repo to work from ready to go see attached screen shoots of baseline project.Budget: $300
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        API Development,                     Babel,                     Es6,                     Node.js,                     Salesforce Marketing Cloud            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 17:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Male Mandarin voice talent -30 - 40 lessons.  Each lesson approx. 1500 words. - Upwork</title>
    <description>Hello, we are rolling out 30 to 40 lessons, which are approximately 1500-1600 words over the next three to five months. These will be in batches of 10 lessons at a time for the same male Mandarin talent to record. We will use the same voice for all 30 to 40 lessons.
The main priority is pacing and delivery of the script. Since there are technical terms in the lessons, its important to have subtle and purposeful pauses throughout in order for the listener to digest/ grasp the information.
The tonality of the voice is to be a blend of conversational and informative and educational. Not too dull, dry and robotic. Not guy next store delivery the whole time. Moderate inflection with a smooth fluid delivery. Personable yet intelligent.
Pay will be $150 for each lesson and if the lesson goes over 2000 words (which if it were to go over it would not be by very much ) I will pay $250. Ideal delivery time for the 10 lessons would be about 10 to 14 days, but I have some leeway if its needed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;As i&amp;#039;m sure you&amp;#039;ve all experienced, &amp;amp;quot;the sooner the better&amp;amp;quot;.
Requirements to be a candidate:
1). Provide a sample or two from the script attached. Feel free to provide different deliveries if you wish (not trying to make more work for you but want everyone to have a fair shot)
2) Be available over the next couple months for all of the lessons
3) Have a home studio that you&amp;#039;re able to deliver with high quality
4) Willing to discuss delivery time to meet time requirements. I would say approximately 10-14 days would be a solid window.
I appreciate and respect your willingness to audition.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;#039;m not asking you to record the whole document, just a two or three sections to showcase tonality, pacing, delivery.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Thank you -- Mark
PS - the short script doesn&amp;#039;t seem to come out in the format that allows you to see the spaces between the paragraphs. Use your discernment and feel free to include ample pausesBudget: $6,000
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Voice Talent
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 21:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need Apple Scripter - Upwork</title>
    <description>We have a set of Apple scripts that were batched into an app. 
This script was for converting a word document, PowerPoint, or excel document into a pdf, but since a recent Microsoft office update it stopped working. 
We need to have this app fixed or a similar script to be developed to convert word documents into PDFs. 
The word document should convert into a pdf in the same exact size that it is currently in and be &amp;ldquo;marginless&amp;rdquo;. 
Also, we have 2 scripts that print using two different page sizes, but these are broken too.Budget: $100
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        AppleScript,                     JavaScript            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 18:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Count keywords on pages behind a list of URLs - Upwork</title>
    <description>Hi!
I have a list of URLs in Excel. About 1000 of them 
Need to count certain keywords on these pages.
Output should Ideally post back to excel cell next to the URL, but can just write a web page where I post a list of URLs and and a phrase and script generates a table with keyword count in front of each URL. In this case web hosting will be on Amazon EC2 Windows Server. Which ever option is faster to load.
Required features
- count of individual key words (each one separately)
- check if all these words are within a certain range of words (say 50, ~ a paragraph apart)
- count full phrase verbatim
- check if the page exists behind the URL
Number of URLs&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;to be processed per batch ~1000
Please provide with your answer
- your full fee including debugging and Q&amp;amp;amp;A
- time for completion
- experience in similar tasks
- resume with qualificationsPosted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Country: Russiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 06:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Technical Email Marketing Manager at Growing Startup - Must Know Python - Upwork</title>
    <description>THE WORK:
We need to run a large number of email marketing campaigns. 
We use Python and the Sendgrid API currently, though we will use marketing automation solutions in the future. 
We will provide email templates and the email addresses to send them to. You will do everything else. 
You will:
- Run the script to send batches of emails as necessary
- Make improvements to the Python script that sends the email 
- Monitor campaigns, track and analyze key email marketing statistics 
THE COMPANY: 
We&amp;#039;re a growing startup that&amp;#039;s making it easier for small businesses in the US to get their accounting and bookkeeping done.
REQUIREMENTS:
- Python
- Javascript
- HTML + CSS
- 100% fluent in English
- Available to work at least 1-2 hours each weekday
No upfront payment. Payment is made based on hours every 2 weeks or every month.Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Email &amp;amp; Marketing Automation
Skills:        Email Deliverability,                     Email Handling,                     Email Marketing,                     Email Technical Support,                     HTML,                     JavaScript,                     Lead Generation,                     Marketing Automation,                     SendGrid            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 22:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a Powershell expert who can create PS scripts in batch file to automate Dynamics CRM 2011 to Dynamics CRM 2016 Upgrade tasks - Upwork</title>
    <description>This runs like a well oiled machine for us. We get these customer databases and we do the same thing every time. No errors, nothing. But it takes 10 hours. 
We have the list of steps. This is for our own environment,
At a very high level these are the tasks:
1. Restore the Client database to a server with Pre-installed CRM 2011
2. Run a sql script to clean the db
3. Import the Organization
4. Back up the DB
5. Run another SQL script
6. Back up the CRM 2013 upgraded DB
7. Restore to another server with CRM 2015 installed already
8. Import Org
9. Run a script
10. Back up the db
11. Restore to another CRM 2016 already installed
12. Import Org
Run another SQL script.
Done.
When we do this on client servers, there are some variations.
For every new installation or deployment of software, we have to do many system checks and verifications on their Windows Servers
Lets define the scope of work. 
Do the low hanging fruits first. 
Lets make it a phased approach. 
Automation of these frequently repetitive tasks with every client will save us a lot of time in deployments and will make us more productive. I have been working on some of these on my own but a powershell expert would be good to work with. 
$100 is a placeholderBudget: $100
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 01:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a Powershell expert who can create PS scripts in batch file to automate Pre-install tasks - Upwork</title>
    <description>You could do this in phased approach as well. Your PS scripts should be able to do these:
For every new installation or deployment of software, we have to do many system checks and verifications on Windows Servers which we connect remotely via vpn connections. 
Typically Windows Server 2012 R2 and above. Some are virtualized as well. SQL 2014 and above. 
1. Get CPU, RAM, Drives, available memory on each drive
2. Server manager - Add/Remove Roles and Features. 
a) Check whether, .NET Framework 4.5, IIS and bunch of other Server components and Windows Server Features are installed
3. Registry Verifications and modify registry entries and values if needed
4. Run SQL commands from command prompt
Also minor things like these Remote desktop connections will go back to screen saver mode and I have to enter password every time to go back in. 
while I am working on Application Server, I want to keep RDP sessions of other Servers open so I can go back in and out without having to enter password every time.
We access these RDPs via Jump servers. Same for Jump servers. 
Also don&amp;#039;t want our PCs to go back to screen saver mode so I have to enter password to get back in to check the progress on how the installs on RDP sessions are coming along. 
Lets define the scope of work. 
Do the low hanging fruits first. 
Lets make it a phased approach. 
Automation of these frequently repetitive tasks with every client will save us a lot of time in deployments and will make us more productive. I have been working on some of these on my own but a powershell expert would be good to work with. 
$100 is a placeholderBudget: $100
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 20:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>WAS Admin (Websphere) - Upwork</title>
    <description>WAS Admin
Employment Type: Full Time or Contractor
Location: Milwaukee, WI.
Basic Skills
Hands on experience on Websphere 7.0, 8.0, 9.0, Redhat Linux and AIX.
Preferred Skills
IBM MQ and Mule ESB.
Code deployment tools like UrbanCode, knowledge of scripting tools like Batch, Perl and Python.
Certifications on IBM and Websphere are also taken into consideration
Soft Skills Desired
Good written and verbal communication skills
Ability to work on Agile-based project
Exposure to SafeAgile framework
Availability to work on weekends for deployment and critical support activities
Experience: 6-8 years
Visa requirements: H1B, GC EAD
Job Types: Full-time, ContractPosted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        IBM WebSphere,                     Python,                     Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL)            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Burmese Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <description>We are launching Burmese narration project and hope to hire some Burmese native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Burmese audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Burmese Yangon Standard Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Background Music: overall tone and the volume of the soundtrack need to be compatible with the related Type, and quieten people&amp;rsquo;s heart to ponder over the words.
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Audio Production,                     Burmese,                     English,                     Translation English Burmese            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Civil Maps is Hiring for freelance consultant - DevOps Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <description>Hi ,
We are Civil Maps .
Civil Maps, provider of 3D mapping technology for fully autonomous vehicles, has raised a $6.6 million seed funding round from Ford Motor Company, Motus Ventures, Wicklow Capital, StartX Stanford and Yahoo cofounder Jerry Yang&amp;rsquo;s AME Cloud Ventures.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; mission is to make it possible for fully autonomous vehicles (SAE Levels 4-5) to drive anywhere smoothly and safely. Through artificial intelligence and vehicle-based local processing, Civil Maps converts sensor data into meaningful map information built specifically to direct fully autonomous vehicles. The company will use the seed investment to accelerate product development and deployment with a number of leading automotive companies and technology partners.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; artificial intelligence software aggregates raw 3D data from LiDAR (high-resolution laser imaging), camera and other sensors onboard autonomous vehicles and organizes the information into machine-readable maps. The information is vastly more actionable information than today&amp;rsquo;s mapping systems and requires a fraction of the data storage and transmission for existing technologies. Thanks to this light data footprint, Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; spatial information is far less costly to transmit over cellular networks, enabling the company to more easily crowdsource, update and share road data in real time&amp;mdash;a major improvement over the lengthy processes that require human annotation in current use. As a result, the company can quickly generate and maintain maps that give fully autonomous vehicles the comprehensive and precise knowledge to autonomous operate safely and smoothly on all roads.
About the Opportunity : 
This is an opportunity to work on some of the most exciting problems in the autonomous vehicle industry. Civil Maps is looking for a Devops engineer to grow its overall infrastructure. You will be interacting with a completely custom-made distributed computing framework, handling terabytes and petabytes of machine vision data, and millions of requests from robotic platforms.
In our interdisciplinary teams, you will get acquainted with the many facets of 3D map creation: data collection, geospatial registration, feature extraction, auditing.
Come work on novel challenges, learn and grow while helping Civil Maps achieve on-demand perception of the world around us.
We are hiring the professionals for the below skills:
Work Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;: Hyderabad
Job Description for DevOps Enginner:
Experience : 3-15 yrs 
Responsibilities : 
Deliver next generation distributed applications using a variety of tools to include Kubernetes, Ansible, RHEL, Openshift, Atomic, Mesos, Openstack and Docker.
Build solutions and provide a framework for Microservices and DevOps.
Bring knowledge and help with continuous integration, deployment and security.
Automating the Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment environment with relative tools.
Troubleshooting Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment issues.
Experience with the following : 
Deploy, manage Continuous Integration tools (Jenkins, Travis etc..).
Cloud-based deployments (AWS, Azure, OpenStack).
Linux administration, usage, and bash scripting (Bash, Batch, Powershell)
Deploying MEAN stack applications.
Security tools like Fortify, Nessus.
Network architecture (routing, load balancing, firewalls, VLANs).
Virtualization (VMWare, XEN, KVM, Openstack).
Container technologies (Mesos, Docker, Rocket, etc.).
Experience in setting up backup and restore mechanism for the DB and other relevant systems.Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>British / Australian / S. Africa Voiceover Training Videos - Upwork</title>
    <description>I need to create voice over videos for our training classes.
The goal is to make extremely dry, boring content at least sound good.
I will provide Powerpoint file and script by page.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Each Powerpoint is approx 10 pages and the script averages about 1000 words.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
I need the video output in a video format (MP4)-- basically PP file with voice over.
The first client has approx 60 videos.
The first batch, which we would consider a test would be 6 videos-- each about 1000 words. 
Assuming this first batch goes well, we will send remaining 54 videos.
I may be willing to pay extra for video of speaking along with PP (As I have heard retention is better when watching people speak).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is obviously dependent on &amp;#039;look&amp;#039;.Budget: $125
Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Voice Talent
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Photoshop editor for repeated work adding text using actions - Upwork</title>
    <description>I am looking for entry level Photoshop editor with basic Photoshop skills. We are developing a portfolio of imagines where we require to do following:
Change text in the photo using action script (around 30-40 different photos)
Adjust the text in the imagine to suit the text box.
Save the file using batch function as .jpg.
Scripts and necessary instructions will be provided.
The job may require basic editing skill like removing trade names adding light to the imagine...
You should be familiar with design and good feel for colour composition.
I am looking for fast worker, and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;quick learner since the time to perform the job will be limited.
We will post the Photoshop projects on the shared drive like onedrive. After the job is done the ready photo will be uploaded to the same share drive by you.
Required number of hours weekly is min 30.
I am looking for freelancers with the lowest rates
Pay is $3 an hour.Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Photoshop,                     Photo Editing            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 22:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Agisoft/Reality capture/Maya job - Upwork</title>
    <description>I am looking for someone with experience using the following:
1) Photogrammetry applications: either Agisoft Photoscan or Reality Capture
2) Animation: Maya
Below are the tasks I would like you to do:
1. Take the captured facial performance and reconstruct using Photogrammetry application into a per frame mesh and texture (if using RealityCapture you can write script to handle Batch processing with command line utility)
2. Import the models into Maya, and create a visibility script, setting the scans visibility on a per frame basis (should take about 10 minutes of coding) 
3. In Maya create a rough lightrig for preview purposes
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Animation
Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 12:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Dutch Christian Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <description>We are launching Dutch Christian Reading project and hope to hire some Dutch native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Dutch audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Standard Dutch Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Post-production: if vocals and reverberation are pleasant to hear; if the overall tone and the volume of the background music is soft, and will not impair people&amp;rsquo;s ability to hear God&amp;rsquo;s words.
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: September 12, 2018 12:22 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Audio Engineering,                     Audio Production,                     Dutch,                     English,                     Voice Over Dutch            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
</ArrayOfFeedItem>