<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfFeedItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer needed for creating a responsive web page in core PHP - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developer-needed-for-creating-responsive-web-page-core-PHP_%7E01dfb2a98255384d44?source=rss</link>
    <description>The main job of the project is to add a report store (eCommerce store) to the existing website. 
Key Task - 
1. Able to upload reports (sample page, Table of Contents, Summary Text) in the back end
2. Able to add reports into various industries and sub-industries
3. The visitors data to be saved in the back-end, once the visitor enters his/her data
3. The upload data format will be MS Excel, MS Word, MS Power Point
4. Payment gateway integration
Additional Task - 
5. Option to run promos for discounts and offers
6. Live chat options
Feature - 
1. The report store will be a stand alone page
2. Links/buttons to be added from the existing industry page to the report storeBudget: $70
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        AngularJS,                     CSS,                     CSS3,                     HTML,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     PHP,                     Web Design,                     Website Development            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 11:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>We need a top-notch Media Buyer to join our team - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/need-top-notch-Media-Buyer-join-our-team_%7E015ddedecb4ac12583?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are a social media agency and owners of several premium entertainment properties. We provide highly appealing content and reach millions of users across the web.
Currently, we are looking for a great media buyer to join our team in a full-time role in our amazing offices in Vilnius Lithuania.
The ideal candidate is someone who:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Has experience in media buyer / paid traffic
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Knowledge of statistics and data modeling
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Strong documentation skills
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Strong Skills in MS Office especially in Excel
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Background in either or: Data Analysis, Mathematics, Statistics, Economics or Finance
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Experience in data engineering
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;â— Strong knowledge of English
What we offer is a competitive salary, flexible working hours and vacations, great offices in Vilnius center, amazing and experienced team to guide you through the process, possibility to grow and learn, great career opportunities.
Should you believe this is you, we would be happy to have you on our team.
Please note that the budget is just a placeholder, you are welcomed to bid for the job, and it will depend of the level of your experience.Budget: $5
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; SMM - Social Media Marketing
Skills:        Analytics,                     Facebook Marketing,                     Instagram Marketing,                     Internet Marketing,                     Marketing Strategy,                     Mathematics,                     Social Media Management,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Statistics            Country: Lithuaniaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 10:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Assistant to Business Owner - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Assistant-Business-Owner_%7E018cc21b4e59fee1fe?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a part-time and upbeat personal/administrative assistant for about 3-10 hours a week who can wear &amp;ldquo;many hats&amp;rdquo; along with great MS Word, Excel, writing and communication skills. The right candidate would be comfortable assisting with different aspects of a new and growing career development firm. We provide career coaching and professional writing services. 
Duties include but not limited to: ad-hoc projects, database management, social media content marketing, creating forms and templates, handling client correspondence via email and phone, setting up network files, industry research and other administrative tasks. Familiarity with creating content on Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Instagram is a plus.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Customer Service,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Phone Support,                     Social Media Management,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Virtual Assistant,                     WordPress            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data entry for an eCommerce business - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-entry-for-eCommerce-business_%7E018a8002e06ef55627?source=rss</link>
    <description>THIS JOB REQUIRES THAT YOU HAVE MICROSOFT WINDOWS AND MS ACCESS RUNNING ON YOUR COMPUTER
Responsibilities include but not limited to:
-Enter tracking data sent by vendors
-Enter invoice data
-Enter product data tasks
Required Skills:
- Must be comfortable with Microsoft Office tools&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(Access &amp;amp;amp; Excel)
- Able to think systematically and critically including the ability to quickly learn new ways of solving problems.
- Experience with Magento 2 is a plus
- A little familiarity with HTML would be good.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Magento 2,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>MS Excel expert for product feed data - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Excel-expert-for-product-feed-data_%7E010c51721da2ede850?source=rss</link>
    <description>Data Feed Export - needs to be fixed up and consolidated - 
needs to be sorted and cleaned.
colors, categories - need to be all made uniform across multiple sheets.
30 sheets total for the first batch.
colors and categories need to be relabeled.
some sheets have 300 products, some have 1000, some more.Budget: $80
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 18:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Backend and API for metering and billing processing [Java 8, stripe] - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Backend-and-API-for-metering-and-billing-processing-Java-stripe_%7E0143b371f1be4c559a?source=rss</link>
    <description>This job is for creating a Java API to process metering and billing. The project will run on Google App Engine, you will work with Android Studio [same as IntelliJ IDEA] and we will help you set up for this scenario. We have a working framework for App Engine Endpoints, but you will write all REST endpoint and logic from scratch.
Milestone 1 is about writing around 11 endpoints, which accept a request from our main system (create customer, create subscription, etc.). From the endpoint, you will feed the received data into a use case which makes one or more requests to stripe https://stripe.com/docs/api to read or write the appropriate objects. All this happens sync, and either succeeds or fails.
Milestone 2 is about writing 2 or so extra endpoints which accept JSON data from our servers and processes it through a workflow (there might be queues involved, and some memcache and SQL, App Engine SDK used here). If a customer is detected as not having enough funding, you will call a hook, or alternatively, our frontend platform can query the data.
Milestone 3 is for writing tests. We need full test coverage, so we can ensure all billing procedures work properly and nothing falls through the cracks. Google Cloud SDK will allow you to run their whole environment locally so you can work with simulated memcache and databases in your tests (no need for extensive mocking). You can work on this milestone parallel if you prefer test-driven environment.
Milestone 4 Integrate. We may need to adjust minor things, like optimize endpoints or data formats and such. What&amp;#039;s important is that your system must play with our remaining system. I have planned this thoroughly, so I believe it should work with minor adjustments, but we may need to work on the details a bit to get this going.
We will break the project total in 4 equal parts at 25%. We expect every milestone to be completed within approximately 2 weeks. Project total around 2 months.Budget: $2,000
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        API Development,                     Java,                     Stripe            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQL &amp;amp;amp; Marketing Cloud Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-amp-Marketing-Cloud-Developer_%7E01c9bd030198d3a4ff?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello,
Looking for a person who can do Salesforce Marketing Cloud development, data extensions, knows contact builder, data extracts, FTP, file transfers, automation studio, SQL for data queries, reports and custom reports, Salesforce integration and data transfer back from Salesforce.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Email &amp;amp; Marketing Automation
Skills:        ExactTarget,                     Marketing Cloud Administration,                     Marketing Cloud Development,                     Salesforce Marketing Cloud,                     Salesforce.com,                     SQL,                     SQL Programming            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 17:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Urgently need a Sage Line 50 consultant with integration experience. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Urgently-need-Sage-Line-consultant-with-integration-experience_%7E01841257a957ff4b3b?source=rss</link>
    <description>We immediately require a Sage 50 consultant to help integrate an analytics system with a Sage Line 50 system. The person should have good understanding of Sage Line 50 systems and their underlying databases. Experience integrating other systems and running or facilitating SQL queries via ODBC is essential.
Location: Consultants preferably based in South West England or open to travel as required for the duration of the project.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Sage 50 Accounting,                     SQL            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 17:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Price Update Specialist - Ukraine, Kiev - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Price-Update-Specialist-Ukraine-Kiev_%7E013872599c925c24ec?source=rss</link>
    <description>Who we are:
A Ukrainian branch of an ecommerce site, headquartered in Los Angeles, seeking a product/price maintenance specialist.
Tasks include:
Spreadsheet tasks such as combining data, referencing information from other sheets, manually seeking information to make final adjustments
Reviewing requests from within the company to correct invalid data and applying correction
Updating products data and prices in the system and on the website
Requirements:
Must be able to work 40 hours a week, Mon-Fri 3PM-12AM
Must be able to communicate with company during United States business hours both using text chat and verbal / phone
Extensive experience in MS Excel is a must (Text/Array/Logical functions, Pivot Tables)
ERP software experience is a plus
Conversational English
Attention to details, ability to work with large volumes of data
Location: This is not a remote job, ONLY Kyiv, UkraineBudget: $950
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Accountant / Bookkeeper Needed to Create Income/ Expense Reports for our Customers - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Accountant-Bookkeeper-Needed-Create-Income-Expense-Reports-for-our-Customers_%7E01dc1a249e60e5322a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Introduction:
Our customers in Ontario, Canada require an accounting report to be created for them. This report helps our customers apply for benefits through their insurance provider. 
The report summarizes the customer&amp;#039;s previous income, their current income, and the difference between past and present income. The difference is usually a loss. 
This loss is used to calculate the amount of weekly benefit, which the customer may be eligible for based on Ontario, Regulation 34/10, section 7 (see https://www.ontario.ca/laws/regulation/100034)
Job Deliverables:
1) Administrative support: Follow up with customers by phone and email to get the necessary information and to collect their personal, tax, and accounting documents to be used for the above accounting calculation. 
2) Accounting calculation (draft): Verify supporting documentation and complete accounting calculation in an Excel template to determine customer&amp;#039;s past and current income. Calculate income loss and corresponding weekly benefit amount.
3) Create a report (draft): Using a MS Word template, create a summary report that shows the weekly benefit amount calculation including a summary of key facts, supporting documents, and assumptions made to calculate this amount based on the regulation above as well as the unique customer&amp;#039;s case.
4) Calculation and report (final): A certified accountant on our team will review the draft calculation and report. Some customer follow up and adjustments may be needed, after this initial review. Please create the final report / calculation with these adjustments.
Skills / Requirements:
- Good understanding of accounting principals
- Knowledge of Canadian accounting and tax rules for individuals, businesses, and self-employed
- Knowledge of how to calculate personal and self-employed income / loss
- Ability to give and receive calls to/from Canadian phone numbers
- Ability to work through an email account (on Gmail), which we will provide to you
- Good communication skills and great follow-up skills
- Fluent written and oral English
- Detail oriented, especially with numbers
- Customer focused
Payment Structure (for each report):
CAD $75 - admin follow up finished and customer documentation received 
CAD $125 - upon completion of the draft calculation and report
CAD $200 - upon completion of the final version of the report.
This is a repeating project. We expect to have 2-3 report requests per month.Budget: $325
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Customer Discovery,                     Customer Support,                     Financial Accounting,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 15:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>PPC (SEM) +SMM + SEO Professional - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/PPC-SEM-SMM-SEO-Professional_%7E019f4ca259868e9c91?source=rss</link>
    <description>PPC (Adwords, Bing)
SEO (on-page + off page)
Social media marketing (SMM): facebook, instagram, linkedin, twitter etc.
Google Analytics
HTML/CSS
Expert in sem, seo, smm and analytics
MS Excel (can handle formula, pivot tables)
Can build marketing calendar and content calendar
It is a part time, monthly job, Salary. NOT HOURLY
Mountain Time Zone
I will only accept applications if your cover letter says &amp;amp;quot;I CAN DO THIS&amp;amp;quot; at the beginning.
NO AGENCIES. We only work with Independent contractorsBudget: $400
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; SEM - Search Engine Marketing
Skills:        Facebook Marketing,                     Google AdWords,                     Google Analytics,                     Internet Marketing,                     Marketing Strategy,                     Pay Per Click,                     Pay Per Click Advertising,                     Search Engine Marketing (SEM),                     Search Engine Optimization (SEO),                     SEO Keyword Research,                     Social Media Marketing            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 15:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Power BI Developer (Full Stack) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Power-Developer-Full-Stack_%7E01a22a39961e08f8e4?source=rss</link>
    <description>&amp;bull;Create and maintain technical design documentation
&amp;bull;Perform quality coding to business and technical specifications
&amp;bull;Work directly with business units to define and prototype Power BI Dashboards
&amp;bull;Extracting, transforming and loading data from multiple sources into Power BI applications
&amp;bull;Design, create and tune physical database objects (tables, views, indexes) to support logical and dimensional models; maintain the referential integrity of the database
&amp;bull;Deep experience in MSBI (SSIS, SSAS)
&amp;bull;Experience building OLAP Cubes is a prerequisite along with RLS
&amp;bull;Proficiency in TSQL queries
&amp;bull;Experience Azure databases
Experience: 3 to 7 yrs.
Location: Baner, Pune
Qualifications
Any technical Graduate / Post GraduateBudget: $10
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Visualization
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     Microsoft Power BI,                     Microsoft Power BI Development,                     Microsoft SQL SSAS,                     SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS)            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Latex Professional - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Latex-Professional_%7E015f712d6c48c185bd?source=rss</link>
    <description>Transcription of text using Latex into MS Excel or Google spreadsheet
Interested Folks, please share the sample of your past work.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Google Spreadsheets,                     LaTeX,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 12:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Formatting Team Leader â€“ to lead a team of data analysts handling CRM database migrations - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Formatting-Team-Leader-lead-team-data-analysts-handling-CRM-database-migrations_%7E017d6fa0b278b3e826?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi there, thanks for taking the time to consider our contract.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
âž¢	Are you a data genius who has a proven history of successfully transforming data for CRM database migrations? 
âž¢	Do you have the experience and skills to lead a team of data analysts?
&amp;amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Do you have the technical skills to solve data formatting problems?
âž¢	Are you available from 3:00am GMT (8:30am IST) daily for 30+ hours per week to work with a client based in Australia?
Our business assists real estate agencies migrate from one CRM database to another and our team has now grown to the point where we need a skilled team leader to oversee and manage the various projects.
WHAT WE ARE LOOKING FOR
âž¢	You will need to have the ability to review and understand various source data tables (excel files with 100,000+ records).
âž¢	You will need to develop instructions/mapping logic to transform the source data files from the client into the import templates (excel) of the destination CRM database.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
âž¢	You will need to write scripts (or have a data analyst develop scripts) to efficiently process the data.
âž¢	You need to be available to answer queries on the logic and provide guidance to the analysts.
âž¢	You need to review the transformed data to ensure it&amp;rsquo;s mapped correctly and provide feedback to correct any errors.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
âž¢	You need to review the quality of the data and provide logic / instructions to ensure that it&amp;rsquo;s cleaned up.
âž¢	You need to think independently and work to find a solution to problems that may arise.
âž¢	You need to have an eye for creating systems and process that are clear for others to understand and you need to thrive in providing direction and delegating tasks to the team of analysts.
âž¢	You need to be available from 1pm Melbourne, Australia time (AEST).
âž¢	The role will involve a combination of team leader and data analyst responsibilities (it will not be 100% team leader from the beginning but will transition as more projects come online).
SKILLS REQUIRED:
âž¢	Expert user of Excel (advanced formulas, VBA tools etc.), MS Access or equivalent software to create efficient solutions to handle data with minimal manual intervention
âž¢	Strong attention to detail to ensure accurate and high quality work is delivered
âž¢	Great communicator - responsive to the client and your team (providing timely and clear communication)
âž¢	Speedy and efficient &amp;ndash; you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with various data formats and software options to complete projects on time and meet deadlines
âž¢	Logical and organised in your approach to work
âž¢	A willingness and interest in working with others, being patient and encouraging of those in your team
âž¢	Possess an ability to look at how you can develop the skills of others in the team
âž¢	An understanding / exposure to the real estate industry would be advantageous
YOUR APPLICATION
If you think you&amp;rsquo;re made of the right stuff and fit with what we&amp;rsquo;re after please do the following:
1. Address your application to &amp;lsquo;Dear Chris&amp;rsquo; (any generic application will be rejected).
2. Answer the screening questions.
3. Ensure your rate is within the specified range ($7-$15/hr).
Please note: you must be available to work with an Australian client and you need to have immediate capacity for the work. 
ABOUT US
We are a technology company that assists our clients (real estate agents) to choose the best CRM database for their business and help them migrate from their existing database solution to a new database solution. 
We are engaged by our clients to: 1) Transform the source data into the import templates of the destination CRM and 2) Format and clean-up (including managing duplicates) the source data to ensure better quality data. 
We are currently experiencing a growth phase and need an additional resource who is available for 30+ hours a week.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Initially the work will involve a combination of 1) reviewing the work of two analysts; and 2) scoping and developing data transformation instructions/logic, scripts and tools for future projects.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
At the moment we are using a combination of MS Access and Excel but we are open to solutions if they can be demonstrated to be superior.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Access VBA,                     Data Entry,                     Data Migration,                     Data Scraping,                     DataTables,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Excel VBA,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Spreadsheets            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data engineer / architect needed to write educational content on AWS, Hadoop tools &amp;amp;amp; architectures - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-engineer-architect-needed-write-educational-content-AWS-Hadoop-tools-amp-architectures_%7E018bcdf90edcd4f5ae?source=rss</link>
    <description>We&amp;#039;re a big data company that&amp;#039;s looking to level up the content we produce. We&amp;#039;re looking for an engineer / DBA / software architect who:
- Has deep knowledge and experience with big data tools and architectures
- Can present this knowledge in a compelling fashion by writing articles and creating diagrams
The job will be to write educational content such as best practices guides and tool comparisons on technical aspects of working with big data, including: Lambda architecture, working with Apache Kafka, ETL tools, AWS/Azure ecosystem (esp. Kinesis, Athena, S3), Hadoop ecosystem (Spark, MapReduce), real-time databases (Cassandra, Redis, DynamoDB).
Examples of the type of content we&amp;#039;d like to see:
https://engineering.depop.com/data-swamp-to-data-lake-on-aws-part-2-12b2bf80ba7a
https://medium.com/teads-engineering/spark-performance-tuning-from-the-trenches-7cbde521cf60
https://blog.timescale.com/sql-vs-flux-influxdb-query-language-time-series-database-290977a01a8a
The first article you will be requested to write is: Airflow vs Oozie for Workflow Management.
Our goal is to produce materials that a software engineer with 5-10 years of experience would find helpful and engaging. This means that the technical skills are required and non-negotiable - we&amp;#039;re looking to hire engineers, not technical/content writers, and are willing to pay accordingly.
Job has the potential to turn into long-term collaboration as we will be needing new content on a regular basis, but will start with a single article.Budget: $450
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Article &amp;amp; Blog Writing
Skills:        Big Data,                     Data Engineering,                     Data Science,                     Distributed Computing,                     Hadoop,                     Software Architecture            Country: Israelclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 09:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>MySQL DBA&amp;#039;s needed for short task - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/MySQL-DBA-needed-for-short-task_%7E0146f4731d87f2418c?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi DBA&amp;#039;s ,
I am looking for MYSQL DBA for short time of help for about 2 hours from 7 PM IST to 9 PM IST on 27 September. Mysql expertise need Replication , Query tuning , Mysql upgrade and basic system administration help . Will be paid good for 2 hours.Please send proposal only if available for above mentioned duration.
ThanksPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        AWS ECS,                     Database Administration,                     Database Design,                     Linux System Administration,                     MySQL Administration,                     SQL            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 08:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior WEB application developer and technical architect - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-WEB-application-developer-and-technical-architect_%7E010d51eb4a86b9ef0f?source=rss</link>
    <description>we looking for senior developer who is hands on with best industry practice for the development using Angular JS, HTML 5, Java Script, /j query, ASP.net c#, SQL server.
Job Description:
We already developed web application tat we would like to deploy as cloud solution and invite customers to use on subscription basis. we looking for technical architect who can guide as on the followings
Payment Gateway Integration
Hosting multiple websites on one server with a single IP
Subdomain &amp;ndash; customization
Source code control.. version control etc
Dashboard
Security
Password
Take user machine control
On-premise &amp;ndash; how to protect our product
API /web service &amp;ndash; need clarity
Additional tasks 
Application segmentation/Separation
Technical Debt
Cloud server setup
Error logging, monitoring and notifications
DB Backup plan
Architecture diagram and documentationBudget: $200
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        AngularJS,                     CSS,                     HTML,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     Web Design,                     Website Development            Country: Omanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 06:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQL programmer needed.  Python experience desirable. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-programmer-needed-Python-experience-desirable_%7E01bd9548dfe2fd2526?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need to offload actual coding for a very large (Access) database project.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Very simple programming, but very large datasets, and program must be carefully developed with an eye towards repeatability with dataset updates.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our algorithm has already been largely defined.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Client will retain all work product, and all intellectual property and all communication and work notes will be proprietary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Compensation format is negotiable (ie hours, lines, deliverables).
WARNING:. This posting is to establish cost and terms for this (database) scope of work, but actual engagement will be subject to subsequent succesful negotiations with the end customer/client, and also subject to clients decisions as to in-house vs outsource coding.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Code developed will rely partially on clients underlying dataset rights and paid API licenses held directly by the client.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;No data, samples, code, notes, algorithms, flow charts, methodologies or the like will be retained by the programming team under any circumstances.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If retaining copies of your work is important to you, do not apply.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If being able to talk about this specific code or the algorithm/method in future engagements or interviews is important to you, do not apply.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you believe that extensions built partially in open APIs or code sets should also be inherently open, do not apply.
We are looking for a creative lone wolf programmer, not a consultant.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge is valued over formal education.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;College students&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;may apply, but this will be time consuming and fast-paced.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will not need a company/LLC, business cards, business suit, logo or brand.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We don&amp;#039;t care who/what/how you are as an individual, as long as you can act and communicate as a professional.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Three exceptions:. 1) Project/programming will incorporate data visualization schemes, so candidate should have at least some visual ability. 2) Candidate must be able to be verbally (highly) communicative.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Email alone will not suffice.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3) Preference (may) be given to candidates based on geographic proximity centered between southern Virginia and northern North Carolina.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Raleigh, Greensboro, Richmond, Charlottesville, Roanoke, Blacksburg, but more distant candidates certainly considered.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Early stage development team may be required to meet in person, but travel would be very limited.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working hours will be extremely flexible. Corresponding flexibility will be expected of you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Initial stage is expected to begin immediately and be completed in 90 days.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;No guarantee of retention for later stages.
Primary work will be centered on SQL queries, but will overlap into statistical functions, social databases, Python and/or scraping tools, and large proprietary dataset APIs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Post engagement, the successful candidate will have documented exposure/experience (resume/references) with a significant and diverse set of large, expensive, corporate entity databases which are typically only available to those employed in investment banking or corporate development roles.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;While none of the data will be retained, post engagement, the candidate will be able to reference (most) of the datasets they will by then be familiar with.
Terms of employment mentioned herein are not intended to be binding.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Candidate will be expected to commit to extensive, project-specific NDA and IP and Employment Agreements, which will be binding and vigorously enforced.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will be helping to discover and jointly create exciting new intellectual property, which you will not own, and which you will agree to be prohibited from recreating elsewhere.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Data Scraping,                     Database Design,                     Python,                     Salesforce.com,                     SQL,                     Statistics,                     Web Scraping            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 02:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>General/Recruitment Administrator - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/General-Recruitment-Administrator_%7E016dfba5f1228a00d8?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for an experienced general administrator to assist with the daily requirements of a recruitment business.
Tasks will be along the lines of the following;
- Formatting Candidates CV into the standard company format, saving as word and PDF files
- Receiving emails, calls, messages, texts and WhatsApp messages from candidates and arranging calls within my diary for me to carry out initial pre screen stage telephone interviews.
- Arranging various stage interviews for candidates between candidate, client and myself
- utilising LinkedIn to be part of the company, assist growth and share social media links/posts as often as possible
- occasionally using the company crm to add companies, locations and contact details of other recruitment agencies
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Calendar Management,                     CRM,                     Customer Service,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Microsoft Office 365,                     Virtual Assistant,                     WordPress            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 01:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>QuickBooks Online Australian version -  Invoice templates from .docx format to import into QBO - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/QuickBooks-Online-Australian-version-Invoice-templates-from-docx-format-import-into-QBO_%7E01de22b6eb35259867?source=rss</link>
    <description>we require an expert in design of .docx templates to upload to QuickBooks online 
we can give you 2 sets of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;templates to work in - in the .docx format 
but we need this to be expertly formatted to our clients instructions - 
then this has to be uploaded to QuickBooks Online successfully we can do this part but only if your design works 
we require 4 templates to be made to upload in different styles 
adding colour to template to match clients main logo
2 logos required 
only people that have achieved&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;this successfully before and successfully had the template uploaded to QuickBooks Online are invited to apply for this jobPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Certified Public Accountant (CPA),                     Computer Graphics,                     Database Design,                     Format &amp;amp; Layout,                     Graphic Design,                     Intuit QuickBooks,                     Letterhead Design,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Microsoft Office 365            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 22:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Drop shipping Researcher/Drop shipping manager - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Drop-shipping-Researcher-Drop-shipping-manager_%7E0133c17a879d9cac2f?source=rss</link>
    <description>Ebay Virtual Assistant/Drop shipping manager/ Shopify expert/Oberlo
Product Research
Zik Analytics
Importing product on to Ebay/Yaballe from Amazon/Aliexpress
Product Listing
Preferable skills on: 
Adobe Photoshop
Theme Designer
MS Excel
MS Word
Data Entry
The project starting part time basis but want to increase to full time basis depends on VA&amp;#039;s success rate.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Ecommerce Development
Skills:        Drop Shipping,                     Shopify            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Real Estate Virtual Assistant. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Real-Estate-Virtual-Assistant_%7E0187c12ff68f645eb4?source=rss</link>
    <description>1) Looking for an experienced Virtual Assistant for Real Estate. I am both a Realtor and Investor
2) Must speak and write perfect English
3) Must know how to answer phones professionally
4) Must be available 9AM - 5PM Eastern time 
5) Must know MS Office, Google Drive, Excel, And others
6) Must be able to do research on property and addresses
7) Must have experience as a real estate assistant
8) Must be available for a video interview. No exceptions.
9) Must have experience making telemarketing calls and talking to people
10) Must be very friendly
11) Answer and making phone callsPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Executive Assistant Needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Executive-Assistant-Needed_%7E01e5962004c3e9dcba?source=rss</link>
    <description>Seeking a hard-working, technology savvy and passion-driven individual for an assistant position to the CEO of a mission-based startup.
This position will require a jack(ie) of all trades to help me manage multiple projects that include online content and media production, marketing and promotions and coaching and speaking work.
MUST be passionate about helping others and making a difference in the world.
Please include the following in your reply subject or first line to be considered - &amp;amp;quot;IGNTD Star Application&amp;amp;quot; - This way I&amp;#039;ll know you actually read this
Full Job Description Below:
Executive Assistant Job Description
IGNTD is looking for a new Executive Assistant to support our CEO. You will manage mostly business related tasks for the team such as helping creating reports, organizing travel and accommodation, taking meeting minutes, and other organizational tasks. To perform this role properly you should have a detailed understanding of the full Microsoft Office suite, social media tools (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, etc) and be extremely comfortable with technology while also being extremely fast at solving problems and have experience as an executive or administration assistant in the past. The ideal candidate is highly self-motivated, professional, and capable of managing their work load and prioritizing tasks in a fast-paced corporate environment.
Executive Assistant Responsibilities:
Maintaining executive&amp;rsquo;s appointment schedule by planning and scheduling meetings, conferences, telecommunications and travel.
Conserving executive&amp;rsquo;s time by reading, researching, and routing correspondence; drafting letters and documents; collecting and analyzing information; initiating telecommunication.
Maintaining executive and customer confidence and protecting operations by keeping information confidential.
Helping with audio and video documentation (and/or setup of those) on an ongoing basis for dissemination.
Preparing financial statements, reports, memos, invoices letters, and other documents.
Answering phones and routing calls to the correct person or taking messages.
Handling basic bookkeeping tasks.
Filing and retrieving corporate records, documents, and reports.
Researching and conducting data preparation to prepare documents for review and presentation.
Helping prepare for meetings/talks/interviews/appearances.
Managing project tasks, assignment, schedules and workloads to assure timely deliverability of end products with an eye towards quality
Accurately recording minutes from meetings.
Greeting visitors and deciding if they should be able to meet with executives.
Using various software, including word processing, spreadsheets, databases, presentation software and online cloud-based sales and marketing tools.
Reading and analyzing incoming memos, submissions, and distributing them as needed.
Making travel arrangements for executives.
Performing office duties that include ordering supplies and managing a records database
Experience as a virtual assistant.
Opening, sorting and distributing incoming faxes, emails, and other correspondence.
Provide general administrative support.
Executive Assistant Requirements:
Proven experience (3+ years) as an executive assistant or other relevant administrative support experience.
True passion for being part of a team with a mission and purpose
In-depth understanding of entire MS Office suite.
High school diploma (college preferred).
Ability to organize a daily workload by priorities.
Must be able to meet deadlines in a fast-paced quickly changing environment.
Strong organization skills, project management and problem-solving skills and impeccable multi-tasking abilities.
A proactive approach to problem-solving with strong decision-making skills.
Professional level verbal and written communications skills.
Position Specifics:
This is a salaried, exempt, position. Most weeks will require 40 hours of work during regular business hours, but some may require effort outside of those bounds (e.g., book launch events, certain talks, etc.). The goal is to get the work done in a timely manner.Regular work hours are between 9am and 6pm (including lunch), punctuality matters!
This position will be privy to very sensitive information &amp;ndash; both business related, methods related and of a health information nature. All information will be kept in strictest confidence and not shared (a separate NDA will be signed).
Creativity and fun are required!Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Other - Admin Support
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Email Etiquette,                     Email Handling,                     English Grammar,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Project Management,                     Telephone Handling,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior Google Professional Data Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-Google-Professional-Data-Engineer_%7E014eff90da774620ec?source=rss</link>
    <description>Appnovation is seeking self-starter Senior Data Engineer with Google Cloud Professional Data Engineer certification to lead our team on upcoming client projects. Candidates should possess excellent time and task management skills, have proficient team communications (oral &amp;amp;amp; written), and be able to either telecommute from home or work in one of our regional offices.
Senior Google Data Engineer Primary Responsibilities
&amp;bull;	Contribute to the design of industry-leading cloud-based data/software solutions to run on Google Cloud.
&amp;bull;	Follow trends in technology and lead new approaches to scalability and high-availability of distributed cloud container architecture &amp;amp;amp; services.
&amp;bull;	Design, architect and implement Google Cloud features and functionality.
&amp;bull;	Work with the team to develop web and mobile applications, APIs, SDKs and other tools as required.
&amp;bull;	Document software designs, functional and design specifications, presentations, and other documents as needed.
&amp;bull;	Work with our team on pre-sales scoping as a technical expert.
Senior Google Professional Data Engineer Qualifications
&amp;bull;	MS in Computer Science or equivalent program from an accredited University/College.
&amp;bull;	10+ years of hands-on experience in engineering as a senior contributor.
&amp;bull;	Experience working with Cloud platforms such as Google Cloud, AWS or Azure; big data pipelines and management
&amp;bull;	Experience with data security for data at rest and in transit (firewalls, hashing, encryption, SSL)
&amp;bull;	Experience automating and managing key business data pipelines to deliver the output of models to targeted applications
&amp;bull;	Excellent SQL coding and experience with a broad array of development tools and platforms including a strong Linux background and big data environment tools/languages, such as SQL, R, SAS, Python, etc.
&amp;bull;	Experience with Google data tools such as MySQL, Postgress, Bigtable, Dataflow, Spanner, BigQuery
&amp;bull;	Hands-on experience with two or more of: Go, python, php, Java, .Net, node.js.
&amp;bull;	Detailed knowledge of and experience with Google Cloud billing.
&amp;bull;	Able to collaborate and thrive in a fast-paced diverse high-performance environment.
&amp;bull;	Demonstrated excellence in written and verbal communications.
&amp;bull;	Google Professional Data Engineer certification.Budget: $5,000
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 19:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Short term Contract work for data entry in Bangalore. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Short-term-Contract-work-for-data-entry-Bangalore_%7E0147650208f46d8a97?source=rss</link>
    <description>Short term Contract work for data entry in Bangalore. Person has to come to event location for data registration. Immediate requirement. 
- Knowledge or experience in MS office and any internet based application
-Positive attitude
-Proficiency in data entry and englishBudget: $100
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 14:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Executive Virtual Assistant For An Amazon Influencer And Seller - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Executive-Virtual-Assistant-For-Amazon-Influencer-And-Seller_%7E016dcd4c4dbe5c2913?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are currently needing an additional Virtual Assistant for our team who can help with scheduling, email management, etc.
You should be knowledgable on Amazon.
For the first couple of months, you are required to work alongside existing VAs in assisting the CEO with everyday business tasks such as:
Replying to email messages from multiple inboxes in a timely manner.
Completing tasks on Trello.
Organizing and managing the CEO&amp;rsquo;s appointments or bookings using Google Calendar
You should be knowledgable in the following:
Amazon Seller Central
Amazon FBA
Scraping Amazon Listings
Updating Amazon Listings
You must be a quick learner and highly efficient, with proven experience working in the same industry in a demanding, fast-paced virtual environment.
Here are the assets that you NEED to bring to the table:
- Excellent verbal and written English skills
- Advanced organizational and project management skills
- Tech-savvy
- Intermediate working knowledge of MS Excel and Google Apps
- Availability to work from 9 AM to 6 PM EST (weekends and holidays might be required at minimal hours.
- Must be easily reachable through email and SkypePosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 14:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Salesforce CRM Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Salesforce-CRM-Developer_%7E0191ac8ae22d1ccf08?source=rss</link>
    <description>At least 4+ years experience working in the IT industry
3+ years of experience developing custom applications on the Salesforce Force.com platform using Apex and Visualforce
Strong understanding of Salesforce Declarative Programming and Administration (develop code, custom objects, Lightning components, Visualforce pages, Apex, reports, workflows, assignment rules, and more)
Knowledge of APEX triggers/SOQL queries and stored procedures
Experience with Salesforce.com Web Services APIs
Experience with Salesforce Visualforce Sites and Communities
Solid understanding of web technologies, such as HTTP, JavaScript, AJAX, HTML, DHTML, CSS and a solid understanding of Object-Oriented design and programming concepts
Ability to work in a fast-paced setting and prioritize among competing tasks and assignments
Must be a self-starter, with the ability to work independently without constant supervision and micromanagement
Must be able to work flexible hours to collaborate with remote IT and business team members
Excellent analytical, organizational and problem-solving skills
Excellent written and oral communication skills
Strong customer service mentality
In Addition, Preferable Skills And Behaviors Include
Salesforce.com Developer certification
Java Developer or SQL certification
Work experience using standard HTML/CSS practicesPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; ERP / CRM Software
Skills:        CRM,                     JavaScript,                     Python,                     Salesforce Apex,                     Salesforce App Development,                     Salesforce.com            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 08:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Transcribe minutes of the meeting - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Transcribe-minutes-the-meeting_%7E01852aa8409119fd22?source=rss</link>
    <description>Individuals who can transcribe audio content of financial results conferences, group project meetings and other general business meetings. Experience with audio transcription is required.
Must type 80+ WPM, have excellent grammar and proofreading skills, have experience with MS Word and Excel, and must demonstrate strong computer literacy.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Active Listening,                     Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     Microsoft Word,                     Transcription            Country: United Arab Emiratesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 06:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Create kibana visualization dashboard - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Create-kibana-visualization-dashboard_%7E011e52084b51586841?source=rss</link>
    <description>Input will be log files and SQL queries. Use filebeat/logstash and elasticsearch.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Budget: $25
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Visualization
Skills:        Data Visualization            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 04:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Digital Marketing Assistant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Digital-Marketing-Assistant_%7E0127df2a63b6c2a3dd?source=rss</link>
    <description>Seeking a full-time Digital Marketing Assistant to help with day to day reporting and tasks related to marketing, analysis and merchandising. Take a look at our websites: CellularOutfitter.com, WirelessEmporium.com and Mobovida.com.
Daily Tasks:
- Assisting the execution of various daily tasks in multiple digital marketing channels: PPC, Facebook/IG, Email, content marketing and more
- Assistance with day-to-day mgmt. of social media channels and online branding initiatives
- Daily KPI reporting and marketing analytics
- Social media comment monitoring, engagement and influencer outreach
- Customer service via chat and email as needed
REQUIRED Experience:
- Prior hands-on Internet Marketing experience preferred (Google Adwords, Facebook Ads or Email)
- Type 70+ WPM
- Proficient as MS office suite, ESPECIALLY Excel (pivot tables, vlookups etc.)
- Tech and software savvy - Basic HTML/CSS a plus
- Social Media savvy (Instagram, Pinterest, FB, Twitter and more)
- Adobe Photoshop a plus
- STRONG communication skills w/native English language proficiency
- USA onlyPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; SEM - Search Engine Marketing
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Email Marketing,                     Facebook Marketing,                     Google Analytics,                     Internet Marketing,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Pay Per Click Advertising,                     Social Media Marketing            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 01:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>VDI Systems Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/VDI-Systems-Engineer_%7E016e019c0b918d8cf2?source=rss</link>
    <description>NOTE: You will need to work US time zone, Please READ IT ALL
The VDI System Engineer will support existing customer base, responding to queries and providing
expertise in relation to cloud services. He/She will work alongside customers to identify, address and
resolve technical issues. The VDI Engineer will work directly with customers through daily
interactions via email, phone, WebEx and occasional in-person meetings.
&amp;nbsp;
To pre-qualify in consideration for this role, the desired candidate must be able to speak very good
English and have a solid technical background and aptitude, with a desire to learn while on the job
and actively work towards obtaining relevant technical certifications. Exceptional customer service
skills and an unwavering commitment to provide a positive customer experience are musts.
&amp;nbsp;
Roles and Responsibilities
This candidate will be responsible for providing support&amp;nbsp;for cloud based solutions including
DAAS/VDI, server hosting, application virtualization, backup and disaster recovery. In addition to
customer support, the technical specialist will help perform maintenance and other activities on-site
at data center facility.
&amp;nbsp;
The candidate will work closely with Sales Teams, Engineering, Support, PM and Customer
Experience (CX) teams to ensure support meets and exceeds customer needs.
&amp;nbsp;
The ideal candidate has exceptional interpersonal skills and can &amp;ldquo;wow&amp;rdquo; customers. He or she should
meet the following criteria or have equivalent experience.
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;At least 2-3 years&amp;rsquo; professional experience in a related field and/or similar role
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Established knowledge of cloud products and technologies including desktop, server
and application virtualization
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Preference given to candidates with experience in the following areas:
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;VDI design, implementation, administration and troubleshooting (Citrix, Vmware etc)
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Remote Desktop Services, application publishing,
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Public clouds,&amp;nbsp;backup, HA and disaster recovery technologies,&amp;nbsp;migrating customer data
and services to the cloud&amp;nbsp;
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Windows Server 2008R2/2012R2/2016
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Microsoft Active Directory, GPO, File Services, DFS, Roaming profiles,
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Office 365, Exchange
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;MS SQL
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;VMware ESXi, Hypver, KVM, physical to virtual migration, Cloud migration
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Windows XP Professional/Vista/Windows 7/windows 10
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;VPN setups
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Network troubleshooting &amp;ndash; latency, bandwidth, packet tracing
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Performance Optimization on windows servers and desktops
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Backup and Recovery
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Data Center technologies &amp;ndash; server farm, SAN/NAS storage, Network switches
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Patch Management, anti-virus management,
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Security, Multi-factor authentication, encryption
&amp;nbsp;
Microsoft-certified candidates are preferred. **
Please submit your monthly rate as this is a full time job.Budget: $1,500
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon Web Services,                     Citrix NetScaler,                     Citrix XenServer,                     Linux System Administration,                     Microsoft Windows Server,                     Network Administration,                     Network Security,                     System Administration,                     Windows Administration            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 23:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>RxLens - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/RxLens_%7E018ab39ab5c9b2965d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Seeking Expert help in creating a web based inventory management system. This system will be used to track daily drug activity. The System should accurately display Inventory on hand by tracking dispensing, receiving and other drug related activities ( returns, expired etc). The tool should also track average usage and suggest what item to buy and or return on a daily basis. tool should eventually be able to retrieve information from third party for pricing file and update automatically daily. Insurance reconciliation is another area within the tool that needs to be built. SQL experience is a plus since the tool will communicate with different types of software. It may require industry standard format so its easy to build inter-phase or transfer information.
Its a retail pharmacy industry that has 100&amp;#039;s of transactions on daily basis and needs to stay compliant, and control inventory. I am looking to build this tool for in house use at our multiple location.
the tool should have a search query.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        MySQL Administration,                     Website Development,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 20:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Spring Batch and Java based  Back-End Utility - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Spring-Batch-and-Java-based-Back-End-Utility_%7E01ff2c8513a55145f8?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a very small Java/Spring Batch based utility that can read .csv and .xml files from an input directory and perform 2 step validation on the data read from the .CSV and XML and finally write the records to a report into an output directory. Those records that fail the validation only should go into the output report. Need unit tests and production level coding with clean comment and formatting.
Prefer using latest technologies like: Spring batch for csv processing, Jackson for xml, Java8 features.Budget: $60
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        J2EE,                     Java,                     Spring Framework            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Database Administrator to review/optimize MySQL Database for current and future growth - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Database-Administrator-review-optimize-MySQL-Database-for-current-and-future-growth_%7E01b8f1366c4eef102c?source=rss</link>
    <description>-MySQL 5.7 on CentOS 6.10 server
-Able to review current implementation and provide recommendations to improve performance when pulling data via queries
-10+ million rowsPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Database Design,                     MySQL Administration            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Call for a RDF/Graphical database developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Call-for-RDF-Graphical-database-developer_%7E0174abaf1836309f0b?source=rss</link>
    <description>The goal is to export information from the spreadsheet into a graphical database in RDF (linked data). We have some code available for this from a previous project. Simple SPARQL queries should be queryable on the database and content editable on the DB directly (moving away from spreadsheets) and through forms connected to the DB.Budget: $800
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Database Design,                     Database Management,                     Microsoft Excel,                     MySQL Administration,                     MySQL Programming,                     Resource Description Framework (RDF),                     SQL            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 17:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Email Support Associate - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Email-Support-Associate_%7E0164cd43c56a8964b5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Job Description:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Peak Support is a customer service and business process outsourcing company.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are seeking Email Support representatives from the Philippines to join our growing team.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We are currently shortlisting for a Customer Service Representative who is physically located in the Philippines and has PLDT connection.
Some requirements for this position:
- Strong verbal and written English skills 
- Someone who enjoys working with others on a team
- Experience in a Customer Support environment
- Vast Experience in Email/Chat Support 
- Research-oriented and Process-Oriented
- Can work with minimal supervision
- Above Average MS Excel Skills
Technical Requirements:
- Good computer setup with Chrome browser
- minimum of 8gb RAM
- minimum processor:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;i5 4th Generation, AMD A8 5000 series, or higher
- Stable high-speed internet connection (at least 5-10 mbps) 
- Stable power supply in your area&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
- Noise cancellation headset 
- Skype accountPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Customer Service &amp;gt; Customer Service
Skills:        Customer Service,                     English,                     English Grammar,                     Salesforce.com            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 16:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant Needed for a New Kindle Publishing Company - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant-Needed-for-New-Kindle-Publishing-Company_%7E013e425696caccb2a8?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi Everyone,
Our company is looking to hire a long-term virtual assistant to help us with various tasks in our publishing business as we continue to grow. 
It is preferred the assistant to possess some knowledge and experience with the publishing business or any type of online business. However, even if this is your first time, we will provide training. 
Our goal is to build a long-term relationship with our assistant. Therefore it is important for you to value these qualities as much as we do:
- Integrity
- Availability
- Communication (MUST BE FLUENT ENGLISH: Reading, Writing, Speaking)
- Organized
- Follow instructions
- Take initiative
- Reliable internet
- Ability to meet deadlines
The job will consist of the tasks listed below. Note: in the beginning, you are not required to do all of them. We will teach them to you one by one. As you learn more, your pay will increase as well. 
- Efficient with MS words and Excel
- Amazon keyword research
- Amazon book categories research
- Contact Amazon support for various tasks
- E-book and paperback formatting
- Promote books using software, forms, and social media (we provide software)
- Soft-manage author&amp;#039;s social media
- Soft-manage/interact with the author&amp;#039;s email list
- Email potential readers
More responsibilities will be given as time goes on
It might seem like a long list, but the tasks listed above will take maximum 2 hours a day. It should also be noted that during book launch weeks you might be busier. There will be days where you won&amp;#039;t be working at all. The starting rate is $80 per month (negotiable), with the possibility of a raise. Also, if we think you are capable of taking on more responsibilities, you will be promoted to co-manager and also receive a pay increase.
We are looking for someone who is committed, efficient, and able to work autonomously. If you are looking for a long-term job, and want to grow in the field of online business, please submit your application.
More details about the job will be discussed during the screening interview. We will also conduct a video chat with screened-in candidates. Lastly, please start your cover letter with the word &amp;amp;quot;Cloud&amp;amp;quot; so we know you actually read the post. 
Thank you,
ChaoBudget: $80
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Customer Service,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     Email Marketing,                     Executive Assistant,                     Facebook Marketing,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Marketing,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Social Media Management,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Freelance Product Development Associate - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Freelance-Product-Development-Associate_%7E01bf1a4f5b8f3f7f7a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Responsibilities:
- Set up style numbers, SKUs, UPCs and create purchase orders.
- Handle daily correspondence with factories. Liaison with design, sales, tech, and traffic dept as needed.
- Work with production team members to oversee all time and action calendars and production WIP charts. Follow up with overseas factories to ensure execution of all production orders
- Responsible for on-time deliveries of bulk orders, and timely communication with sales with any delivery updates
- Partner with the traffic and accounting department to make sure payment release and goods arrive in WH on time
- Approve/comment on shipping marks, packaging layouts etc.
- Create cost charts to review with the department head for relevancy and meeting the desired margin.
- Review, check and comment on samples for spec and quality.
- Reports directly to the Chief of Staff
Qualifications:
- 0-3 years of experience
- Proficiency in MS office, with a strong emphasis on Excel
- Excellent organizational and communication skills
- Very detail-oriented, flexible and able to multi-task
- Ability to problem solve and troubleshoot in a fast-paced environment.
- Working knowledge of garment construction, patterns, process and timelines, testing understanding a plus.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Adobe Illustrator,                     Adobe Photoshop            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 21:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Interactive Floor Plan Builder - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Interactive-Floor-Plan-Builder_%7E019981b208e7e68e26?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need to develop interactive floor plan builder for exhibition. Should have functionality to add, merge, spilt, assign stand to exhibitors, change text etc. with below specifications:
- Shoud be SVG Based
- All SVG Shapes should be saved and retrived from database as seperate recored e.g if there are 10 stands on the floor plan there should be 10 records in the database.
- Shape Dimension should be stored in database for example if a particular shape is Square then it length and breadth should be stored in database. This means that the dimension that is stored in database according to that the shape should be visible in Front. If shape dimension is edited then its value must be updated in database.
- Merge/Split functionality of shapes. Its co-ordinates must be updated in database accordingly.
- Search functionality (Text written over shape, Shape number written over shape)
- Print functionality (By Text written over shape, By shape number written over shape, By some shapes that I want to print, By Shape dimension given on shape)
- Zoom out, Zoom in, Fit functionality.
- View functionality (just shape, Just by Text written over shape, Shape number written over shape, in 3D, Symbols given on floor plan like icons).
- Reports to generated from database in CSV.
See attached image for sample floor plan. Feel free to ask any query, Freelancers with previous experience in floor plan projects will be preferred, please send your previous work details, links etc. in proposal.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Adobe Flash,                     ASP.NET,                     C#,                     CSS,                     CSS3,                     HTML,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     Microsoft SQL Server Programming,                     SQL,                     SVG,                     Web Design,                     Website Development            Country: British Indian Ocean Territoryclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 12:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Text animation we are here to give our best and fresh work. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Text-animation-are-here-give-our-best-and-fresh-work_%7E01f5805a7d5f5678de?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need a company logo design. Want to design an ecommerce website. Want a joomla or WordPress website. Want graphics design. Ms word. Ms excel. PowerPoint projects. Text animationPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Illustrator,                     Adobe Photoshop,                     Banner Ad Design,                     Graphic Design,                     Logo Design,                     Photo Editing,                     Print Design,                     Print Layout Design,                     User Interface Design,                     Web Design            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 09:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Fulfillment Operations Manager - Remote position - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Fulfillment-Operations-Manager-Remote-position_%7E01cbe346bd03fccc76?source=rss</link>
    <description>Job Post: Fulfillment Operations Manager for a Fast Growing Ecommerce Company
We are looking for a Fulfillment Operations Manager, creative &amp;amp;amp; analytical, passionate about internet marketing and e-commerce who would like to work in a startup environment and grow exponentially, read on!
ABOUT THE COMPANY
Trafilea creates and expands disruptive customer-first global brands online.
We are data-driven enthusiasts, passionate about marketing, exponential technologies and innovation, leading the global, e-commerce, direct-to-consumer retail transformation.
We design, manufacture, promote, sell and distribute our products. We take care of the entire customer journey, delivering wow-worthy experiences that positively influence and empower millions of customers in the US and worldwide.
We are experts in online marketing with a world-class ability for online customer acquisition and branding strategies which have resulted in +150% year-over-year profitable growth.
Founded by millennials in May 2014, we favor remote ways of working, proudly employing 200+ freelancers from over 14 countries, who work from anywhere they want.
Trafilea provides an ideal environment for remote and freelance work. This has become a main advantage and one of the very means by which we actually comply with our main mission: changing people&amp;#039;s lives.
We have an always-growing mindset; we are ambitious, self-disciplined, passionate, goal-oriented individuals, optimistic about an abundant future and happy life.
Now, we&amp;rsquo;re looking for a full-time Fulfillment Operations Manager to join the journey!
Your Day-to-Day will look something like:
Track all order activity by day/week/month
Provide trending reports for order processing daily/weekly/monthly
Own the customer experience throughout the order cycle
Ensure the Humanscale brand is reflected at each touchpoint of the order entry process
Handle order related questions/concerns/escalation
Propose improvements and efficiencies in the order entry process
Create customer feedback loop on order process (CSAT/NPS)
Be a catalyst for continuous improvement
Prevent future issues from arising by assessing trending issues and partnering with the SPM team to created or modify process to address at the root cause
Proactively suggest solutions based on past resolutions and experience
Manage the order processing team across the US and Canada
Manages department staff including training, staff development, performance appraisals and assignments. Monitors goals versus attainment and takes corrective action when necessary.
Create an accountable environment with clear performance targets and career path opportunities
Required Skills:
*Excellent verbal and written communication skills (Fluent English is a must)
*Quick learner and problem solver; able to seek out solutions autonomously
*Professional leader with ability to manage remote teams
*Organised and accurate in your work with an understanding of supply chain/logistics principles
*Experience of customer ordering systems
*Advanced MS Excel Skills (V-lookups, pivot tables, formulas, filtering, sorting, formatting)
*Aptitude to analyze data to identify trends, issues and opportunities
*Warehouse Management Systems
Required Experience:
*2+ years of E-commerce experience in an Operations Management/Leadership/Supervisor role
Now, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the benefits of working with us.
Live Where You Want
Proximity doesn&amp;rsquo;t influence productivity. As a global distributed team, you can live and work wherever you want. 
Take Vacation (Seriously)
Yes, we&amp;rsquo;re growing and need your undivided attention, but we encourage you to take a vacation! It&amp;rsquo;s important to get out and do something.
Up Your Game
We love to see our people growing fast. We budget for it! Think courses, conferences, events&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s really up to you and your manager.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
What to Expect
Full-time, Shifting schedules
Freelance/Home-based
What We Have to Offer You
Competitive salary
Very good growth opportunities based on a result oriented compensation plan
Like we said, trainings and development opportunities are on us!
If After Reading This Job Post You Still Feel this Opportunity Is for You .. Please, Apply Now!Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Customer Service &amp;gt; Other - Customer Service
Skills:        Drop Shipping,                     Logistics &amp;amp; Shipping,                     Order Processing,                     Trend Analysis            Country: Uruguayclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 05:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Application configure and sql help - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Application-configure-and-sql-help_%7E01a6579207ac70e245?source=rss</link>
    <description>We need someone to make some changes in a software application for example we want to add fields like:
We take the client method of contact:
Work phone, mobile phone, email, etc. and we would like to add
&amp;#039;preferred method of contact&amp;#039;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A new field on the screen that will be saved to their record. 
I have another one but i have to get the exact spec during week but that would be conditional, if the answer is A then present another screen etc.
else if the answer was B present a different screen. The application has a good user community forum u can check for how they do these things. Basically, they use forms and the trick is to get a User table connected to it. THey are using a type of SQL based query.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 01:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer looking for customization for existing app (PhoneGap, AdobeCordova) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developer-looking-for-customization-for-existing-app-PhoneGap-AdobeCordova_%7E013760685540817b90?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have an existing app that was developed with PhoneGap (AdobeCordova). This app is used by different customers. The database is separate per customer and location. Communication or access is via a web service. For example, https://tld.com/app/customer/webservice. We would like to extend the app to include PushNotification for iOS and Android. We want to use a separate web service for each customer. Who can help us, what is needed on existing files? We provide a web service which is available e.g. in a table holding messages per user, the function looks e.g. like this...
public function getUserNotification ($ org)
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;{â€‹
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;$ sql = &amp;amp;quot;SELECT * from WebService_Notification WHERE OrgUnitID =&amp;amp;quot;. $ org. &amp;amp;quot;AND Received is null ORDER BY Date Desc&amp;amp;quot;;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;return $ this-&amp;amp;gt; query ($ sql);
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;}â€‹Budget: $300
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Platforms:Android,         iOS            Devices:Phone            
Country: Germanyclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 13:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant (advertising / Excel / research / data entry) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant-advertising-Excel-research-data-entry_%7E0122b3ef0b7b5eb8ee?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;#039;m looking for a skilled, independent and reliable person to do easy support and VA tasks for me. The first task would be in an online campaign platform (similar to Google Adwords), further tasks will include these things:
- creating campaigns on an advertising network according to a template
- adjusting campaigns according to requirements
- copying and uploading banners
- managing project&amp;#039;s content and social networks
- merging two Excel sheets with data into one
- using Excel macros
- analyzing web data
Time availability depends on you, can be part-time but I have enough work for full-time as well. You can work whenever you want as long as you reply to my messages.
All of these tasks can be done directly in a web browser and previous experience is not necessary but of course it is an advantage. This task does not include any sales or making or recieving any phone calls, yet you will be given different kind of various tasks. We&amp;acute;ll start with easy tasks, and as you develop, and learn new things, I&amp;acute;ll give you more challenging/interesting assignments. If you read the description, write 9%2 in your bid. I&amp;#039;m looking for self motivated person who can easily understand the tasks and follow the given steps, you are expected to have good skills with MS Excel and advanced internet research.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Content Writing,                     Customer Service,                     Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     HTML,                     Internet Research,                     Media Buying,                     Pay Per Click Advertising,                     Project Management,                     Research,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: Czech Republicclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 12:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need CodeIgniter Developers for Custom Ticket Tracker Website - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-CodeIgniter-Developers-for-Custom-Ticket-Tracker-Website_%7E014417fc989a74dd22?source=rss</link>
    <description>OBJECTIVE: Code a &amp;amp;quot;ticket&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;bug&amp;amp;quot; tracker site.
LANGUAGES/FRAMEWORKS:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;PHP/mySQL/CodeIgniter
TOOLS YOU WILL USE:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;GIT / OpenVPN
Our goal is to create a custom ticketing tracker, similar to Redmine (https://www.redmine.org/), for our secure server system. Webpages will be created with CodeIgniter, and developers will use PHP to query some SQL databases and display the information to the users. Any applicant will have to be able to communicate with Skype and log into our secure system. Additionally, all work will be monitored with Upwork screen recording, and progress will be tracked with another issue tracking service. We are looking for 2 or 3 developers to work on this project.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        CodeIgniter,                     Git,                     PHP,                     Redmine,                     SQL,                     Website Development            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 01:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Simple Inkscape Extension - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Simple-Inkscape-Extension_%7E011111320647cbb8b4?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi,
I need a very simple Inkscape extension written.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I process large batches of images with PHP scripts through the Inkscape command line tool.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Unfortunately, the command line tool does not have all of the functionality I require.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I have read in forums that I can write an Inkscape extension and will have access to all Inkscape functionality.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is great because I can run these extensions via the command line tool from my existing PHP scripts.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This provides an easy workaround for me.
Unfortunately, I&amp;#039;m not a Python programmer.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I think if you know Python, you could probably research for an hour on how to complete this task, and have it completed within 2 hours.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Heck, who knows... Maybe you even have experience writing Inkscape extensions...
The required extension functionality:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-select &amp;amp;quot;Relative to: Selection&amp;amp;quot; from the Align and Distribute panel
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-name the extension &amp;amp;quot;Relative to Selection&amp;amp;quot;, place extension in a folder named &amp;amp;quot;HTA&amp;amp;quot; on Inkscape Extension menu.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-make a copy of this 1st extension, and make the selection &amp;amp;quot;Relative to: Page&amp;amp;quot; from the Align and Distribute panel
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-name the extension &amp;amp;quot;Relative to Page&amp;amp;quot;, place extension in a folder named &amp;amp;quot;HTA&amp;amp;quot; on Inkscape Extension menu.
Inkscape extension docs:
https://inkscape.org/en/develop/extensions/
See the attached screenshots.
Message with questions.
Thank You,
WyattBudget: $100
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        Inkscape,                     Python            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 18:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Techincal Writer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Techincal-Writer_%7E01d7bf26e879f01578?source=rss</link>
    <description>Job Description
*There is an executed 2018 MOU between the District of Columbia Workforce Investment Council (WIC) and the Department of Employment Services (DOES). For 2018, WIC has agreed to the transfer of funds to DOES to fund the integration of a successful workforce intermediary program. These funds in this MOU are earmarked to assist DOES in the development of innovative programs that provide pre-apprenticeship, job training, and supportive services. The programs under this partnership include occupational job training and related services intended to assist District residents to prepare for direct employment in the hospitality and/or construction industry.
In order for DOES to complete its assigned tasks under the executed MOU with WIC, temporary services will be needed to help complete the work prior to September 30, 2018. Thus, a Contractor(s) is needed to provide staff to work closely with the DOES Office of Apprenticeship, Information and Training (OAIT) team to perform critical administrative and operational duties that help OAIT daily workflow to ensure participants that are 18 and over are connected to meaningful work experiences, training, pre-apprenticeship and apprenticeships as approved by WIC*
Technical Writing services that encompass evaluating program performance using metrics defined by WIC which are contained in the MOU; writing and an annual report at the end of the Fiscal Year highlighting key outcomes and takeaways and writing new and revising existing operational policies to help improve Workforce Development operations.
Technical Writer should have some formal education in business, education, English or related field; This position requires a minimum of 2-3 years professional experience in marketing, technical writing, consulting, or related fields; Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Office with an emphasis on Word, PowerPoint, and Excel Experience in MS Access and SharePoint is highly desirable; Ability to review and correct grammar, punctuation, inconsistencies in style, and spelling errors; Advanced knowledge and experience in data collection and data analysis around program evaluation; and 1 to 2 years&amp;rsquo; experience writing operational policies and procedures,
Must be able to work from Monday 9/24/18 to Friday 9/28/18; no exceptions
This is a temporary position with the possibility of being extended.
Job Type: Temporary
Salary: $35.72 /hourPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft SharePoint Administration,                     Microsoft Word,                     Microsoft Office SharePoint Server,                     Microsoft SharePoint Designer,                     Technical Editing,                     Technical Writing            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 17:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Technical Writer needed to create tech manuals - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Technical-Writer-needed-create-tech-manuals_%7E017b2ea086bd27d086?source=rss</link>
    <description>There are two deliverables for this project:
1. Xevo VOD User Guide:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is a user guide that provides basic usability instructions.
2. Installation and Support Manual:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This manual provides technical details related to the installation, configuration, and other technical aspects of the Xevo VOD product.
*&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;#039;m looking for a freelancer with a solid understanding of:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;+ Linux/Unix
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;+ Strong understanding of relational database, networking, server set-up, and admin.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;+ Configuration and experience with virtual environments (VMware, Hyper-V, VirtualBox).
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;+ Experience modifying and creating SQL queries.
The freelancer will have to create a user guide and tech manual from a collection of misc docs and interviews with ProdOps team members.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        CentOS,                     Linux System Administration,                     Network Administration,                     System Administration            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 17:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQL table copy - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-table-copy_%7E01b280b3c2125bb263?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have minor SQL tasks, I need to have an sql table copied over duplicate SQL table, while not over writing parts of it,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
I also need some queries written to help us del with our product labels to accommodate prop 65.
I don&amp;#039;t&amp;#039; expect this to be a large project but I will require assistance.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        SAP Crystal Reports,                     Database Administration,                     Database Design,                     MySQL Administration,                     MySQL Programming,                     SQL            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 17:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant - with knowledge/experience in accounting - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant-with-knowledge-experience-accounting_%7E01c76f27e068e3f1f7?source=rss</link>
    <description>Are you a super-organized, detail-focused person looking for a job that is challenging and promises never to be the &amp;amp;quot;same old, same old?&amp;amp;quot;
Great!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are looking for you!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We have a geographically dispersed (multiple time zone) company) that continues to grow.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Need a smart, reliable colleague to join our team.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is a full-time, long-term position. The job requires 5 days a week, 6-8 hours a day.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Added responsibilities and hours will be given to the right person.
JOB REQUIREMENTS:
&amp;bull; Have a strong knowledge of and experience with MS Excel
&amp;bull; Have a solid knowledge of accounting, specifically Profit and Loss statements
&amp;bull; Be detail obsessed; we are freaks for accuracy 
&amp;bull; Be able to multi-task and work under pressure
&amp;bull; Be able to manage shifting priorities
&amp;bull; Must be self-motivated, organized, open-minded, positive, and flexible.
&amp;bull; Speak English as a native language with an excellent command of both spoken and written English
&amp;bull; Be effective at collaborating with team members (e.g., able to provide accurate status updates, show respected for their inputs and time)
&amp;bull; Follow-up on &amp;ldquo;loose ends&amp;rdquo; and complete tasks without needing step-by-step instructions or reminders
When you submit your cover letter, you must address it to HGT-007 for consideration!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(This helps us screen applicants who are not detail focused --- thanks!)
------------------------------------------------
More about us:
Please note, we are picky.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Why?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The right people make the difference for our colleagues, customers, clients, and management team.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our company has and continues to grow steadily because of our personnel.
If you have questions please ask!Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Accounts Payable Management,                     Accounts Receivable Management,                     Administrative Support,                     Bookkeeping,                     Data Entry,                     Financial Accounting,                     Financial Analysis,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 14:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Transfer and convert file from SharePoint to Azure Blob - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Transfer-and-convert-file-from-SharePoint-Azure-Blob_%7E01b2b1520a858d4258?source=rss</link>
    <description>Convert excel file from SharePoint library to CSV file and uploaded to Azure blob using Azure logic app or MS FlowPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Microsoft Azure App Services,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Flow,                     Microsoft SharePoint Development            Country: Irelandclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 14:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>(JS/React) SVG exporter for Illustrator that lives in the browser - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/React-SVG-exporter-for-Illustrator-that-lives-the-browser_%7E01a969c72539a88a5e?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need help to build an awesome export script for Illustrator. Mission is to generate optimized and clean SVG with one click, and show it as a gallery in HTML. For Mac.
1.) Saves out all artboards as SVGs with names. The extension needs one button &amp;amp;quot;Export&amp;amp;quot;.
2.) Batch renames the filenames (Illustrator adds an annoying prefix)
3.) From there the browser opens with a preloader. We optimize SVG code using SVGOMG service.
https://jakearchibald.github.io/svgomg/
https://github.com/svg/svgo/blob/master/docs/how-it-works/en.md
4.) In the same browser window and when done processing, we show a gallery layout in HTML of all the exported SVGs, with buttons to download/show code.
5.) The gallery will have a button to download the whole set.Budget: $300
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        CSS,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript            Country: Swedenclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 12:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior Data Analyst (Economist) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-Data-Analyst-Economist_%7E018238fe1497e1f4f4?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for Senior Data Analyst (Economist) to lead research and evaluation activities on various projects, including developing M&amp;amp;amp;E strategy and conducting rigorous evaluations and research studies for various projects. We are looking for someone with strong quantitative and qualitative background and with some experience conducting RCT studies. 
We need someone experienced in quantitative methodologies, and relating software packages and extensive experience cleaning, analyzing, and reporting quantitative data using statistical software such as MS Excel, SPSS, STATA, R, or SAS.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Quantitative Analysis
Skills:        IBM SPSS,                     Market Analysis,                     Market Research,                     NVivo,                     Qualitative Research,                     Quantitative Analysis,                     R,                     Research Papers,                     Stata,                     Statistics,                     Survey Design            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 09:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Scraper for creation of Tradeshow Lists - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Scraper-for-creation-Tradeshow-Lists_%7E01580c87b52ca70483?source=rss</link>
    <description>The responsibilities include but not limited to:
- Execute research on standardized and customized data sets for various tradeshows.
- Utilize search engines (like Google, Yahoo etc.) to research data
- Building Company / Exhibitor Lists, extract contacts for given list as per requirement
- Make use of MS Excel to systematically capture researched data. Ensure quality of data 
- Communicate with internal stakeholders to provide updates on progress of research and identify any issues
- Ability and desire to meet the deadlines and deliver results with minimal supervision.
- Customer database updates at regular intervals for different regions
-Validate and Search for relevant contacts and email using email searching toolsBudget: $20
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        B2B Marketing,                     Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Excel VBA,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 08:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Murex Application Developer (Banking Industry) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Murex-Application-Developer-Banking-Industry_%7E015d474f6db066732d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Responsible for Design, installation, implementation, application management and support of new Treasury solution for Murex.
&amp;bull;	Knowledge in Murex V3.1 module, experience in Murex V3.1 support &amp;amp;amp; development. 
&amp;bull;	Provide technical support, implementation &amp;amp;amp; Infrastructure support
&amp;bull;	Design, develop and maintain configuration of application systems and services involving reports and interfaces
&amp;bull;	Analyses and design reports, interfaces and templates based on user&amp;rsquo;s requirement and conversion of existing reports/interface.
&amp;bull;	Investigate &amp;amp;amp; resolve application supports queries or problem in a timely and effective matter.
&amp;bull;	Familiar in dynamic table, data mart, horizontal field, feeder, MXML workflow.
&amp;bull;	Support EOD batch run
&amp;bull;	Minimum 4 years working experience as a programmer/analyst that covers system analysis, design, programming and software testing. 
&amp;bull;	Ability to do programming in Visual Basic, Java, Crystal Report &amp;amp;amp; SQL (ie ability to design/write and troubleshoot), UNIX Scripting.
&amp;bull;	Support users in any of testing (i.e. guidance info during SIT,UAT, etc.)
Immediate joiners and locally available in Kuala Lumpur, MalaysiaBudget: $5
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Devices:Phone            
Country: Malaysiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Murex Application Developer (Banking Industry) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Murex-Application-Developer-Banking-Industry_%7E015d474f6db066732d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Responsible for Design, installation, implementation, application management and support of new Treasury solution for Murex.
&amp;bull;	Knowledge in Murex V3.1 module, experience in Murex V3.1 support &amp;amp;amp; development. 
&amp;bull;	Provide technical support, implementation &amp;amp;amp; Infrastructure support
&amp;bull;	Design, develop and maintain configuration of application systems and services involving reports and interfaces
&amp;bull;	Analyses and design reports, interfaces and templates based on user&amp;rsquo;s requirement and conversion of existing reports/interface.
&amp;bull;	Investigate &amp;amp;amp; resolve application supports queries or problem in a timely and effective matter.
&amp;bull;	Familiar in dynamic table, data mart, horizontal field, feeder, MXML workflow.
&amp;bull;	Support EOD batch run
&amp;bull;	Minimum 4 years working experience as a programmer/analyst that covers system analysis, design, programming and software testing. 
&amp;bull;	Ability to do programming in Visual Basic, Java, Crystal Report &amp;amp;amp; SQL (ie ability to design/write and troubleshoot), UNIX Scripting.
&amp;bull;	Support users in any of testing (i.e. guidance info during SIT,UAT, etc.)
Immediate joiners and locally available in Kuala Lumpur, MalaysiaBudget: $5
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Devices:Phone            
Country: Malaysiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQL Expert needed to create a PAR Loan calculation and Update queries - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-Expert-needed-create-PAR-Loan-calculation-and-Update-queries_%7E016e614c5911d2da4a?source=rss</link>
    <description>What you would do:
1. Write a query to calculate PAR Loans.
2. Review and Update a number of SQL Queries
I&amp;#039;m looking for a freelancer with a good understanding of loan system with previous experience working on a fin-tech project or finance or loans calculations. You can use SQL queries to write simple and complex calculations.Budget: $15
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Database Administration,                     Database Management,                     MySQL Programming,                     SQL            Country: Nigeriaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 13:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for an experience PL/SQL developer to write queries and reports - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-experience-SQL-developer-write-queries-and-reports_%7E01142e9c50649bd756?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for an experience PL/SQL, Oracle developer to help with the writing of queries and reports.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        SQL Programming            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 08:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Fix boostrap mobile issues using e107, design changes, and generate sql query - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Fix-boostrap-mobile-issues-using-e107-design-changes-and-generate-sql-query_%7E01c9c899db7671705a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Fix boostrap mobile issues using e107 and generate sql query that counts how many new users per month since the beginning of time.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I would also like the download page to be redesigned while.keeping it mobile friendly.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Also, I need someone to convert the upgrade page to css and not the flat image that it is now.Budget: $150
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Bootstrap            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 16:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Lead Data Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Lead-Data-Engineer_%7E01e21dbcdba638a017?source=rss</link>
    <description>Position Description
Works independently under limited supervision and applies knowledge of subject matter. Possess enough knowledge and skills to effectively deal with issues, challenges within field of specialization to develop simple Data solutions. Second level professional with direct impact on results and outcome.
Required Qualifications to be successful in this Role
&amp;bull;	Minimum 7+ years hands on experience with Hadoop and other Big data Technologies (such as Hive/Spark/Hadoop/Kafka/HBase etc )&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;with 2 Big Data implementations.
&amp;bull;	Proficient in shell script and programming languages - Python and Scala
&amp;bull;	Experience in ETL process from legacy database to GRAPH and/or SQL database
&amp;bull;	Should have working experience with - cloud DB (Redshift/Google BQ) and Unstructured DB (Elasticsearch).
&amp;bull;	Experience with ML tools like tensorflow, scikit etc.
&amp;bull;	Proficient in data structures &amp;amp;amp; algorithms and logical Database Modelling as per the business requirement. 
&amp;bull;	Good to have domain knowledge (Marketing Database).
Skills
&amp;bull;	ETL
&amp;bull;	Machine Learning
&amp;bull;	Analytical Thinking
&amp;bull;	Excellent Communication (Oral/Written) 
&amp;bull;	Multi-taskerPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Amazon Redshift,                     Bash Shell Scripting,                     Big Data,                     BigQuery,                     Data Analytics,                     Data Mining,                     Data Science,                     Data Scraping,                     Hadoop,                     Machine Learning,                     Python            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 11:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Lead Data Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Lead-Data-Engineer_%7E017c73f9e29175486c?source=rss</link>
    <description>Position Description
Works independently under limited supervision and applies knowledge of subject matter. Possess enough knowledge and skills to effectively deal with issues, challenges within field of specialization to develop simple Data solutions. Second level professional with direct impact on results and outcome.
Required Qualifications to be successful in this Role
&amp;bull;	Minimum 7+ years hands on experience with Hadoop and other Big data Technologies (such 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;as Hive/Spark/Hadoop/Kafka/HBase etc) with 2 Big Data implementations.
&amp;bull;	Proficient in shell script and programming languages - Python and Scala
&amp;bull;	Experience in ETL process from legacy database to GRAPH and/or SQL database
&amp;bull;	Should have working experience with - cloud DB(Redshift/Google BQ) and Unstructured DB 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(Elasticsearch).
&amp;bull;	Experience with ML tools like tensorflow, scikit etc.
&amp;bull;	Proficient in data structures &amp;amp;amp; algorithms and logical Database Modelling as per the business 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;requirement. 
&amp;bull;	Good to have domain knowledge (Marketing Database).
Skills
&amp;bull;	ETL
&amp;bull;	Machine Learning
&amp;bull;	Analytical Thinking
&amp;bull;	Excellent Communication (Oral/Written) 
&amp;bull;	Multi-taskerPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Amazon Redshift,                     Big Data,                     BigQuery,                     Data Analytics,                     Data Mining,                     Data Science,                     Python            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 09:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Full Stack Laravel Developer wanted for a &amp;#039;Booking&amp;#039; Application - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Full-Stack-Laravel-Developer-wanted-for-Booking-Application_%7E0165a1d2bbd182a0d0?source=rss</link>
    <description>Are you an highly experienced, ambitious Fullstack developer looking for an exciting project that pays?
We are looking for a motivated PHP / Laravel developer to come join our agile team of professionals.
If you are passionate about technology, have the mindset to digest a project that is in progress, pick up the existing pieces and extend then we are looking for you!
PHP / Laravel developer duties and responsibilities
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Help finish developing cutting edge web-based PHP applications.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Collaborate with the User Experience (UX) team
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ensure HTML, CSS, and shared JavaScript is valid and consistent across applications
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prepare and maintain all applications utilizing standard development tools
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Utilize backend data services and contribute to increase existing data services API
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Lead the entire web application development life cycle right from concept stage to delivery and post launch support
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Convey effectively with all task progress, evaluations, suggestions, schedules along with technical and process issues
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Document the development process, architecture, and standard components
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Coordinate with co-developers and keeps project manager well informed of the status of development effort and serves as liaison between development staff and project manager
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Keep abreast of new trends and best practices in web development
PHP / Laravel developer requirements and qualifications
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Previous working experience as a PHP / Laravel developer 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;BS/MS degree in Computer Science, Engineering, MIS or similar relevant field (not required)
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;In depth knowledge of object-oriented PHP and Laravel 5 PHP Framework
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hands on experience with SQL schema design, SOLID principles, REST API design 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Software testing 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;MySQL profiling and query optimization
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Creative and efficient problem solver
This application plans to incorporate functionality that satisfies the following topics &amp;#039;directory&amp;#039;,&amp;#039;chat&amp;#039;,&amp;#039;Booking&amp;#039;, &amp;#039;time management&amp;#039;,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;and &amp;#039;payment flow&amp;#039;Budget: $4,000
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Laravel Framework,                     PHP            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 01:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch script for MULTIPAR parity files creation - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-script-for-MULTIPAR-parity-files-creation_%7E0159e241f5edaa9b07?source=rss</link>
    <description>3 batch .bat files containing automation script must be done. The goal is to recursively create parity files on all children folders using a program called multipar. Script must be done in batch .bat files runnable unantended on a windows machine. See complete requirement in attached file.Budget: $60
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        Bash Shell Scripting,                     Scripting            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developers needed for a Project - iOS Developer, Android Developer, PHP Laravel Developer, React JS - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developers-needed-for-Project-iOS-Developer-Android-Developer-PHP-Laravel-Developer-React_%7E012af91f2e8d18a3c4?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for Freelancers who have been working with Startups/New Product development
The team is full of young and dynamic processionals who are passionate about their work and project.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Android Developers:
Strong knowledge of Android SDK, different versions of Android, and how to deal with different 
screensizes. Understanding of Googles Android design principles and interface guidelines.
Familiarity with RESTful APIs to connect Android applications to back-end services.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Strong knowledge of Android UI design principles, patterns, and best practices. 
Experience with offline storage, th reading, and performance tuning.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Ability to design applications around natural user interfaces, such as touch. 
Familiarity with the use of additional sensors, such as GPS. 
Knowledge of the open-source Android ecosystem and the libraries available for common tasks.
Ability to understand business requirements and translate them into technical requirements.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
iOS Developers:
Proficient with Objective-C or Swift.
Experience with iOS frameworks such as Core Data, Core Animation, etc.
Experience with offline storage, threading, and performance tuning.
Familiarity with RESTful APIs to connect iOS applications to back-end services.
Knowledge of other web technologies and UI/UX standards.
Understanding of Apple&amp;rsquo;s design principles and interface guidelines.
Knowledge of low-level C-based libraries is preferred.
Experience with performance and memory tuning with tools.
Familiarity with cloud message APIs and push notifications.
PHP Laravel:
Strong knowledge of PHP Laravel.
Understanding of MVC design patterns.
Knowledge of object-oriented PHP programming. 
Working knowledge of MySQL and other SQL/NoSQL databases and their declarative query languages. 
Database optimization and Designing.
Proficient understanding of code versioning tools, such as Git. 
Basic understanding of front-end technologies, such as JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS3. React
Extensive knowledge and experience with RESTFul API&amp;#039;s. Optimized for App as well as web.
App related service managing
Automated functional testing with PHPUnit or similar
Knowledge of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;enterprise search platforms (e.g. Solr, Lucene, Google Search Appliance, Microsoft Fast, Microsoft SharePoint, Endeca, or Elasticsearch).
Build reusable code and libraries for future use &amp;amp;amp; Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability. 
Build innovative, state-of-the-art applications and collaborate with the User Experience (UX) team
experience in common third-party APIs (Google, Facebook, chat etc).
React.Js
Requirement analysis, coding, design, implementation, testing, problem analysis and resolution, 
and technical documentation.
Identify inconsistencies in architecture and determine simpler and optimal programming solutions.
Able to create a design for small components and participates and contributes to research projects.
Creatively define load tests, troubleshoot performance and build scalable solutions, able to
suggest DB structure normalization changes.
Understand technical requirements and how they relate and familiarity in general performance
practices like caching, query optimization, memory utilization and clean-up, etc.
Familiarity with RESTful APIs development.
Expertise with code testing best practices, including unit and integration testing to ensure quality 
of code.
Familiarity with code versioning tools such as Git lib and TFS and Agile/SCRUM Development methodologies. 
Familiarity on agile methodology and proficiency of participating in the stand up and handling tasks workflow.
Good experience in JavaScript front-end of React.js, react-native.
Experience developing Adaptive or Responsive websites using UI technologies like HTML5, CSS3 
and jQuery.
Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs.
Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability.
Assure that all user input is validated before submitting to back-end.
Integration with backend API.
Follow the best practices of client side MVC.
Strong proficiency with JavaScript, TypeScript.
Knowledge of Node.js and frameworks available for it such as, ReactJS.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development
Skills:        Objective-C,                     React Native,                     Swift            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for a person who can write SQL Queries.  A plus for Google Apps Script/Google BigQuery. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-person-who-can-write-SQL-Queries-plus-for-Google-Apps-Script-Google-BigQuery_%7E0118f19a4ab624b569?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want sql queries to be written to work with Google BigQuery.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Google APIs,                     Google Apps Script,                     SQLite Programming            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>.NET Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/NET-Developer_%7E0126ba250973cc4057?source=rss</link>
    <description>Required Skills &amp;amp;amp; Experience
&amp;bull;	SQL
&amp;bull;	T-SQL
&amp;bull;	.NET (C#)
&amp;bull;	PowerShell
Responsibilities
&amp;bull;	Supporting a vendor application by creating, maintaining, and updating scheduled tasks, Windows Services, SQL scripts, PowerShell scripts, batch files, C# programs, and VB programs.
&amp;bull;	Utilize Windows Server 2008 R2 to check error logs and Event viewer, as well as install service packs and patches.
&amp;bull;	Make use of SQL Server Management Studio to view database tables, schedule SQL jobs, create SQL code files, and track database errors.
&amp;bull;	Create, maintain, and update custom reports via the use of SQL scripts, PowerShell scripts, and C# code. These reports are populated with new data every day and dispersed via EBO, email, or FTP.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        C#,                     Windows PowerShell,                     SQL,                     Transact-SQL            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch program for Whitepages API - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-program-for-Whitepages-API_%7E019066efe416ff8f36?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a simple windows based program which will loop through a list with names/city/state and for each entry make a REST API call to the whitepages API.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The program should take the JSON based responses and format them to return address for each input entry and then export the list of responses to a spreadsheet.
This can be done either with excel, VB, or any other technology which makes sense.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;#039;m looking for something very simple to perform only this one function.
Here&amp;#039;s a link to a thread on excel forum which contains an example spreadsheet that sort of does what is needed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;#039;m looking for something slightly more reliable and possibly faster.
http://www.excelforum.com/excel-programming-vba-macros/788072-loop-to-do-whitepages-api-calls.html
I also have a windows program that I can provide which provides an example of what is needed but no longer works perfectly after whitepages has changed the order of their response fields.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Simple modification of a batch file - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Simple-modification-batch-file_%7E01e7a0903929a2e0af?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want to modify an existing batch file which will open a random file from a folder. Any of the scripts on this page will work for this project:
https://superuser.com/questions/872048/opening-random-file-from-folder-and-subfolders-with-batch-script-windows-7
So what this script should be able to do is open two files. When it selects the first file, it should be able to save the name of the file and be able to open another corresponding folder with the same name in another folder. For example:
First file: C:\Users\(name)\Documents\My Games - choose file and save name
Second file: C:\Users\(name)\Documents\My Saves\(saved file name)\ - choose file
When the script saves the name of the file it should automatically remove the last 4 characters from the name of the file when recording it - so &amp;amp;quot;X.exe&amp;amp;quot; becomes just &amp;amp;quot;X&amp;amp;quot;.Budget: $50
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        .NET Framework,                     C#,                     C++,                     CSS,                     HTML5,                     Java,                     JavaScript,                     PHP,                     Python,                     VBA,                     Windows App Development,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into Romanian - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-Romanian_%7E018a18548ef129da92?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into Romanian. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Two basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: Romanian ( bilingual is preferred: Romanian and English)
2. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to Romanian.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Film Dubbing,                     Music,                     Poetry,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English Romanian            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into French - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-French_%7E01c27961099f1c7b8c?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into French. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Three basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: French ( bilingual is preferred: French and English)
2. The translators should be French natives who can speak standard French.
3. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to French.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Christian Theology,                     Editing,                     Music,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English French            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Deep Barry White type voice for series of short audio ads and video voice over - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Deep-Barry-White-type-voice-for-series-short-audio-ads-and-video-voice-over_%7E01c3ef92e029862e40?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a very deep, Barry white style talent for a series of short audio ads and video voice overs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This will be an ongoing project with possible additional milestones after the initial batch.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A script and basic outline will be provided for each piece created.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Each audio ad will be no longer than 30 seconds and the video overs no longer than 15 seconds. The initial contract is for 4 separate ads, each with it&amp;#039;s own milestone.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The entire initial project (including all 4 milestones) is $120, or $30 each.Budget: $120
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Voice Talent
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 23:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for strong Nodejs/API and Angular5x  Developers â€“ Agency Preferred - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-strong-Nodejs-API-and-Angular5x-Developers-Agency-Preferred_%7E010aaccc5bac173566?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking to establish a long term relationship with an Upwork Agency and hire 1-2 members as dedicated resources. We do not require a Project Manager for day to day activities and are happy to communicate directly with the developers, however we would like to know there is a manager available for escalations and oversight. We would ask that a standard start time be maintained so we can schedule some overlap (we prefer morning hours of CST timezone) to review work and discuss tasks.
**Your Responsibilities Will Include:
-	development, migration and updates to a large content management system that manages a lot of retail and mall content
-	work collaboratively in Slack together as a group. Your team will interface with myself, our project managers, and our development team on a regular basis and the ability to quickly respond in chat is very important
-	have regular starting hours with some overlap of CST timezone and consistently starting work at that time
-	tracking your time per task with notes for our records
Our goal is that you will be a part of our team and we will work together on this cool platform and others for months and years to come.
** About the CMS System:
You will be working purely on the data side of the CMS and not the front-end website. We inject data from a few sources, we expose APIs and webservices to other systems which consume our data either for processing or sending to the other system which manages the actual website and mobile application. We have about 2 months of work in our backlog and we would like to bring on skilled professionals to work with us on getting this stuff done. As part of the onboarding and development we will be working on documentation and diagramming the system. We feel that having new developers work on this will also help them learn the system and how it works so that when they develop on it, it will make sense to them.
** Technologies You Should be Familiar With:
We have put together a list of specific skills that would be involved in our application and for the new team members to be responsible for. It&amp;#039;s not critical that you are 100% experts at all the areas listed below but you need to be proficient in larger applications built in a MEAN stack which utilize a lot of AWS services. 
Servers
1.	Ubuntu 
2.	Windows Server 2016
App/ languages
1.	Back-end
a.	Nodejs 6
2.	Front-end
a.	Bootstrap 
b.	Angular 1
c.	Jquery
3.	NGINX configuration - performance and security
4.	Python - for processing data, lambdas, or general script stuff like image resizing in batches
5.	Javascript ES6
Database languages
1.	Mongodb - what version 3
2.	Redis - version 2+
AWS specific things like 
1.	S3 - read and write, setup, ACL generation, compression, proper headers
2.	Lambdas ** Key knowledge area
3.	SNS
4.	SQS 
5.	etc...
Integrations
1.	SSO - okta, Auth0
2.	CI tools like&amp;hellip;
3.	Airbrake or similar
4.	Keymetrics or similar - Server Metrics, alerts, etc..
5.	Slack integration 
6.	Webhooks - creating, processing, debuggingPosted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Amazon S3,                     Amazon Web Services,                     AngularJS,                     Auth0,                     AWS Lambda,                     JavaScript,                     Linux System Administration,                     MEAN Stack Administration,                     MongoDB,                     Redis            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Wanted:	Bada$$	Virtual Assistant	with	Real	Estate Experience - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Wanted-Bada-Virtual-Assistant-with-Real-Estate-Experience_%7E019a978fc00b5c4965?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m	a	looking	for	a	full-time	VA	to	help	with	my	real	estate	business.		
**	Responsibilities	Include	**	
Screening	buyer	&amp;amp;amp;	seller	leads	daily
Addressing,	stamping,	and	stuffing	batches	of	100	mailers	on	a	regular	basis
Running	comparable	sales	and	determining	value
Understanding	my	buying	criteria	&amp;amp;amp;	recommending	a	course	of	action
Receiving	inbound	calls	and	making	outbound	calls	(I&amp;rsquo;ll	provide	the	call	script)
Coordinating	paperwork	and	closings
**	Must	Have	**
Hawk-like	attention	to	detail
Dog-like	dependability
Ox-like	work	ethic
Cat-like	reflexes
Please	respond	with	your	availability,	samples	of	past	work,	and	favorite	&amp;lsquo;80s	movie.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Internet Research,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a Copywriter For Scripts (For Video Ads) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-Copywriter-For-Scripts-For-Video-Ads_%7E01f99051d491040bfd?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello Copywriters!
We&amp;#039;re looking for simple scripts to be created for video ads in a &amp;amp;quot;testimonial&amp;amp;quot; format that is pushing people to an advertorial. We need a good 30 to 60 second long scripts that will be persuasive and comes off as authentic.
We have a supplement product and we have a girl who is already a video actress who will be recording herself using a selfie-type video.
This is how we&amp;#039;re going to push people to read (her) article, which is an advertorial that gives a review of the product.
I have an example to show you what we&amp;#039;ve done in the past that have worked, and we&amp;#039;d like more quality, persuasive scripts.
This will be continuous, every week or so we&amp;#039;d come up with a good batch of 5 scripts or so.
If this is something that interests you, I&amp;#039;d love to hear back!Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Copywriting
Skills:        Copywriting,                     Sales Writing,                     Scriptwriting            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 20:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into French - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-French_%7E011b699118a7d6fed7?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into French. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Three basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: French ( bilingual is preferred: French and English)
2. The translators should be French natives who can speak standard French.
3. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to French.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Christian Theology,                     Editing,                     Music,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English French            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 19:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need Apple Scripter - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-Apple-Scripter_%7E01adcc64989ab5c52b?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a set of Apple scripts that were batched into an app. 
This script was for converting a word document, PowerPoint, or excel document into a pdf, but since a recent Microsoft office update it stopped working. 
We need to have this app fixed or a similar script to be developed to convert word documents into PDFs. 
The word document should convert into a pdf in the same exact size that it is currently in and be &amp;ldquo;marginless&amp;rdquo;. 
Also, we have 2 scripts that print using two different page sizes, but these are broken too.Budget: $100
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        AppleScript,                     JavaScript            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 18:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Technical Email Marketing Manager at Growing Startup - Must Know Python - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Technical-Email-Marketing-Manager-Growing-Startup-Must-Know-Python_%7E01db95a3a37d2ccdcd?source=rss</link>
    <description>THE WORK:
We need to run a large number of email marketing campaigns. 
We use Python and the Sendgrid API currently, though we will use marketing automation solutions in the future. 
We will provide email templates and the email addresses to send them to. You will do everything else. 
You will:
- Run the script to send batches of emails as necessary
- Make improvements to the Python script that sends the email 
- Monitor campaigns, track and analyze key email marketing statistics 
THE COMPANY: 
We&amp;#039;re a growing startup that&amp;#039;s making it easier for small businesses in the US to get their accounting and bookkeeping done.
REQUIREMENTS:
- Python
- Javascript
- HTML + CSS
- 100% fluent in English
- Available to work at least 1-2 hours each weekday
No upfront payment. Payment is made based on hours every 2 weeks or every month.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Email &amp;amp; Marketing Automation
Skills:        Email Deliverability,                     Email Handling,                     Email Marketing,                     Email Technical Support,                     HTML,                     JavaScript,                     Lead Generation,                     Marketing Automation,                     SendGrid            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 22:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a Powershell expert who can create PS scripts in batch file to automate Dynamics CRM 2011 to Dynamics CRM 2016 Upgrade tasks - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-Powershell-expert-who-can-create-scripts-batch-file-automate-Dynamics-CRM-2011-Dynamics-CRM-2016-Upgrade-tasks_%7E01efb24a71c92896d3?source=rss</link>
    <description>This runs like a well oiled machine for us. We get these customer databases and we do the same thing every time. No errors, nothing. But it takes 10 hours. 
We have the list of steps. This is for our own environment,
At a very high level these are the tasks:
1. Restore the Client database to a server with Pre-installed CRM 2011
2. Run a sql script to clean the db
3. Import the Organization
4. Back up the DB
5. Run another SQL script
6. Back up the CRM 2013 upgraded DB
7. Restore to another server with CRM 2015 installed already
8. Import Org
9. Run a script
10. Back up the db
11. Restore to another CRM 2016 already installed
12. Import Org
Run another SQL script.
Done.
When we do this on client servers, there are some variations.
For every new installation or deployment of software, we have to do many system checks and verifications on their Windows Servers
Lets define the scope of work. 
Do the low hanging fruits first. 
Lets make it a phased approach. 
Automation of these frequently repetitive tasks with every client will save us a lot of time in deployments and will make us more productive. I have been working on some of these on my own but a powershell expert would be good to work with. 
$100 is a placeholderBudget: $100
Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 01:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Burmese Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Burmese-Reading-Audio-Review_%7E01785ced4855cdb7dc?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are launching Burmese narration project and hope to hire some Burmese native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Burmese audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Burmese Yangon Standard Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Background Music: overall tone and the volume of the soundtrack need to be compatible with the related Type, and quieten people&amp;rsquo;s heart to ponder over the words.
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Audio Production,                     Burmese,                     English,                     Translation English Burmese            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Civil Maps is Hiring for freelance consultant - DevOps Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Civil-Maps-Hiring-for-freelance-consultant-DevOps-Engineer_%7E019e79d6f1ec4273af?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi ,
We are Civil Maps .
Civil Maps, provider of 3D mapping technology for fully autonomous vehicles, has raised a $6.6 million seed funding round from Ford Motor Company, Motus Ventures, Wicklow Capital, StartX Stanford and Yahoo cofounder Jerry Yang&amp;rsquo;s AME Cloud Ventures.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; mission is to make it possible for fully autonomous vehicles (SAE Levels 4-5) to drive anywhere smoothly and safely. Through artificial intelligence and vehicle-based local processing, Civil Maps converts sensor data into meaningful map information built specifically to direct fully autonomous vehicles. The company will use the seed investment to accelerate product development and deployment with a number of leading automotive companies and technology partners.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; artificial intelligence software aggregates raw 3D data from LiDAR (high-resolution laser imaging), camera and other sensors onboard autonomous vehicles and organizes the information into machine-readable maps. The information is vastly more actionable information than today&amp;rsquo;s mapping systems and requires a fraction of the data storage and transmission for existing technologies. Thanks to this light data footprint, Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; spatial information is far less costly to transmit over cellular networks, enabling the company to more easily crowdsource, update and share road data in real time&amp;mdash;a major improvement over the lengthy processes that require human annotation in current use. As a result, the company can quickly generate and maintain maps that give fully autonomous vehicles the comprehensive and precise knowledge to autonomous operate safely and smoothly on all roads.
About the Opportunity : 
This is an opportunity to work on some of the most exciting problems in the autonomous vehicle industry. Civil Maps is looking for a Devops engineer to grow its overall infrastructure. You will be interacting with a completely custom-made distributed computing framework, handling terabytes and petabytes of machine vision data, and millions of requests from robotic platforms.
In our interdisciplinary teams, you will get acquainted with the many facets of 3D map creation: data collection, geospatial registration, feature extraction, auditing.
Come work on novel challenges, learn and grow while helping Civil Maps achieve on-demand perception of the world around us.
We are hiring the professionals for the below skills:
Work Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;: Hyderabad
Job Description for DevOps Enginner:
Experience : 3-15 yrs 
Responsibilities : 
Deliver next generation distributed applications using a variety of tools to include Kubernetes, Ansible, RHEL, Openshift, Atomic, Mesos, Openstack and Docker.
Build solutions and provide a framework for Microservices and DevOps.
Bring knowledge and help with continuous integration, deployment and security.
Automating the Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment environment with relative tools.
Troubleshooting Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment issues.
Experience with the following : 
Deploy, manage Continuous Integration tools (Jenkins, Travis etc..).
Cloud-based deployments (AWS, Azure, OpenStack).
Linux administration, usage, and bash scripting (Bash, Batch, Powershell)
Deploying MEAN stack applications.
Security tools like Fortify, Nessus.
Network architecture (routing, load balancing, firewalls, VLANs).
Virtualization (VMWare, XEN, KVM, Openstack).
Container technologies (Mesos, Docker, Rocket, etc.).
Experience in setting up backup and restore mechanism for the DB and other relevant systems.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Photoshop editor for repeated work adding text using actions - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Photoshop-editor-for-repeated-work-adding-text-using-actions_%7E01956d4abb6db9599d?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for entry level Photoshop editor with basic Photoshop skills. We are developing a portfolio of imagines where we require to do following:
Change text in the photo using action script (around 30-40 different photos)
Adjust the text in the imagine to suit the text box.
Save the file using batch function as .jpg.
Scripts and necessary instructions will be provided.
The job may require basic editing skill like removing trade names adding light to the imagine...
You should be familiar with design and good feel for colour composition.
I am looking for fast worker, and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;quick learner since the time to perform the job will be limited.
We will post the Photoshop projects on the shared drive like onedrive. After the job is done the ready photo will be uploaded to the same share drive by you.
Required number of hours weekly is min 30.
I am looking for freelancers with the lowest rates
Pay is $3 an hour.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Photoshop,                     Photo Editing            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 22:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Agisoft/Reality capture/Maya job - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Agisoft-Reality-capture-Maya-job_%7E01082d8b4c6330c37f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for someone with experience using the following:
1) Photogrammetry applications: either Agisoft Photoscan or Reality Capture
2) Animation: Maya
Below are the tasks I would like you to do:
1. Take the captured facial performance and reconstruct using Photogrammetry application into a per frame mesh and texture (if using RealityCapture you can write script to handle Batch processing with command line utility)
2. Import the models into Maya, and create a visibility script, setting the scans visibility on a per frame basis (should take about 10 minutes of coding) 
3. In Maya create a rough lightrig for preview purposes
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Animation
Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 12:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Dutch Christian Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Dutch-Christian-Reading-Audio-Review_%7E01602c2b88ee568672?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are launching Dutch Christian Reading project and hope to hire some Dutch native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Dutch audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Standard Dutch Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Post-production: if vocals and reverberation are pleasant to hear; if the overall tone and the volume of the background music is soft, and will not impair people&amp;rsquo;s ability to hear God&amp;rsquo;s words.
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: September 27, 2018 13:11 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Audio Engineering,                     Audio Production,                     Dutch,                     English,                     Voice Over Dutch            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
</ArrayOfFeedItem>