<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfFeedItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Research - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Research_%7E01255153b048a716f7?source=rss</link>
    <description>We&amp;#039;re an online education company. We need help compiling all the education platforms into a spreadsheet and eventually into a database. Once we get the majority of them in the system we&amp;#039;ll need ongoing work to find new schools, as well as rank/rate the schools. This job requires understanding of education, online education, and how to conduct thorough research.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Web Research
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Education Technology,                     Google Search,                     Internet Research,                     Market Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            click to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Statistic/math problem related to trailing stop loss/buy values - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Statistic-math-problem-related-trailing-stop-loss-buy-values_%7E0100fc2f5778d50eb3?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a mathematical/statistic problem. I need to calculate the optimal trailing stop loss and buy percentages for a trading bot I use. I searched Google for that and come up with really complicated math papers (at least for me!) such as this one https://goo.gl/36CLyN. 
Can you help me calculate the optimal values for those variables?
The trailing stop loss works like this: as soon as the asset price decreases X% from the previous highest high, the position is liquidated. 
The trailing buy works like this: as soon as the asset price increases Y% from the previous lowest low (after the asset sell) the position is reopened. 
Thanks a lot!Budget: $100
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Mathematics,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Python,                     Statistics            Country: Brazilclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual assistant to do research for a golf website - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-assistant-research-for-golf-website_%7E012ab6fad22ac4360f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a golf travel website and need research done to find other golf and travel websites that are looking for guests posts. Which would mean contact information and guidelines?Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Pull Logos and One Data Point from List of Company&amp;#039;s Websites - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Pull-Logos-and-One-Data-Point-from-List-Company-Websites_%7E0157c61fa8b66fd71b?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need someone to take an Excel sheet that I have of different companies and find their logo online and one data point then put them in the Powerpoint Slides that I also attached. 
For the list, there are almost 70 companies and most of them have website links that you can click to find their website. 
I&amp;#039;d like you to use their websites and the internet to find each company&amp;#039;s logo and the number of their AUM (Assets Under Management) then put them together in the Powerpoint slides. 
In the spreadsheet, there is a column that also lists &amp;amp;quot;Stage&amp;amp;quot;. Please use this column to determine what slide to put that company&amp;#039;s logo and AUM number on (Ex. Stage 0, Stage 1, Stage 2, etc.)
For the AUM number, you can write it with letters. For example, for $1,000,000 (one million) you can write $1M. Please strive to find AUM numbers for all companies. If there is a few you can&amp;#039;t find, you can type &amp;amp;quot;??&amp;amp;quot; instead.
I&amp;#039;m happy to answer any questions that you might have. Quality and speed are important for this project. 
Thanks!Budget: $35
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Presentations
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft PowerPoint            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a data miner to pull lists of dermatology offices based on physician locator websites. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-data-miner-pull-lists-dermatology-offices-based-physician-locator-websites_%7E01d898efbeee309074?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for someone to create a single spreadsheet list of dermatologists/dermatology offices including the types of aesthetic devices that they own. The list should include the clinic name, location, address, email (if available), phone (if available) and if they own various devices (Miradry, Fraxel, Thermage, Ulthera, Coolsculpting). The data should be a simple extraction of lists from physician locator webpages and then combined into a single spreadsheet so that we can see who has which devices. The webpages to pull the information from are:
http://find.coolsculpting.com/find-a-center/
https://locator.ultherapy.com/united-states
https://miradry.com/locator/
https://www.thermage.com/find-a-doctor
https://www.fraxel.com/find-a-doctor
I believe that manually entering zip codes and entering the data is too cumbersome and not very cost effective. Thus I believe that I need someone experienced in website/data scraping to pull all this data together. We only need the list to include US-based physicians/clinics at this time.Budget: $2,000
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a data miner to pull lists of dermatology offices based on physician locator websites. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-data-miner-pull-lists-dermatology-offices-based-physician-locator-websites_%7E01d898efbeee309074?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for someone to create a single spreadsheet list of dermatologists/dermatology offices including the types of aesthetic devices that they own. The list should include the clinic name, location, address, email (if available), phone (if available) and if they own various devices (Miradry, Fraxel, Thermage, Ulthera, Coolsculpting). The data should be a simple extraction of lists from physician locator webpages and then combined into a single spreadsheet so that we can see who has which devices. The webpages to pull the information from are:
http://find.coolsculpting.com/find-a-center/
https://locator.ultherapy.com/united-states
https://miradry.com/locator/
https://www.thermage.com/find-a-doctor
https://www.fraxel.com/find-a-doctor
I believe that manually entering zip codes and entering the data is too cumbersome and not very cost effective. Thus I believe that I need someone experienced in website/data scraping to pull all this data together. We only need the list to include US-based physicians/clinics at this time.Budget: $2,000
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant_%7E0101d28786c4572865?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need a bit of help organizing my life.. 
Looking for a assistant that is highly skilled. 
Some upcoming projects will include...
Opening a online supplies store which we will need marketing specialists for. 
Also social media marketing for an collective of events in the Seattle area. 
Please have flexible availability and a positive attitude I look forward to meeting with you!
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Virtual Assistant            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Fitness Market Research - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Fitness-Market-Research_%7E018e4df10a3f51010f?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello! I am looking for someone to update a list of personal training associations/organizations with additional information:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
 &amp;bull;	How many certificate holders do they have?
&amp;bull;	How many members do they have (if an association)? 
&amp;bull;	Who is their insurance provider (if they have one)?
&amp;bull;	What is their website?
&amp;bull;	When did we last contact them?
&amp;bull;	Who is the credentialing organization behind them?
*If these categories are not 99.99% full, the job is NOT done. This is a strict deadline. 
I have attached an excel file. This is already partially filled out and this is the one that should be added to.
This person should be knowledgeable and have a background in research. I am also looking to have this done PROMPTLY.Budget: $75
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Market &amp;amp; Customer Research
Skills:        Business Analysis,                     Google Search,                     Internet Research,                     Market Research,                     Microsoft Excel            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry Analyst and Microsoft Excel User needed for Data Entry job. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-Analyst-and-Microsoft-Excel-User-needed-for-Data-Entry-job_%7E019bce8e17b0917cb9?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;#039;m just looking for someone who can count and use Microsoft Excel. English must be good, but doesn&amp;#039;t have to be great. That&amp;#039;s all.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Financial Analysts - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Financial-Analysts_%7E0121fd6b3dd596aa6b?source=rss</link>
    <description>This is a great opportunity to learn a new skill. Most people pay for this model and knowledge but I am starting to team to analyze a multitude of deals at a time and I need the man power. So I am offering to provide training for free but you have to be committed to long term growth with the company. 
Also if you end up analyzing a deal for us that we purchase you will receive $5000. there will also be opportunity to move up and even be a partner on deals.
What I need from you:
I need individuals to use my provided excel financial model to analyze real estate investments.
You will need to review broker packages with financial data and place it in the model to analyze the investment. 
I will supply the model and training videos on how to use the model before I hire you.
You will need to prove you can successfully use the model before being accepted into the group.
This is a limited opportunity to have access to an amazing educational tool to change your life forever. 
Growth opportunities for successful candidates.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Financial Planning
Skills:        Accounting,                     Financial Accounting,                     Financial Analysis,                     Financial Forecasting,                     Financial Modeling,                     Financial Reporting,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Telemarketing List Cleanup. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Telemarketing-List-Cleanup_%7E01fd22707e1fb00634?source=rss</link>
    <description>Roughly a little more than 200 companies need to be called&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;to verify name and email address of two specific contacts.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Lead Generation
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Researcher needed to compile local hotel information - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Researcher-needed-compile-local-hotel-information_%7E010e2cda66f19a583e?source=rss</link>
    <description>Our company needs a listing of all hotels within a 50 mile radius of Los Angeles (zip code 90001). Should be delivered as an excel document. 
Document should include: 
- Hotel Name
- Hotel Address
- Direct Hotel Phone NumberBudget: $50
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Web Research
Skills:        Business Development,                     Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Research            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Amazon RDS pricing spreadsheet - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Amazon-RDS-pricing-spreadsheet_%7E01331806207b189504?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want an Excel spreadsheet that replicated e below functionality (Amazon RDS pricing estimate)
https://calculator.s3.amazonaws.com/index.html
The pricing data for Amazon Aurora RDS is available below:
https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/pricing/
Sample spreadsheet is attached for your convenience, which can be used as a starting point. This work is expected to be delivered as early as possible.Budget: $50
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        Excel VBA,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need an expert or individual familiar with SQL, API solutions and Restful API integration - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-expert-individual-familiar-with-SQL-API-solutions-and-Restful-API-integration_%7E01fc9df1afbc0107a2?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a project I would like to send you which will take roughly less than 3 hours to complete. From this project, I would like to see your thought process and from there I have an idea in mind for possible future job opportunities. 
The project has to do with restful API integration and using basic SQL.Budget: $30
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        API Development,                     Google Query Language,                     SQL            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>QA Automation - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Automation_%7E01b8a7784fcdf87356?source=rss</link>
    <description>SweatWorks, the leading technology company in the fitness industry, is hiring a Quality Assurance Automation engineer/architect, fluent in written and spoken English and with full time availability.
The main focus of this role is to continue building and maintaining our automation regression suite at the UI &amp;amp;amp; integration layers. You will also mentor other team members in developing UI, integration and unit test automation while working in an Agile environment with independent cross-functional teams.
RESPONSIBILITIES
- Building and maintaining automated testing framework to support functional, integration and unit level testing throughout AWS microservices architecture.
- Working closely with developers to create automated scripts that support Continuous Integration/Continuous Delivery pipeline.
- Productively working in a distributed Agile team, mentoring junior team members, and actively participating in knowledge sharing.
- Responsible for creating performance and load tests, and creating reports on performance impact.
- Gathering requirements, testing and deployment within set time lines.
- Preparing, designing and leading Test strategies and Test plans for all projects.
- Should be able to counsel client on Test practices and Test strategies.
- Should be able to develop POC/working solution for client, based on best industry practice.
- Developing quality standards through the participation in initial software development stages.
- Validating and enhancing the existing QA plans and strategies.
- Creating Test logs and Test reports.
- Responsible for Defect logging, tracking through Element tool (Defect Management tool).
- Interacting with team members to ensure a smooth progress of the project; ensuring customer delivery and adherence to quality norms throughout the implementation process.
- Participating in candidate interviews and talent management.
REQUIREMENTS
- Must have 4-6 years experience in authoring and designing test automation frameworks at both UI layer and service layer.
- Must have experience in Automation testing (using Protractor, Node.js and TypeScript).
- Must have good experience in testing applications hosted on cloud (specifically AWS tech stack).
- Must have working experience in:
--- SQL Databases MSSQL/MySQL (Query writing, Joins, Views, Triggers, Views) and NoSQL Databases (DynamoDB).
--- Distributed SCM (GitHub/GitLab).
--- Setting up CI tools and services (Jenkins Pipeline, AWS CodeBuild).
--- Performance Testing tools (JMeter, BlazeMeter).
--- Testing cloud architectures that include microservices and RESTful APIs.
- Should have working knowledge of Agile (Scrum/Kanban) and DevOps practices &amp;amp;amp; methodologies.
- Should have knowledge of Software Testing Methodology and QA processes.
- Good to have experience in mobile automation testing and distributed test execution tools (Selenium Grid, Sauce Labs, BrowserStack).
- Defect tracking activities including defect identification, recording and tracking to closure using defect tracking tools.
- Responsible for communication with the clients and with all key stakeholders.
- Strong inter-personal and communication skills.
- Demonstrated problem solving, analytic and troubleshooting skills.
- Ability to deal with ambiguity and flexibility to work collaboratively with others in dynamic Agile environments.
- Desire to learn new automation technologies and development tools.
WE OFFER
- Home-office job
- 25 day paid vacation per year
- Benefits: health insurance, Internet expenses and gym expenses
- Salary in USD
Thanks for your application. Join us!Budget: $2,000
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; QA &amp;amp; Testing
Skills:        Amazon Web Services,                     Automated Testing,                     DevOps,                     Functional Testing,                     GitHub,                     Integration Testing,                     Jenkins,                     JMeter,                     Manual Test Execution,                     Node.js,                     NoSQL,                     Performance Testing,                     Protractor,                     Scrum,                     Software QA Testing,                     SQL,                     TypeScript,                     Web Testing            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data entry in custom web application - 3-4 times a week / 2-3 hours per day - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-entry-custom-web-application-times-week-hours-per-day_%7E01967732f26d6ea8d5?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have an online/web application that requires data from small merchants to be entered, updated and managed on a weekly basis. 
The responsibility is to learn how to understand the data and enter into relevant fields in a web based application.
Excellent command of English is required to understand the intent of unstructured data (sent over emails, google docs or google spreadsheets).Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Spreadsheets            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQL expert in WP database - woocommerce - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-expert-database-woocommerce_%7E0101aba925374306f5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi
I need someone good in SQL and data manipulation to make a small query to update a woocommerce db with 800 products. We need the contents of one field in postmeta table to be updated in posts table. 
Please provide a few samples of your work in sql and wp databases.Budget: $25
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        phpMyAdmin,                     SQL,                     Woocommerce,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Quickbooks expert for two companies needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Quickbooks-expert-for-two-companies-needed_%7E013da15260f6a8f727?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have two companies that need help with the accounting. 
Requirements are the following:
- Must have knowledge of subscription-based payment system
- Must be fluent in English
- Must have 5 years experience with QuickBooks and Quickbooks online
- Must be responsive to communications 
- Must be proactive in all workPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Accounts Receivable Management,                     Bank Reconciliation,                     Bookkeeping,                     Certified Public Accountant (CPA),                     Financial Accounting,                     Intuit QuickBooks,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Tax Preparation            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Statement of Purpose for Economics PhD - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Statement-Purpose-for-Economics-PhD_%7E01a334accd4b51cbfe?source=rss</link>
    <description>This is simply a statement of purpose that is required for every single U.S, Ph.D. program application. 
The project is for me. Please do not hesitate to message me about my background.
The type of freelancer I am looking for is people who had consulting experience in college career centers. If the freelancer is fluent in Mandarin, that would be better (not required though), so he/she would know exactly how to make the paper effective while convincing the admission committee that it is written by a student whose first language isn&amp;#039;t English.
I had one of my older drafts for my master program last year, the final polished paper was lost. You may want to take a look or even use it as the skeleton. It&amp;#039;s in the additional project files.Budget: $80
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Academic Writing &amp;amp; Research
Skills:        Econometrics,                     Economics,                     MATLAB,                     Microsoft Excel PowerPivot,                     Python Pandas,                     R,                     Stata            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Excel Spreadsheet Expert Needed to Automate Tasks - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Excel-Spreadsheet-Expert-Needed-Automate-Tasks_%7E0197ae506239d704b4?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a spreadsheet of data. I would like to be able to enter data in and have this data copied into a new spreadsheet within the workbook if a condition is met. A good description of what I would like is posted here: https://answers.microsoft.com/en-us/office/forum/office_2007-excel/copy-data-from-one-sheet-to-another-if-criteria/1834f3b6-9b5a-e011-8dfc-68b599b31bf5?auth=1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If what is described on that link would be an easy task for you, please contact me. Thanks.Budget: $10
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Converte pdf files to excel sheet - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Converte-pdf-files-excel-sheet_%7E01554e44e41469c583?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want to converte pdf files excel sheet.I want this work done precisely.Budget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Fluent English VA needed for data entry/misc VA tasks. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Fluent-English-needed-for-data-entry-misc-tasks_%7E01bc05d55f8bd42441?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for someone part time weekly to handle various tasks for my business.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The tasks will range from spreadsheets, google research, emails, customer service,scheduling etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fluency in English is a must.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Any plus&amp;#039;s would be experienced in marketing and/or adwords.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hours should start at around 10hrs per week with opportunities for more. 
Looking forward to hearing from potentialsPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Google Sheets,                     Marketing Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Research            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need to hire a VA - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-hire_%7E01e067e15a3a70a11e?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello, 
I need a VA to watch videos and complete what is listed in the video. 
Very simple work to do. Need it completed ASAP.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Web Research
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Google Search,                     Internet Research,                     Market Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Customer Service Rep - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Customer-Service-Rep_%7E0134596e717aa697c2?source=rss</link>
    <description>Summary
We are looking for positive, energetic people who like helping others. If you enjoy working with a fast growing company, and are willing to learn the ropes, we&amp;#039;d love to talk to you
Duties &amp;amp;amp; Responsibilities:
Taking orders at the sales counter and over the phone
Building relationships with customers
Ability to use company computer system to enter orders
Develop product knowledge to assist customers with purchases
Update / document customer records with accurate information
Overcome objections of prospective customers
Other administrative duties as assigned
REQUIREMENTS:
Excellent Telephone Skills,Written &amp;amp;amp; Verbal Communication skills.
Ability to resolve customer questions or problems
Skilled with Microsoft Office applications, especially Word and Excel.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Customer Service &amp;gt; Customer Service
Skills:        Customer Service,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Chief Virtual Operations Manager needed for executive management support: Admin/Accounts/Operations - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Chief-Virtual-Operations-Manager-needed-for-executive-management-support-Admin-Accounts-Operations_%7E01810ea801428c48c0?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a top-rated, highly-experienced, * ROCKSTAR VIRTUAL CHIEF OPERATIONS MANAGER*
Only applicants from Pakistan will be considered for logistical reasons.
ONLY APPLY IF you meet the following criteria: 
* You have logged over 1,000+ hours on Upwork. 
* You have a 100% job satisfaction rate.
* You are the best of the best.
* You can devote 50+ hours to this job every single week.
* You DO NOT work for an agency.
Virtual Chief Operations Manager Wanted
Permanent full time role. Options to work from a home based office. Opportunities to relocate to UAE and Europe. 
Our long running organization has been established for over 15 years and have employee retention rate of over 90%. 
Our organization deals directly with industry leading manufacturers such as Apple, Samsung, Sony and Panasonic. We are known for the great care we take with clients and employees alike. 
We actively encourage and finance professional development qualifications of all our employees. This often opens up opportunities to network and meet like minded professionals. 
As the role is virtual the candidate would have the freedom to work from anywhere.
Summary: The &amp;lsquo;virtual chief operations manager&amp;rsquo; will ensure all company operations flow smoothly and economically. He or she will be responsible for making sure that necessary work is done properly and on time. An understanding of details of the business and an enjoyment of handling details are necessary. Must be able to handle external relations with a diverse cultural client and supplier base. An excellent command of the English language is imperative. You will also set in motion the vision, strategic plan and goals for the organization alongside and reporting directly to the Chief Operations Officer. A very good understanding of the basic financial statements is required. Experience in financial modeling and financial planning is desirable. 
We need someone who is a self-starter, a great project manager (managing several projects at once), can constantly stay on top of different colleagues to receive work and accept new additional work, be diligent and organized to request new things that need to be done. Ability to co-ordinate between all team members on the phone. Is able to meet tight deadlines and work under pressure. Someone who is punctual, accurate, very detailed in their work and works in a very efficient manner.
Why apply? 
&amp;bull;	Excellent rates of pay 
&amp;bull;	Career progress opportunities
&amp;bull;	Workplace flexibility
&amp;bull;	Paid Holidays
&amp;bull;	Performance related bonus
&amp;bull;	Job security with a long term contract
Required skills, experience and qualifications: 
1.	Senior management level experience.
2.	A bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or above. An MBA would be desirable.
3.	Exceptional verbal and written English communication skills.
4.	Adaptability and strong problem solving skills.
5.	Excellent active listening skills.
6.	Highly proficient in Microsoft excel and adobe. 
7.	Managing masses of spreadsheets.
8.	Graphic and writing skills.
9.	Very proficient on all aspects of computer skills.
10.	A solid understanding of accounting and book keeping. AP and AR.
11.	Able to do web research using advance techniques.
12.	Critical thinking.
13.	Support for executive management.
14.	Project management experience.
15.	Organizational skills.
16.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A fast learner.
Qualities we look for: 
Ability to put him/herself in my shoes and make smart suggestions on how the above can be achieved. Efficient, yet with attention to detail. Creative and ready to go the extra mile in thinking things through to create solutions rather than just completion of tasks! 
What we don&amp;rsquo;t want: 
- No distractions
- No internet issues
- No personal / family problems
- Nothing that will take you away from work ever
- No excuse makers
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;*HOW TO APPLY IMPORTANT*
Send your bespoke cover letter response along with a CV. Please do not send a generic response instead tell us why you think you are the best for this role. Due to an extremely high volume of candidates we are asking that you submit a quick video (nothing fancy) telling us why you are a &amp;lsquo;Rockstar&amp;rsquo; for the position. You can email the video toPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Project Management
Skills:        Accounting,                     Administrative Support,                     Adobe PDF,                     Bookkeeping,                     Computer Skills,                     Data Mining,                     Email Handling,                     Graphic Design,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     Management Skills,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Project Management,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data entry for {â€‹type of data entry or your company name}â€‹ - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-entry-for-type-data-entry-your-company-name_%7E01c06f3a4dd8b2ceb9?source=rss</link>
    <description>About us:
{â€‹Description of your company and type of data entry work needed}â€‹
We&amp;#039;re looking for an experienced data entry specialist to transfer data into our main database. We anticipate that this project will require {â€‹#}â€‹ hours per week for {â€‹#}â€‹ weeks.
Deliverables:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Transfer invoices and customer data into our content management system
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Enter notes into database (when appropriate) to clarify any changes
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Compile all our past/current marketing campaigns into one central file
Requirements for the project:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Experience with Microsoft Suite (Word, Excel, etc.)
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Excellent grammar and a high attention to detail
In your proposal, please share a brief summary of your experience.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for an individual to assist in the operation of a watch repair service center in NYC Midtown - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-individual-assist-the-operation-watch-repair-service-center-NYC-Midtown_%7E01c30b327e5f300091?source=rss</link>
    <description>Top watch repair service center looking for an individual that is motivated, self-starter, proactive with below skills:
- Greet clients in office showroom
- Data entry of client and job information within customized system
- Write invoices and estimates through another system 
- Obtain status of job from watchmaker, jeweler and relay this status to client either online/phone/in-person
- Receive and send packages via USPS/FEDEX/UPS
Dear Candidate - our business is exciting, fun and growing. The energy is good and positive. Our clients love us (read our reviews).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Our co-workers and owners are very friendly. You will want to come into work everyday with an open heart. We have a great reputation online, in the industry and treat our associates like family. The days fly by quickly because of the good vibrations generated. Finally, the candidate selected will learn a tremendous amount about business and the jewelry/watch industry from the owners. Good luck, EricPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Customer Service &amp;gt; Other - Customer Service
Skills:        Drop Shipping,                     Google Docs,                     Logistics &amp;amp; Shipping,                     Microsoft Excel            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Marketing and Project Manager - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Marketing-and-Project-Manager_%7E016dd8476829dcb5f0?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a bilingual project manager with a lot of knowledge in marketing. The individual must be:
a) Knowledgeable and experienced with online and offline marketing
b) Have some experience managing other people. Project manager will have to manage 2-5 other individuals to deliver projects for our clients
c) Willing to grow and invest in the company
d) Responsible for the projects assigned to them
e) Responsible to keep those clients current with the help of the team.
About Us
We are a bilingual marketing agency based in Colorado that works with bilingual (Spanish and English) clients mostly in the construction industry. We identify and provide growth opportunities for our clients to improve revenue. Our vision is to become a major force to improve the businesses of Spanish-speaking individuals that own a construction company in the US and are looking to grow their businesses.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Project Management
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Translation English Spanish,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Google Sheets Specialist - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Google-Sheets-Specialist_%7E016eb309c53b97fe48?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a freelancer who has experience with Google Sheets and loves to create APIs and systems to make Google Sheets function like a tool.
We are looking to use APIs with in Google Sheets to create project management tools within Google Sheets. The freelancer needs to be well versed with Google Sheets, creating API functions, drop-downs, formulas, calendar options, and etc. 
HAVE TO BE AN EXPERT WITH GOOGLE SHEETS.
This is a one-time project that can turn in to more opportunities based on Google Sheet needs and project management tools needed to be created in Google Sheets. 
Candidates must be able to speak English fluently and be able to communicate occasionally via Upwork or email. 
Candidates that are considered for this role has to put the name &amp;amp;quot;Google Sheets Expert&amp;amp;quot; somewhere in their application!Budget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Google Sheets,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Internet Research - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Internet-Research_%7E012f034931d0ff3b80?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want a freelancer who can go over to the internet &amp;amp;amp; search for companies 
Please see the attached job description. 
Only apply if you have read the description
ThanksBudget: $50
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Excel Data to fill up - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Excel-Data-fill_%7E01a17f3dc92abd7dfc?source=rss</link>
    <description>have a excel file with upc&amp;#039;s I would like to get the asin number and the selling price and ranking and if amazon selling itPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assitant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assitant_%7E01ee0480801090c5ad?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are an organization that is committed to helping companies rethink the way that they support a workplace environment that is respectful for people of all backgrounds.
We are seeking to develop an ongoing relationship with a talented virtual assistant who is self-directed, and motivated to handle the action items of our various needs which include:
-CRM
-Project Management
-Research
-Email communication
-Strong writing skills
-Verbal communication skills
-(Customer service/over the phone communication)
This individual&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;will work closely with the founder of our organization and will be asked to:
-Work within agreed upon deadlines
-Bring a passion and drive for creating a high standard of work
-Sign our work for hire agreement
We ask that providers include the following for their bid:
-links to various emails/ content they have written
Happy Bidding!Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Content Writing,                     Email Handling,                     Email Marketing,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Telephone Handling,                     Virtual Assistant,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Manual Web Data Scrapping and Data Entry into Excel Spreadsheet - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Manual-Web-Data-Scrapping-and-Data-Entry-into-Excel-Spreadsheet_%7E01f40812bda32be001?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a detailed-oriented person that can scrape data on companies from specific websites, then do a couple of quick google searches to extract additional information about those companies and then compile the data in an excel spreadsheet. We are aiming to collect the company names, contact phone number, contact name, website url, and address for these companies. Identifying the contact name will require being able to use google search and then dig within the search results to find the proper name.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Google Search,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Super easy need kitchen line map recreated in excel and able to read need it ASAP really basicf - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Super-easy-need-kitchen-line-map-recreated-excel-and-able-read-need-ASAP-really-basicf_%7E011bd893385076802e?source=rss</link>
    <description>need redone in excel ASAP for a kitchen line prep station need to be able to read and exactly how its mapped outBudget: $25
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Microsoft Excel            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>I am looking for an experienced worker to list on eBay for me - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/looking-for-experienced-worker-list-eBay-for_%7E0105e3bb3ddb25ce3e?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for an experienced worker to list on eBay for me
What I am looking for someone who have or be able to use 
eBay listing experience.
High-speed internet
Google apl&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;like spreadsheet, doc.
Dropbox apl
How it will go
I will train you to list my eBay items using a system.
I&amp;rsquo;ll give you a manual and video in which I&amp;rsquo;m listing actually.
What is my system
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I put the pictures of items already in Dropbox.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The lister look over a file of pictures and uploaded pictures in the system.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Then fill in some parts of descriptions like size, color, parameters etc. 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I give URL of the items I would like the lister list then the lister uploaded pictures.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Next the lister fill in some parts of specification, descriptions on the system.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(There is some data the lister might need to list already in spreadsheets or Excel sheets)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
I need someone who can have enough bandwidth to download and upload pics,
No trouble writing english copy
List at least 10 items per 1 hour.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;( over 20items per day is preferable) 
Listing on a daily basis.
I will be paying the lister $1.00 per 10 items listed.Budget: $5
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Dropbox API,                     eBay Listing/Writing,                     Google Docs,                     Google Search,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Spreadsheets            Country: Japanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>DATABASE SPECIALIST (SQL SERVER) / SSRS - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/DATABASE-SPECIALIST-SQL-SERVER-SSRS_%7E015b904b5ba38b91ee?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are seeking for a Database Developer which should help us solve complex database design problems, including performance, scalability, security and integration issues.
Required responsibilities:
Develop ad-hoc SQL queries and reports on demand.
Develop queries, views, scalar and table-valued functions, and stored procedures.
Review the database designs and code of other developers and provide recommendations for improvement or optimizations
Provide support to troubleshoot and resolve technical issues within applications
Qualifications
5+ years of experience in developing databases in MS SQL Server utilizing stored procedures, functions, queries etc.
2+ years of experience developing reports in SSRS
Knowledge of SQL Server 2012 and newer versions
Knowledge of SQL internals, monitoring, and performance tuning is a plus
Experience working in small teams with a good mix of autonomy and accountability.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Database Design,                     Database Programming,                     Database Testing,                     SQL Programming            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Extraction / ETL - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Extraction-ETL_%7E01df4b0b218b203766?source=rss</link>
    <description>Dashboard migration: from Power BI to Tableau software
We need a tableau software expert to handle advanced ETL in Tableau.
- Extraction is out of scope
- Data model: Create relations between tables (&amp;amp;gt;5)
- Data quality: automation of data transformation
- Settings: filters management
- Calculated fields, time comparison management
- Data visualisation: charts creation (~75)
- Dashboard layout: 6 pages including story telling
- feedbacks implementation
You will be part of the data team of a famous agency and participate to a big performance measurement project. Interacting directly with a senior data scientist and a data consultant. 
A detailed documentation will be provide.
Forst estimation of the mission: ~30 days.
Delivery: A tableau desktop file containing all settings and visualisationsPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Business Intelligence,                     Microsoft Power BI,                     Tableau Software            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 14:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>DBA/Database developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/DBA-Database-developer_%7E012006804f2e6bf88b?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a seasoned DBA with SQL Server 2012 and up experience to help us maintain and follow up on the health on our ever-changing database. Must be able to provide 2 hours response time
Must have experience with 
1.	SQL Server installation
2.	Backup
3.	Index Tuning
4.	Maintenance plans
5.	Permissions
6.	Database migrations
7.	Query optimization
8.	Solid experience with writing SQL QueriesPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 12:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Report analyst (Mexico) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Report-analyst-Mexico_%7E016e0400d2b77b9749?source=rss</link>
    <description>Is a highly focused professional experienced in the Data Analysis sector that designs and monitors internal reporting and researching of results to prevent potential problems and detect deviations. The CX Intelligence Analyst acknowledges the importance of understanding metrics and what is searching for. The analyst also will be responsible for modeling clear and concise reports for varying management levels within the Company.
Define relevant topics, taxonomies and queries to be monitored
Monitor reporting results and audit data quality: conduct listening &amp;amp;amp; monitoring to detect any opportunity or risk for the Connection Centre or client internal stakeholders
Ensuring and producing searching and analysing data according to pre-defined keywords and processes tracing and conducting manual sentiment analysis from the data ad hoc, daily, weekly, monthly and yearly reports
Ensure Intelligence services are delivered according to the standards in order to achieve KPIs and SLAs.
Ensure standard metrics are followed and results are interpreted correctly by collaborating with Relations Center Teams.
Define and update reporting structure definition to match with clients needs for insights.
Development and continuous improvement of Relation Center reporting.
Build close relationship with the Relation Center Teams to drive the delivery of information solutions. 
Develop new measurement systems when required.
Obtain data required to generate information reports and structure it assuring integrity and data quality.
Proactively contribute to the improvement of operations and simplifying processes.
Generate ad-hoc information and reports to the Management Team when necessary.
Continuous research of consumer behaviour.
Requirements
BS degree in marketing, business economics, mathematics, statistics or computer sciences.
Expert knowledge of Microsoft Excel, SQL and Access.
Expert user of Pages, Keynote and Powerpoint.
Interest in digital marketing, social media and technology.
Fully proficient in English and Spanish. Other languages are a plus.
At least 2 years of relevant experience
Proactive and positive attitudeBudget: $1,500
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Country: Spainclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 11:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>iPhone App - API &amp;amp;amp; Database - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/iPhone-App-API-amp-Database_%7E01e5aea2ea5d3c9487?source=rss</link>
    <description>App design - only European freelancers - NDA required
I am building an iPhone app that gives the user quick access to product information drawn from two different data 
The app shall be
- equipped with a scanner to read barcodes and extract GTIN or HIBBC numbers (identidier) from the barcode
- alternatively users can enter the identifier
- the number is then used to query an online database via API
- the app will then extract certain values from the online database, which are used to query another table and extract further information. The table is available online but will have to be downloaded to a operating Webserver and automatically updated whenever a new version is available online. An RSS feed can be used to check availability of the new version
- the user should then have the possibility to see all information for the specific product (from table and online database)
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Budget: $800
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development
Skills:        API Development,                     Database Management,                     iPhone App Development,                     Relational Databases            Country: Switzerlandclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 11:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data entry, extracting telephone numbers from a website to an Excel spreadsheet. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-entry-extracting-telephone-numbers-from-website-Excel-spreadsheet_%7E0130f74ba5dbc92345?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need an Excel doc filled with numbers and names from specific websitesPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 10:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>AWS Lambda Developers - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/AWS-Lambda-Developers_%7E010ad4a0e83c7e952b?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for developers with at least 2 years of experience with Amazon Web Services, particularly on server-less computing (AWS lambda).
Responsibilities
- Primary focus will be on logic operators, Lambda jobs and API integration.
- Write SWF jobs
- Write Lambda jobs
- Develop simple UI for input of custom attribute tags
- Assist in higher level QA tickets that require codebase knowledge
Core Skills / Requirements
- AWS Certified (preferred, not required)
- Amazon Cognito
- AWS Lambda (Python, Node.js, C#)
- React
- SQL queriesPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon Cognito,                     AWS Lambda,                     C#,                     Node.js,                     Python            Country: New Zealandclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 08:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Extract Facebook Group Emails - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Extract-Facebook-Group-Emails_%7E014319729683c79ced?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello,
I would need someone who could extract facebook and linkedin groups emails.
Someone experienced&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;that knows what he&amp;#039;s doing.
Thank youPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Country: Portugalclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 06:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Develop script to pull data from websites to paste into excel - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Develop-script-pull-data-from-websites-paste-into-excel_%7E0131782549bd12ea8f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for a script to pull realtors and offices from local MLS boards. I want the script to run from excel and pull data based a provided url. This can be done very easily and efficiently to someone who knows what they are doing. Essentially you just need the script to go to a given website and extract the data into excel. 
Script Specifics:
1. In Excel file, put input field for user to place url to extract data from
2. In Excel file, provide toggle option for list to be agents or offices as data fields differ if necessary* see urls below for clarification
3. In Excel file, put run button
4. For agent, script should pull:
name, address, city, state, zip, cell, home, office, email, website, realtor profile link, office name, office main #, office fax #, office address, office city, state, zip, office website, and any other data fields present in agent records
5. For office, script should pull:
office name, mailing address, city, state, zip, main #, fax #, website, email, physical address, city, state, zip and any other data fields present in office records
6. Place all data into excel with one record per row with agents on one tab and offices on another, should also include url data was pulled from
Script should work on multiple websites using the Systems Engineering platform. It absolutely must work on the following two websites and urls for both agent and office data:
https://aikenmls.com/default.asp?content=agents&amp;amp;amp;the_letter=ALL
https://aikenmls.com/default.asp?content=office&amp;amp;amp;the_letter=ALL
https://www.usamls.net/augusta/default.asp?content=agents&amp;amp;amp;the_letter=ALL
https://www.usamls.net/augusta/default.asp?content=office&amp;amp;amp;the_letter=ALL
NOTE: Site data structure should be the same but fields and data available may differ. Please refer both sites before bidding and state approach to process and project.Budget: $40
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Excel VBA,                     Python,                     Scripting,                     VBA,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Help/Tutor SQLlite SQL data/view formatting. 1 hour. Right now. (skype chat) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Help-Tutor-SQLlite-SQL-data-view-formatting-hour-Right-now-skype-chat_%7E01bdd39392412abc7d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need help building a query in SQLLite (Using DB Browser) right now.
Looking for someone to help via skype chat messaging.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        MySQL Programming,                     SQL,                     SQLite Programming            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior Backend Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-Backend-Developer_%7E01b9dcde1e3f7f8dce?source=rss</link>
    <description>&amp;middot; Responsible for adding smaller new features to the main product
&amp;middot; Communicating effectively while writing clean code
&amp;middot; Cooperate with Product Owners, Software Engineers, and UX Designers on the product roadmap
Requirements
&amp;middot; 3-5+ years of experience building the UI of consumer-facing or enterprise software products
&amp;middot; Comfortable with JavaScript libraries/frameworks like Angular 2+, React.js, Vue.js, etc
&amp;middot; Willingness and aptitude to get up to speed on Vue.js development
&amp;middot; Experience or familiarity with MySQL, or AWS
&amp;middot; Comfortable with JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS3
&amp;middot; Knowledge on backend with NodeJS, python (for data)
&amp;middot; Knowledge on putting up data-driven documents
- Excellent understanding of machine learning techniques and algorithms, such as k-NN, Naive Bayes, SVM,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Decision Forests, etc.
- Experience with common data science toolkits, such as R, Weka, NumPy, MatLab, etc. Excellence in at least one of these is highly desirable
- Great communication skills
- Experience with data visualisation tools, such as D3.js, GGplot, etc.
- Proficiency in using query languages such as SQL, Hive, Pig
- Experience with NoSQL databases, such as MongoDB, Cassandra, HBase
- Good applied statistics skills, such as distributions, statistical testing, regression, etc.
- Data-oriented personality
Desired Skills
&amp;middot; Professional or personal experience with Vue.js
&amp;middot; Knowledge or professional experience with Firebase and AWS (EC2, S3, Lambda, DynamoDB)Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Country: Philippinesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 04:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Project Manager for Silicon Chip project - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Project-Manager-for-Silicon-Chip-project_%7E01557d8e7e9ae5afcb?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are implementing a silicon chip that will be used to expand data centers by a factor of 12 in the same budget.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The project is very complex, with multiple different technologies, and various aspects such as vendor interactions, negotiations, etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Make no mistake, this is hard to manage.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Looking for a brave soul to try their hand.
Specifically, the technologies involved:
-] Hadoop, Spark, Kafka, NoSQL databases, Python, Machine Learning
-] RTL implementation in Chisel HDL (plus some Verilog development)
-] Physical Design using Cadence EDA tools for synthesis, layout, extraction, and signoff
-] FireSim FPGA based full system simulator
-] Packet switch implementation
Projects:
-] Measuring performance of applications written in those technologies on our chip
-] Porting OpenJDK over to RISC-V instruction set
-] Recruiting / Hiring
-] Physical Design implementation of the processor core, and of the switch, and of the chip
-] RTL implementation of the processor core, and the switch, and the chip
-] Verification of RTL
-] Modification of FireSim to make it model our product
-] Verification of entire product, via FireSim
-] Customer acquisition
-] Customer evaluation of product via FireSim
-] Fundraising -- includes press releases, gathering letters of support, etcPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Project Management
Skills:        Project Management,                     Project Planning,                     Project Scheduling            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 04:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry from a print book to Excel Spreadsheet - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-from-print-book-Excel-Spreadsheet_%7E010d4d9c4c5706d2d3?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have an address book of approx 700 pages, which includes approx 2000 contacts. We would like someone to extract the email addresses from the contacts that have an email address on each page and enter them in an excel spreadsheet.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 04:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>International trade data- extraction, organization, queries (Data Scientist w/ JS skills) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/International-trade-data-extraction-organization-queries-Data-Scientist-skills_%7E01bca0986adb9c4a94?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are building an International Trade Dashboard prototype that leverages our data to understand the historical, immediate, and potential impact of trade activities on the US economy. This includes dashboards of US Trade Activity, US Trade Impacts, International Trade Activity, among other data.
We will provide you all the data KPIs that are needed, which datasets to find them in, and how we&amp;#039;d like the data structured.
Ready to start immediately on an hourly basis, we&amp;#039;ve built prototypes like this in the past in 2-3 days, and want to complete the prototype by the end of the week.
Thanks for reading, and look forward to hearing from you.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     Data Extraction,                     Data Management,                     Data Mining,                     Data Science,                     JavaScript,                     Python,                     R            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 02:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web data extraction EXPERT - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-data-extraction-EXPERT_%7E0116ff0fc105a5dbf6?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a Web data extraction expert! (also known as web scraping, web harvesting, screen scraping, etc.) 
I need to extract lots of data through an automated process. I&amp;#039;m looking for someone who can help me import data into excel from a website.
I will need this done within the next week. If you read this far what&amp;#039;s 40-27=
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        CSS,                     CSS3,                     HTML,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     PHP,                     Web Design,                     Website Development,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 23:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Tableau Consultant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Tableau-Consultant_%7E01c8ffdedf95d998a2?source=rss</link>
    <description>Sr. Tableau Consultant
Alethix LL is looking for a Sr. Tableau Consultant will be working with database and business to design, develop, implement data visualization and document data integration processes as well as creating dashboards. 
The ideal candidate will have extensive experience with traditional Reporting, ETL, and Data Warehouse concepts. The candidate should have excellent communication skills and able to work with product owner to develop and define technical requirements. The candidate should have strong command with Tableau and related solution set. 
Responsibilities:
&amp;bull;	Interact with Business users and understand their requirements from a data analytic, visualization and UI/UX perspective.
&amp;bull;	Design Dashboards and Reports in Tableau with different data sources - DB2, SQL, Oracle etc.
&amp;bull;	Support the Business Intelligence/Analytics data analyst with the understanding of business and data requirements, and iteratively designs visualizations for initial concepts and prototypes that can be presented to customers for feedback
&amp;bull;	Perform detailed data analysis (i.e., determine the structure, content, and quality of the data through examination of source systems and data samples)
&amp;bull;	Build prototypes for demonstration and illustration purposes for peer groups, Business partners, or senior leaders.
&amp;bull;	Understand and analyze the data to find patterns and valuable business insights
&amp;bull;	Act as a mentor and Tableau SME for other Tableau users across the enterprise
Location: Washington D.C.
Minimum Requirements:
&amp;bull;	10+ years of professional experience in building Reports, Dashboards and Scorecards
&amp;bull;	10+ years of experience and in-depth Knowledge of Business Intelligence tools and architectures (primarily with Tableau)
&amp;bull;	7+ years of experience in SQL, RDBMS design, development and performance tuning
&amp;bull;	7+ years of data warehousing tools and techniques (Datastage ETL, Netezza, MapR preferred)
&amp;bull;	5+ Previous experience in the BI design of complex systems projects
&amp;bull;	Ability to understand and analyze the data to find patterns and valuable Business Insights
&amp;bull;	Understanding of the Data warehouse life cycle right from data source to ETL to transformations to multidimensional models like data marts, star schema and Reporting
&amp;bull;	Strong Semantic design (Like Universe, Tableau Data Source, QVD) and data modeling skills
&amp;bull;	Ability to read and write effective, modular, dynamic (parameterized) and robust code, establish and follow already established code standards, and ETL framework.
&amp;bull;	Extensive experience interpreting functional needs and writing or editing solution designs for new systems, systems changes or system enhancements of a highly complex and sophisticated nature.
&amp;bull;	Strong consulting, leading and mentoring skills
We are driven by our commitment to our clients and to our employees. If you are looking for a new opportunity, we would love to have you join our team!
Alethix, LLC is a growing company. We are a leading-edge Information Infrastructure Transformation Services company committed to delivering agile and effective solutions by leveraging the latest technology innovations and industry best practices.
Our team leverages decades of past experience across U.S. federal agencies and the commercial sector to deliver practical solutions to meet the business- and mission-critical challenges of our clients.
Every project we undertake is guided by our methodology of success. This proven methodology focuses on understanding our clients&amp;rsquo; business needs, developing strategic solutions, incorporating evolving requirements throughout implementation, and delivering quality and cost-effective solutions.
Alethix, LLC uses E-Verify to validate all new hires&amp;#039; ability to legally work in the United States. Alethix, LLC is an Equal Opportunity Employer, and all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, age, gender, national origin, sexual orientation, genetic information, disability, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     SQL,                     Tableau Software            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 22:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>spss statistician - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/spss-statistician_%7E01e1c68b582348d1fb?source=rss</link>
    <description>spss data analysis want to hire a spss statistician who can find mean, standard deviation, frequency, percentage, pearson correlation coefficient and multiple linear regression.
data is already extracted in excel sheet from questionnaires
need on urgent basis.Budget: $30
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        IBM SPSS            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 20:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Symfony Developer (PHP) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Symfony-Developer-PHP_%7E0146c653d1cc9cb831?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a creative, hardworking and trustworthy (4+ years of relevant experience) full-stack developer. 
We are only looking for developers in the European Timezones!
As a full stack PHP Developer you will be responsible for the development, performance and scaling of our public websites as well as internal systems. 
You should be available for full-time up to 30 / 40 hours a week.
We are working with 6 team members, on different web applications.
The technology stack you will be using consists of:
* PHP 7.0 (Symfony Framework 4, Doctrine ORM);
* HTML5, CSS (Bootstrap)
* PHPUnit
* (Debian) Linux
* PostgreSQL
* Gitlab
* Vagrant
* Jira/ Confluence
Requirements:
* You&amp;rsquo;re an experienced (min. 4 years) Developer with hands-on experience with (object oriented) programming in PHP 7.0, using PostgreSQL and MVC;
* You have experience with Symfony Framework 4.
* You are a residence in one of the European Timezones.
* You are available for at least 30/40 hours a week.
* You have good experience with HTML5, JavaScript and CSS3
* Your code is efficient, aware of patterns and anti-patterns, properly structured, easily comprehensible and well documented
* HTTP and server-side technologies (web servers, database servers) are an obvious part of your experience;
* You&amp;rsquo;re proficient in writing efficient SQL queries.
* You&amp;rsquo;re experienced in distributed version control (GitLab)
* You&amp;rsquo;re proactive in communication.
* You have experience with working in a SCRUM Team. 
* You have experience with working in Jira.
* You&amp;#039;re Fluent in English (speech and writing)
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        JavaScript,                     PHP            Country: Netherlandsclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 20:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Website Scrape Get paid in less then 30 min! - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Website-Scrape-Get-paid-less-then-min_%7E011a8fcf8bd4ab87eb?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need Website Scrape
Just looking for 2 quick scrapes...
1.
https://www.google.com/search?ei=oeDEW89Kg_6PBKzsn-AN&amp;amp;amp;q=financial+crimes+jobs+nyc&amp;amp;amp;oq=financial+crimes+jobs+nyc&amp;amp;amp;gs_l=psy-ab.3..0.68875.74356..74469...1.0..1.339.3364.28j7j0j1....2..0....1..gws-wiz.......0i71j0i131j0i131i67j0i67j0i10j0i131i10j0i22i30.DB9frxYbwaQ&amp;amp;amp;ibp=htl;jobs&amp;amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwi257iIjoneAhWQ0YMKHRf2BnAQiYsCKAF6BAgGECU#fpstate=tldetail&amp;amp;amp;htidocid=T13q0biYrXtxAbJhAAAAAA%3D%3D&amp;amp;amp;htivrt=jobs
2. https://www.indeed.com/jobs?q=financial+crimes&amp;amp;amp;l=New+York,+NY&amp;amp;amp;radius=50&amp;amp;amp;jt=fulltimeBudget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Data Extraction            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 20:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>.Net Developer (CONTRACT WORK for 6 MONTHS) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Net-Developer-CONTRACT-WORK-for-MONTHS_%7E0199c6a19d013bd17a?source=rss</link>
    <description>A leading US software solution company is looking for Developer/Consultant in .Net. This company has a suite of legal practice software products, individually or combined that allows law firms to improve the workflow necessary to support the entire litigation or filing lifecycle, and reduce the risks associated with missing dates and current content.
LOCATION:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ENCINO, CALIFORNIA (Must work on-premise - OUR OFFICE)
THE POSITION&amp;rsquo;S PURPOSE: 
Application Developer will work primarily with new MVC application being using .Net Core. 
Major daily tasks involve around Angular JS, HTML 5, bootstrap, .Net Web API. Database schema 
design and complex data analysis are also critical part of the development process.
ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS / MAJOR OBJECTIVES / DELIVERABLES:
MVC Application Development using .Net Core:
Build/Enhance the Angular JS based MVC Application.
Develop/Expand the .Net Web API using .Net Core. 
Interact with various UI libraries like JQuery, Bootstrap, HTML5, Angular JS and Integrate the Front end with .Net core.
Write windows services, web applications and desktop application in .net
Write CSS and front end code.
.Net Expertise:
SQL Server Development(Query Optimizations, Writing Stored Procedures )
T-SQL:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Analyze data sets and determine how information relates to an information system.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Perform ad-hoc queries using SQL And able to Optimize queries for performance.
Adhere to project timelines and deliverable, effective communication of changes or disruptions to the schedule with a focus on expectation alignment.
Build applications using Web N-Tier application development architecture.
Identify business processes and develop solutions to solve problems.
EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS / SKILLS / EXPERIENCE:
* 5+ years of application programming experience using industry standard development tools.
* 5+ years with SQL (T-SQL, SSRS, SSIS, SSAS) 
* Experience with bit bucket or Git hub is a major plus.
* Expert at creating and consuming web services using technologies such as SOAP, REST, WCF, WebAPI, Generic Handlers, etc.
* Agile/Scrum project development.
* Strong problem-solving skills required.
* Have strong and confident communication skill set in customer support and presentation.
* Have background in engineering and reverse engineering system logic.
* Be able to work in a team environment.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Mobile programming languages:C#,         Javascript            App development frameworks:Angular            Databases:MS SQL            Devices:Tablet            
Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Application Firewall (WAF) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Application-Firewall-WAF_%7E01621c344b6060a990?source=rss</link>
    <description>A Web Application Firewall (or WAF) filters, monitors, and blocks HTTP traffic to and from a Web Application. WAF Inspects HTTP traffic, it can prevent attacks stemming from web application security flaws, such as SQL injection, cross-site scripting (XSS), file inclusion, and security misconfigurations, etc. We require a Web Application Firewall similar to &amp;amp;quot;https://www.cloudflare.com/waf/&amp;amp;quot; 
The final Product is supposed to be a Web Application which will be hosted on Amazon Cloud by the Freelancer,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;we are looking for Freelancer(s) who are expert in PHP and MySQL, freelancers who have hosted 5-10 online web applications may only apply to this job, please.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Note: Please use the attached excel file to submit the Proposal. Include as many attacks as possible. Include the cost of hosting and maintenance in the Quotation. Please share your Portfolio. 
Kindly let us know if you have any queries.Budget: $17,500
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        Network Security,                     PHP,                     Website Development            Country: Norwayclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 16:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Research/Data Entry for Real Estate Investor - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Research-Data-Entry-for-Real-Estate-Investor_%7E01384e6394c41444fd?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;#039;m looking for a fast, detailed and efficient person to help with a small web research/data entry project. Qualified applicant must be able to lookup property addresses on a tax assessor website and populate a spreadsheet with the required data.
I will provide the property address, and that address should be looked up on the Pierce County tax assessor website. From the website, I&amp;#039;ll need you to extract the owner name and mailing address, as well as the last sale date and last sale price. That&amp;#039;s it.
I believe our list is about 200 records. In your response, please provide three things:
1) when you can start on the project
2) how quickly you can turn it around
3) how much per record you would chargeBudget: $10
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Research            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 16:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>visualize twitter network - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/visualize-twitter-network_%7E01d76555b2a507249c?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a programmer to help me to extract data from Twitter. build the relationship between nodes according to the retweet interaction. then visualize the network. calculate the retweet path (width and depth)Budget: $200
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Visualization
Skills:        Python            Country: Saudi Arabiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Scraper - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Scraper_%7E01ff9598097372067e?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need to build a web scraper that can query Google with a list of city names and the search term &amp;amp;quot;homes&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;real estate&amp;amp;quot;
Example would be to search Google for new york homes or new york real estate
For every search, the scraper would need to be able to extract the top 10 search results and output them to a CSV file which has the top 5 domain names and their google rankings
The city list has 99 cities, this means that upon execution of the web scraper, I would need to be able to see both searches (2), example: new york homes and new york real estate, with each of the 5 results. In total, meaning there should be an output of:
99 cities * 2 types of searches (homes or real estate) * 5 results = 990 results
Ideally the way this would work is an easy to execute file, that I could use once per month to collect these 990 results.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Scraping,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>We need a freelancer to extract data and provide information - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/need-freelancer-extract-data-and-provide-information_%7E01241a658e9ee6e5dd?source=rss</link>
    <description>Word Limit: 2000 words + TOC + 100 word Executive Summary + Calculations + Graphs/Figures/Tables 
(FInancial Planning -Budgeting &amp;amp;amp; Debt Managment)Budget: $80
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Financial Analysis,                     Financial Planning,                     Financial Writing            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Well researched Technical Content Writing On Data Warehouses Like Redshift, Snowflake, Bigquery. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Well-researched-Technical-Content-Writing-Data-Warehouses-Like-Redshift-Snowflake-Bigquery_%7E01d3af59b8179d95cc?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for individuals/teams that can deliver technically researched, in-depth content on data warehouse technologies such as Redshift, Snowflake and Google BigQuery. You should have had hands on experience in these technologies to get the technical facts right. 
Example of the content: 
https://hevodata.com/blog/mysql-to-redshift-etl/
https://www.periscopedata.com/blog/redshift-and-rds-postgres-benchmarkedBudget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Amazon Redshift,                     BigQuery,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Research,                     Snowflake,                     Technical Writing            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 09:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Website Data Extraction / Research Project on Multiple Websites - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Website-Data-Extraction-Research-Project-Multiple-Websites_%7E01b0562cd4dbf95ef1?source=rss</link>
    <description>We require someone who will be able to collate various data across multiple websites (around 300) using web scraping. The websites contain information on car parking facilities provided by local authorities across the UK. 
Further details on what is required will be provided on application.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 09:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Excel Data Entry - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Excel-Data-Entry_%7E01bc43b4bfabe14373?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for someone to find and extract the nutritional data from selected restaurants and put them into a spreadsheet for me that I will provide. 
The work must critically be mistake free and accurate.
Have attached an example of what I would need in the exact format I need it. 
The role would involved data mining, web research to find any missing data and ultimately the input of the data. 
Best RegardsPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Create Custom Hana Calculation View - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Create-Custom-Hana-Calculation-View_%7E01bfb5cc747224f436?source=rss</link>
    <description>Create a custom calculation view in SAP Hana that is based upon data extracted from SAP Business One.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The data to be reported on includes Sales Orders and for each order the first 3 invoices issued for each order.
The invoices must be ranked based upon invoice date.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The resulting data from each invoice would then be pivoted into three sets of columns with each column set to include invoice number, invoice date and invoice amount.
The resulting package must be portable to migrate to a production system with appropriate permission to run.
Input parameter will be order date range.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Analytics,                     SAP BusinessOne,                     SAP Hana            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Desktop Software Development - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Desktop-Software-Development_%7E019e437b977b393e50?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am working on an interactive Form project using C#. This Form extracts data from an existing table in SQL server. View Data button can only download users data based on their Windows login process (they are restricted to see their own data only).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Users are able to enter new data in to the Form and be able to modify the existing their own data and then upload the new data back to the same table. The first 6 columns are configured as Read only (non editable), the remaining columns are read-write and can be edited. 
I have developed this project using C# and the code is about 40 lines. Some areas of the code are functioning properly as described above,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;however, some parts of the code are generating error.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Here is the breakdown of the Form components; 
1- One label box,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Two command buttons (1- View Data, 2- Upload) and One DataGridView to pull data from SQL table.
What is working:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
1- &amp;#039;View Data&amp;#039; button is working properly for all users as well as for login restriction. Able to extract data from SQL Query successfully.
2- &amp;#039;Upload&amp;#039; button is working properly without login restrictions. (e.g. extracting data for all users)
3- However, upload button is not working after user login restrictions are implemented. (Based on users Windows login).
4- The first 6 Columns Read Only restriction option is not working. Error message is generated.
I need someone to help me to troubleshoot the areas that aren&amp;#039;t working properly (as listed under items 3 and 4 above). Please let me know the time frame and cost.
Thank you,
MikeBudget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        C#            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 03:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Desktop Software Development - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Desktop-Software-Development_%7E019e437b977b393e50?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am working on an interactive Form project using C#. This Form extracts data from an existing table in SQL server. View Data button can only download users data based on their Windows login process (they are restricted to see their own data only).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Users are able to enter new data in to the Form and be able to modify the existing their own data and then upload the new data back to the same table. The first 6 columns are configured as Read only (non editable), the remaining columns are read-write and can be edited. 
I have developed this project using C# and the code is about 40 lines. Some areas of the code are functioning properly as described above,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;however, some parts of the code are generating error.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Here is the breakdown of the Form components; 
1- One label box,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Two command buttons (1- View Data, 2- Upload) and One DataGridView to pull data from SQL table.
What is working:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
1- &amp;#039;View Data&amp;#039; button is working properly for all users as well as for login restriction. Able to extract data from SQL Query successfully.
2- &amp;#039;Upload&amp;#039; button is working properly without login restrictions. (e.g. extracting data for all users)
3- However, upload button is not working after user login restrictions are implemented. (Based on users Windows login).
4- The first 6 Columns Read Only restriction option is not working. Error message is generated.
I need someone to help me to troubleshoot the areas that aren&amp;#039;t working properly (as listed under items 3 and 4 above). Please let me know the time frame and cost.
Thank you,
MikeBudget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        C#            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 03:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Scraping expert. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Scraping-expert_%7E01ddd15ad0d587a909?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for sommeone with expertise in extraction in web scraping and data extraction. pls inbox me only if you have rich experience in the field and is serious about the project.Budget: $70
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Data Mining,                     JavaScript,                     Python,                     Web Scraping            Country: Nepalclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 02:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Online Listing Directory Extraction - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Online-Listing-Directory-Extraction_%7E0124069833699b822f?source=rss</link>
    <description>Project:
Data extraction from two directory websites. Need 7-8 fields pulled per listing and dumped into an Excel file including listing pictures (if available). Will provide detailed instructions upon acceptance of&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;job.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I imagine there are around 300 listings. 
Columnar Deliverable in Excel:
Unique ID per each listing in the list (Start with DR-1, DR-2, DR-3, DR-4 etc)
Name
Type of [shared after job acceptance]
Sex (if known)
Phone Number
Address (add more columns if more than one address)
Website
[shared after job acceptance] Name (if available)
Email address (if available)
Photo (if available, extract and name the same as the Unique ID you created for each [shared after job acceptance])
Minimum Requirements:
You have done this before and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;can deliver within 36 hours.Budget: $20
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        Data Extraction,                     Data Scraping,                     Scripting,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 02:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQLite DB Developer (preferably with C# experience) for Windows 10 UWP App (Portland OR based only) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQLite-Developer-preferably-with-experience-for-Windows-UWP-App-Portland-based-only_%7E01742846c737afb2a0?source=rss</link>
    <description>This project is a Windows 10 UWP app that interfaces with a local on-device SQLite database.
The person hired for this job must bring excellent database design skills (preferably with experience using C# for database development). Their design should be able meet our app&amp;#039;s functional and performance expectations, which will be provided later to the short-listed candidates.
The project deliverables include:
* SQLite Database schema designed and tested for all of use cases on all supported device types (Windows 10 Phone, Windows 10 Tablet, Windows 10 PC)
* Example SQL queries for all of our use cases and documentation on their usage, as well as any test data creation
* The database design should meet and validated for our performance expectations on all supported device types 
* Detailed documentation that describes the schema (primary and foreign key constraints, joins and relationships, etc)
IMPORTANT: 
* There is an existing implementation of SQLite database which is not designed optimally or uses any of the best practices as it was designed by a developer who had to pick up database programming on the fly. Nonetheless, it can be made available as a starting point to the person hired for this assignment.
* Detailed use-cases and requirements will be made available to the person hired for the job, but if it helps in estimating effort or coming up with a quote, here&amp;#039;s some information on the size of the database in tables, records, and relationships:
- The current implementation uses less than 15 tables. Most of these tables are meta-data tables with less than 50 rows.
- The maximum number of records that any table can have is capped at 100,000
- There is a main table that maintains historical data and has foreign-key constraints/joins with some meta-data tables. Those meta-data tables in turn may have constraints/joins with other meta-data tables or amongst themselves.
- Since the database lives on a consumer device (mobile device or a PC), the design or scale isn&amp;#039;t complex or complicated, but may require creativity in coming up with optimal queries that meet functional and performance requirements, especially due to the limited features that a SQLite database provides on a Windows mobile device.Budget: $1,000
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Mobile programming languages:C#            Platforms:Windows            Databases:SQLite,         MySQL,         MS SQL            Devices:Phone,         Tablet            
Other Skills:        Database Design,                     Database Programming            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Hiring a Data Analyst/Mathematician - Experience with Klipfolio and Excel Reporting - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Hiring-Data-Analyst-Mathematician-Experience-with-Klipfolio-and-Excel-Reporting_%7E019dc9b9c7ed8f1dc6?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for an individual to join our team several hours per week to assist our company in the following:
-Identify trends (red alters or where we are doing well) in our call center customer service reporting, as well as in internal reports for sales, leads, and accounting. 
-Develop and provide reporting 
-Determine where the gaps are with our current reporting systems (we generate multiple reports from various online systems). 
Ideally, you are also a skilled data analyst who is proficient in extracting data information from API&amp;rsquo;s and other data libraries, excel files, etc in order to help us interpret multiple data streams.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        API Testing,                     Business Mathematics,                     Data Analytics,                     Klipfolio,                     Trend Analysis            Country: Panamaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 21:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>data processing - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/data-processing_%7E01f5c9636a6beb6d6d?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have movement data of people. I have a piece of code written in python this code to read csv files and process the data then extract processed data in csv file. I need to add some function to this code. Do you have time to help me in this.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Machine Learning,                     Predictive Analytics,                     Python            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 20:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Google Maps Scrapper Required to Extract the Listings - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Google-Maps-Scrapper-Required-Extract-the-Listings_%7E01a987c5f26a623ab2?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi, I need a scrapper who can scrap all the google maps listings for a category in UAE. All map listings to be scrapped with following details 
Required:
Listing Name, Address, Email, Website, GPS coordinates/map location, phone, Timings, reviews and photos from Google Maps and Reviews.Budget: $25
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Extraction,                     Data Mining,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Arab Emiratesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 17:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Webscraping Expert needed for various projects - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Webscraping-Expert-needed-for-various-projects_%7E0160a42423b2f87344?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have 3 webscraping projects right now I need help with in the short term. Looking for a a freelancer who: 
- Is very capable of scraping large amounts of records (5Million+)
- Ability to increase performance on the scrapers
- Data has to be sent a SQL server on Amazon AWS. 
- I will provide a SQL table schema. 
- Looking for someone who can 
- Ideally I find someone who wants to build a long-term relationship
- We will sometimes have video calls to exchange ideas
Details about the first project are in this document. 
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pSHTpvl9pDw5ZPJkdBq99Ltu-EqVBs67SvA1KyxzGvI/editPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Data Scraping,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Web Scraping            Country: Netherlandsclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 10:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Scrape property developers - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Scrape-property-developers_%7E01e56b18b0c25221d9?source=rss</link>
    <description>We need to build a real estate &amp;laquo;&amp;nbsp;search engine&amp;nbsp;&amp;raquo; of property developers. 
To build it we need to scrape all properties available to our providers (property developers) and put them in a database.
We will provide links and credentials of each property developers. 
This database will be use via some criteria&amp;rsquo;s (5 or 6) with drop down menu like city,department,price, size etc..
This tool (scraper &amp;amp;amp; database) should be upgradable if we add new offers tool should be able to manage new offers of new property developers added. 
Search engine will be implemented into a landing page and website, result will be a scrolling list (with pic associated to each property in second column) of properties according search criteria if none criteria is selected, output will be list of all database an extract file (XL) user should be able to download it.Budget: $100
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Scraping,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     Python,                     Web Scraping            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 08:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Ad hoc reporting from mongodb - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/hoc-reporting-from-mongodb_%7E017353cbbaaa77a2ec?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi - I have a mongodb used as the backend for my inventory business.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;55k entities with probably 15 attributes each.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I need to build some reports summarizing the data.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I am familiar with excel and SQL queries but know nothing about mongodb. I will provide a copy of the database for the reporting to be built on top of (this is a one time exercise it won&amp;rsquo;t be done against the live db on an ongoing basis).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ideally I&amp;rsquo;d like it to be setup to work locally on a desktop but would be ok putting it in AWS and running some reporting package (Quick Sight?).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Also I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pay some $100/month subscription to do so.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;So let&amp;rsquo;s chat on how best to implement.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;rsquo;d like to canned reports to be built but I can also build my own. Feel free to ask questions.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     Data Mining,                     Microsoft Excel,                     MongoDB            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 20:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch job management utility development. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-job-management-utility-development_%7E011e1b511b174a21d5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a developer with skills in C#, SQL database and web browser interface.
The project involves developing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;a batch job management&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;utility.
We have a Microsoft SQL Server database with a list of jobs that need to be started,
monitored and reported. The database has a basic winform interface. We have updated
the database and plan to use webui based interface.
Project involves 
1. creating webui forms for interaction with this database. We expect 7 different forms needed
to manage inputs for the database.
2. Write new SQL functions to support reports and status generation. Reports will be both tables and charts. We expect 6-7 reports to be generated with table and charts.
3. Create batch job commands, launch, monitor and report status on webui..
We are looking for a developer with experience in
SQL, C# and web development with charting functions.
Will provide a detailed design document once candidate is selected.
We will provide the database script to selected candidate along with winform snippet.Budget: $150
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        .NET Framework,                     C#,                     HTML5,                     Microsoft SQL CE            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 07:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>PHP-WordPress and Database(MySQL) Developer needed for Long Term - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/PHP-WordPress-and-Database-MySQL-Developer-needed-for-Long-Term_%7E01bacbf803c68a3469?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi Freelancers,
We&amp;#039;re looking for an experienced PHP back-end developer having expertise in PHP, MYSQL and PHP based frameworks/CMS like CodeIgnitor, WordPress etc to focus on developing web project and mobile projects. I am looking for someone who has good hands on experience in following skills and can play a role of the Individual contributor and team player both:
- PHP (Must Have)
- MY SQL (Must Have)
- WORDPRESS (Must Have)
- REST APIs using core PHP, Codeignitor, and WP (Must Have)
- CODEIGNITOR (Must Have)
- CMS (Must Have)
- AJAX (Must Have)
- JAVASCRIPT (Good to have)
- HTML/CSS (Good to have)
=&amp;amp;gt;Minimum technical requirements:
* Ability to handle DB and create Rest Apis in PHP using industry standards and clean code
* Expertise in Wordpress and custom PHP development
* Experience handling high-end Database and queries.
* Expertise in Mysql.
* Experience in creating database Architecture.
* Have knowledge of GIT
=&amp;amp;gt;Generic requirement, expectation &amp;amp;amp; commitments:
- We are expecting a minimum 1 Year work commitment from freelancer.
- We are Flexible with timings, just work should not get affected.
- Good communication skills.
- Should be punctual, honest and should take ownership.
- This will be an ongoing job and amount proposed in this job post will be paid every month.
- We expect the freelancer to work for a nearly of 5 to 6 hours on daily basis, though we are mostly concerned about the quality of work, timelines and positive attitude of the freelancer, so this is up to you how soon you can finish the job.
Please write &amp;#039;&amp;#039;I am willing to work&amp;amp;quot; on the top of your application to get considered. No Agencies please, we only want to work with a freelancer.
I am looking for an experienced developer who has a good eye for the web design and development who can provide solutions wherever required. You should be willing to showcase your skills and proof that you are the genuine developer and now just some guy who copy-paste templates and deliver and are available for the interview and a simple PHP test to validate your skills. 
I look forward to listen from you and work with you soon.
ThanksBudget: $250
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        API Development,                     CodeIgniter,                     CSS,                     Database Design,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     MySQL Programming,                     PHP,                     WordPress            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 07:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Python code to upload data from Excel to MS SQL (follow-up: build Django app) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Python-code-upload-data-from-Excel-SQL-follow-build-Django-app_%7E01fb77dead53fc50b6?source=rss</link>
    <description>**Caveats &amp;ndash; please read first**
1.	Although this project is narrowly focused around one task, what you build here will be part of a full-blown web application with which we&amp;#039;ll also need help. And we&amp;#039;d like to keep working with the same person or team all the way. For this reason, in addition to qualifications determined by this project, we need someone with demonstrated success developing Django apps working with MS SQL server on AWS. The app will be fairly basic, for internal use only, and we&amp;#039;ll make it as easy as possible to develop it, but nonetheless we need someone who did it before.
2.	Once deployed, this web app will be a mission-critical component of our business, and so, in a way, will be person who built it. For this reason, continuity is very important. Ideally, we&amp;#039;d prefer a team. An individual freelancer will be considered if he has at least 3 years&amp;#039; worth of consistent (full-time) experience and reasonable expectation of availability in the future (e.g. we don&amp;rsquo;t need a current student who will graduate and get a full-time job in 6 months).
**Specification**
We enter financial data into Excel (3-4 years&amp;#039; worth of quarterly data for&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;~130 metrics for ~1000 companies) and need a script which will upload it to MS SQL DB. &amp;amp;quot;Metric&amp;amp;quot; refers to a financial metric such as revenue, total debt etc., a scalar value with 2 decimal places. Excel file has metrics in rows and quarters in columns. Quarters are strings (e.g. &amp;amp;quot;Sep&amp;#039;18&amp;amp;quot;) with no datetime characteristics and are not aligned for all companies (most companies report Mar, Jun, Sep, Dec, others can do Jan, Apr, Jul, Oct). DB is already built, with schema matching Excel sheets but transposed, i.e. DB has metrics in columns, and every quarter will be a row. You will be able to tweak DB schema and interface, if needed. DB will be on AWS.
The reason we need a custom script, as opposed to using off-the-shelf SQL functionality, is that we need to add some conflict-resolution logic. Roughly speaking, once the data is uploaded from Excel, every time we try to change it, this system, let&amp;#039;s call it &amp;amp;quot;bridge&amp;amp;quot;, should throw a warning and require the user to enter a comment as to why the change is made. Two examples help clarify this:
Normal scenario: company A reports quarterly financial results, we create a new *column* in Excel and manually type in about 20 metrics, and the bridge uploads this first batch. This creates a new *row* in DB with new unique ID (say ID 1). Usually within a week or so, the company files full report with ~130 metrics, and our data provider fills them in the same Excel book (fully populating the column which we manually created a week before). This is the second, and almost always, final, upload &amp;ndash; with initial 20 metrics potentially overwritten and new ~110 ones added. When this second batch gets pushed to DB, it creates a new row (say ID = 2), and row with ID1 gets deactivated (via a boolean field). Since time delta between row 2 and row 1 does not exceed threshold of say 10 days, the bridge simply pushes up the data without regard to existing values.
Exception scenario: while researching company B, we find out that it had made an acquisition 5 months ago, such that its financial condition is affected, so we need to adjust historical data for the company. In Excel, we change 10 metrics for each of the most recent and previous 4 quarters. Since time delta for at least one of target columns exceeds threshold, the bridge shows an error and requires the user to enter a comment. The bridge creates 5 new rows, deactivates 5 old ones (via boolean field) and adds user comment to the deactivated rows. Note that all conflicts pertaining to the same ticker within the same time period (all changes to Q1&amp;#039;18, for example), will be collapsed into one warning and comment.
The bridge works one way &amp;ndash; only upload.
If more information is needed, don&amp;#039;t hesitate to ask.
**Deliverables**
A Python class (compatible with 3.6), with complete docstrings and with full test coverage (pytest).Budget: $600
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        AWS CodeDeploy,                     Django,                     Microsoft SQL Server Programming,                     Python            click to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>iOS - Swift 4 Developer (Speciality in UI / UX and Animations) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/iOS-Swift-Developer-Speciality-and-Animations_%7E01511e55695b9398e1?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi there,
We are looking for 4 days of development work (Approx. 32-35 hours) for an expert iOS developer to bring an existing platform&amp;#039;s interface closer to our original Sketch designs and professional UI/UX expectations.
Aspects we are looking for:
&amp;ndash; You&amp;rsquo;re a full-stack iOS development pro and have worked with Swift, Objective-C, Foundation, UIKit, XCTest, Core Animation, Core Data and Quartz Core 
&amp;ndash; You have a deep understanding of both MVC and alternative architectural UI design patterns 
&amp;ndash; You have worked with automation tools such as Jenkins and Fastline 
&amp;ndash; You have a strong understanding of how to design and interact with RESTful APIs and have experience developing backend APIs 
&amp;ndash; You have worked with SQL, writing custom queries and designing schemas 
What will you be working on:
1. UI Improvement - Pixel perfect alignment and scalability across new device resolutions iPhone XS and XS Max
2. UX Animations - We want to replace our existing default push transitions on iOS with something more bespoke, think of subtle fade in transitions for images, gestures which respond proactively to your touch, loading animations for cards and content, button presses and slide transitions.
See these examples of what we are looking for: 
https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/0*Xae3CInVMX60WWCS.gif
https://cdn-images-1.medium.com/max/1600/0*uaLSpSpp5DDgNLgH.gif
3. Minor Bugfixes and improvements to usability
Please share any Git repositories which show of your skills. After a short coding test &amp;amp;amp; interview, we would have a run through of our Trello board containing which tasks are achievable in the timeframe.
Salary expectations:
 We will pay your standard hourly rate for this short-term project
 - Also, a sizeable bonus will be provided as an extra incentive if all tasks are completed in the time period
If impressed by your performance, we may consider extending the project timeframe.
Kind regards,
ArjunPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Apple programming languages:Swift            Platforms:iOS            Devices:Phone            App features:In-App Purchases,         User Profile Creation,         Chat and Messaging,         Camera or Video,         Map Integration,         Location,         User Authentication,         Social Media Account Integration,         In-App Search            
Other Skills:        Swift            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch file - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-file_%7E01a23168804e3226f7?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;batch file as follows;
Move all sub folders in folder
I want to make sure that when it moves it. It&amp;rsquo;s also deleting the files from the original folder.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Budget: $40
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 16:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Software Development - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Software-Development_%7E01919b7450d6e91de9?source=rss</link>
    <description>West LONDON - Local /London based a MUST!
ASP.NET skills - Minimum version 4. Primarily C# knowledge.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;OO within N-Tier architecture, Restful Web services. Knowledge of MVC and MVC Mobile. 
SQL Server skills - version, 2008/16. Ability to design, implement and manage databases in SQL Server. Excellent T-SQL skills i.e. the ability to write efficient stored procedures and handle large datasets, Triggers and XML manipulation.
CSS/HTML - A good working knowledge and understanding of CSS and XHTML 
from a design implementation point of view i.e. the ability to replicate modern/accessible designs as provided by the design team using ASP.NET controls.
jQuery and JavaScript - A good working knowledge and understanding of jQuery, jQuery UI, jQuery Ajax, creation of plugins, OO JavaScript and jQuery-JavaScript UI manipulation, JSON manipulation and data transfer between Ajax calls.
upgrade existing of the web site
add new functionality - we will discuss ,
add Content management system.
add easy payment system.
add complete pharmacy shopping basketPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        ASP.NET,                     ASP.NET MVC,                     C++,                     Content Management System,                     HTML,                     Java,                     jQuery,                     Microsoft SQL Server Programming            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 11:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>AutoCAD 17, LISP, Batch Script Coder - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/AutoCAD-LISP-Batch-Script-Coder_%7E0172d9db80a9cca487?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need some assistance updating a LISP and batch script to automate an AutoCAD job to convert DWG to DWF.
I have some sample scripts and screenshots to demonstrate what the script needs to accomplish.
One script is a .kix and another is a batch script.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Engineering &amp;amp; Architecture &amp;gt; 3D Modeling &amp;amp; CAD
Skills:        AutoCAD,                     AutoLISP,                     Automation,                     Lisp,                     Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities,                     VBScript            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 03:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Business Analyst / Scrum Master (5+ years experience only) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Business-Analyst-Scrum-Master-years-experience-only_%7E01df47326dbd515d10?source=rss</link>
    <description>Extensive experience in gathering, analyzing, documenting and managing business and user requirements (both functional and non-functional) and identifying potential solutions for the business and providing input to issues or risks (through solid knowledge of the business and user requirements).
â— Facilitated JAD sessions, meetings, conference calls, questionnaires, storyboard presentations &amp;amp;amp; workshops with Business Users and Subject Matter Experts (SME) for business and technical requirements gathering.
â— Experience in leveraging technical knowledge &amp;amp;amp; business acumen to ensure a mutual understanding of processes and applications with business relationship managers, technology teams and business partners at management and end user levels.
â— Practical knowledge of SDLC methodologies like Waterfall, Iterative and Agile software development.
â— As a scrum-master, conduct daily standup meetings, remove impediments of the development team, help the product manager create and manage product backlogs. Facilitated Sprint Planning, Daily Standups, Sprint Reviews and Sprint Retrospectives.
â— Proficiency in writing Business Requirement Document (BRD), Functional Requirement Document (FRD) and
Use Case Specifications, Requirement Traceability Matrix (RTM), process flows, operational support documentation and archival of all related project documentation.
â— Demonstrated clear capability to document the ASIS, TOBE process flows. Conducted full analytics collaboratively to identify and provide solutions for gaps and abnormal work flows.
â— Experience in developing the required user acceptance test (UAT) scripts, Test Cases and Test Plans. Facilitated User Acceptance Testing, tracked deviations and analyzed bugs.
â— Developed Use Case, activity diagrams and class diagrams with UML for new product functionality. Created user stories to business objectives and the product vision throughout the sprint to ensure it&amp;#039;s actually been delivered as imagined.
â— Experience is conducting GAP analysis, SWOT analysis and development of training materials and facilitation of end user training sessions.
â— Proven active involvement in Post Production Validation and Production Support.
â— Strong expertise in Data analysis, Data mapping, and development of Databases for business applications in Data warehouse environments using ETL tool Informatica.
â— Familiar with Tableau, Microsoft power BI and Excel for data visualization and analytic needs of large sets of data.
â— Proficiency in SQL including ability to independently read and write queries
â— Expertise in performance analysis and tuning using various debugging tools like run time analysis and sql trace.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; QA &amp;amp; Testing
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 02:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Golang Back-End Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Golang-Back-End-Developer_%7E01378b9e97e678f85f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am seeking a talented Senior Full Stack Software Engineer with a demonstrated passion for software development and problem solving. This is an exciting opportunity for a team player who wants to have an immediate impact on the development of an emerging cybersecurity product.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The prospective candidate will work in our Solutions Division with a dynamic team in our Washington, D.C. office.
Responsibilities
A successful Senior Software Engineer will be expected to:
Work with a modern microservices architecture using Golang to create and deploy enterprise grade software solutions using Concourse CI/CD pipeline
Write advanced SQL queries and stored procedures
Serve as a Senior developer and a work as part of a team using Agile development methodologies
Actively participate in the development of user story creation and sprint planning 
Build automation services that integrate with 3rd party APIs and software
Interact with customers and development team to gather and define requirements
Develop and maintain software technical documentation to assist with software maintenance and upgrades
Ensure use of secure coding best practices and DevSecOps
Qualifications
Bachelors degree in Computer Science or equivalent discipline from an accredited university with a minimum three (3) years backend development experience. Equivalent experience can be used in lieu of education
Understanding of microservice architectures or core distributed systems principles, and exposure to Amazon Web Services (AWS) with core services (EC2, VPC, VPN, RDS, etc.) required
Extensive knowledge working with complex data sets and developing PostgreSQL queries
Demonstrated ability of strong analysis and problem-solving skills required
Extensive experience using Linux and MacOS as development environments required
Excellent communication skills, both written and oralPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        Go,                     Golang            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 01:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Intermediate PHP Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Intermediate-PHP-Developer_%7E014921c15a1ff56609?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for passionate, talented and innovative developer to join our small startup but growing team to work on our new eCard platform. We are focused on reducing consumption of paper and adopt an environmental friendly approach, yet providing a powerful fully customized, corporately branded eCards.
We always encourage new talent so fresh graduates and junior developers are welcome to apply.
Preferred Experience:
&amp;bull;	We are looking for an intermediate PHP developer for a full-time contract. 
&amp;bull;	Must have strong experience and proficiency in Microsoft SQL.
&amp;bull;	Strong knowledge with API integration.
&amp;bull;	Strong, working knowledge of PHP, CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX, HTML5 and JavaScript technologies.
&amp;bull;	Basic networking knowledge include TCP/IP, DNS and understanding of web-related protocols such as HTTP, HTTPS and FTP and sFTP.
&amp;bull;	Experience in working with Zebra printer drivers is an asset.
Responsibilities and Duties:
&amp;bull;	Develop new features.
&amp;bull;	Explore and implement latest technologies for email delivery and system integration.
&amp;bull;	Accurately estimating programming hours needed to complete project requirements.
&amp;bull;	Strong database skills and can work with and troubleshoot complex SQL queries
&amp;bull;	Adhere to development KPI; Design, build, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable code. Strong knowledge of general algorithms, design patterns and good coding practices.
&amp;bull;	Improve performance and user experience
&amp;bull;	Maintain existing code and fix bugs
&amp;bull;	Ability to work on project independentlyPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web &amp;amp; Mobile Design
Skills:        CSS,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     PHP,                     SQL            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Microsoft Dynamic CRM and Web services Development/Customization. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Microsoft-Dynamic-CRM-and-Web-services-Development-Customization_%7E01beab116fa3becbff?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;#039;d like to invite you to apply to my job. Please review this job post and apply if you&amp;#039;re available.
We are looking for a few developers with high proficiency in Microsoft Dynamic CRM and web services. using MS SQL and other related technologies. Project entails automated updating of external Microsoft Agile Servers, using MS Dynamic CRM, running multiple simultaneous queries and creating tables on external servers. 
Candidate must show expert knowledge of the project, be quick to learn and adapt to our custom developmentvenvironment, and must be a great/dedicated problem solver.
Work could become long-term if the candidate show expertise.
Thank you, 
Raymond BrownPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Microsoft Azure App Services,                     Database Administration,                     Database Management,                     Microsoft Dynamics CRM,                     SQL,                     Web Services Development,                     Web Testing            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Assistant - Production Design Set Up - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Assistant-Production-Design-Set_%7E0146ed0c81659fe47a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Job Description for Production Design Set Up Assistant-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We are looking for someone who can review orders and then place artwork files on a production template that matches up with these orders.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This set up process is done in photoshop with scripts and actions and we will provide the steps on how to do this.
The files will be available in batch folders to be set up on the template. Since the files are photos, graphic images, or stylized text the person needs to have some graphic design experience to be able to visualize and scale and/or edit the images for printing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This job is basically order set up with some image editing applied when needed and will be an ongoing job.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The hours at the beginning will vary depending on the number of orders we receive and will increase during the holiday season.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We are looking for someone who is interested in building a working relationship with our US based design team with a turnaround time of 12 hours for us to receive the completed files.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The order set up is a seasonal business, so the demand will increase substantially October through December.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Requirements-
Photoshop CC using scripts and actions, clipping images, and editing images when needed.
Basic photo editing skills - brightness, contrast, and color balance 
Graphic design experience
Fluent in English and complete understanding of English grammar
Attention to detail is a must
Ability to follow written directions and a quick learnerPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Illustrator,                     Adobe Photoshop,                     Graphic Design,                     Photo Editing,                     Print Layout Design            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Business Intelligence Analyst - (Tableau and MySQL) MUST BE US CITIZEN - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Business-Intelligence-Analyst-Tableau-and-MySQL-MUST-CITIZEN_%7E01e25d8b2ae24b6557?source=rss</link>
    <description>1099 CONTRACTOR (part-time hours for approximately 6 months)
Here is the opportunity at the Washington DC Navy Yard:
Position Description: Business Intelligence (BI) Analyst (Mid-Level)
Ridgewood is actively seeking a Mid-Level Business Intelligence (BI) Analyst, to join our team at our Washington DC location. The analyst will provide analytical consultation and support to a team developing new capabilities for our analytical tools and services.
The Mid-Level Business Intelligence (BI) Analyst will be responsible for working with Ridgewood customers to capture BI enhancement requirements, identifying, gathering, developing and maintaining existing data feeds. The analyst will also be responsible for troubleshooting data quality related issues and coordinating with Program and Business Analysts to formulate and implement appropriate courses of action. The position requires the ability to analyze data, generate reports, and provide guidance to other BI analysts to ensure accuracy and timeliness of deliverables. The analyst will lead efforts focused on driving consistency, quality improvements and enhancements throughout the data, analytics, and reporting areas.
Proficiency Qualifications 
3+ years of experience in the following areas:
Understanding customer needs and converting these needs in to clear, concise and verifiable requirements.
Identifying and analyzing business intelligence data for the purposes of improving customer profits and efficiencies.
Tableau
&amp;bull; Transforming complex business requirements into data visualizations using Tableau Desktop and 
Tableau Server
&amp;bull; Verification and validation of Tableau Reports
&amp;bull; Knowledge of Data Joining, Blending and Cross Data Joins SQL
&amp;bull; Writing Complex SQL Queries using MySQL and Microsoft SQL Server
&amp;bull; Database Analysis, Design, Development and Support
&amp;bull; Knowledge of Relational Data architecture and RDBMS Concepts
Essential Functions
Work with customers to collect data from disparate sources and deliver accurate analysis and interpretation of that data
Work with large datasets in various formats and perform data integrity/QA/reconciliation
Provide analytical and data support to research team for setting up research studies (e.g. analyzing user segments, pulling lists for surveys and qualitative user tests, etc.).
Build and maintain analytics data pipelines.
Prepare complex deliverables using analytical tools (e.g., Tableau) in a consistent and reusable format
Perform other duties as assigned by the Accounts or Product Manager
Meet routine deadlines and work schedules as well as timely and accurate completion of special projects and any other duties as assigned
Proven track record and enthusiasm for complex problem solving and analysis, including working with large data sets.
Quantitative mindset, comfortable and proficient with basic statistical analyses.
Ability to communicate complex analytical insights in a simple, concise manner and to build strong relationships with marketing and product teams to effectively convert insights into action.
Comfortable and confident working as part of a fast-paced, self-directed, dynamic team.
Help empower data-driven product and marketing efforts.
&amp;middot; Strong written and Verbal Communication Skills.
Knowledge, Skills, and Experience
Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in relevant field, 4+ years&amp;rsquo; data analysis experience required
Demonstrated exceptional analytical and problem-solving skills with strong attention to detail
Ability to work independently in a fast-paced environment
Expert knowledge of MS-SQL and Excel functions required
Experience with RDBMS
Business analysis and Government Acquisition experience a plus
Excellent communications skills and strong commitment to delivering the highest level of service
Demonstrated knowledge of automated business processes, scripting experience a plus
Security Requirements
** Must be able to obtain and maintain a Secret Clearance. **
Active Clearance preferred.
(Applicants selected will be subject to a government security investigation and must meet eligibility requirements for access to classified information)
Thanks,
Troy Preston
Ridgewood Technology Partners, LLC
703.860.4795 x103
www.ridgewoodpartners.comPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        iDashboards,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Office 365,                     MySQL Administration,                     MySQL Programming,                     SAS,                     SQL Programming,                     Tableau Software            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 18:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>On Demand DBA Services needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Demand-DBA-Services-needed_%7E0112ad120bc9dd0ef6?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;#039;m looking for an experienced DBA.
We have CSV files with more than 20 Million rows which we need imported into a database structure. 
On a nearly daily basis we will have different queries we need run against the database to extract specific segments which we will need help with on an ongoing basis.
Overall updates will be made to this database on a monthly basis, and these changes will need to be managed. Duplicates will need to be handled and managed among other common data challenges.
Data will need to be convered into hashed or MD5 format.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Microsoft SQL Server Administration,                     MySQL Administration,                     MySQL Programming,                     SQL,                     SQL Programming,                     SQLite Administration,                     SQLite Programming            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 15:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need Data Polling for dynamic Bootstrap dashboard - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-Data-Polling-for-dynamic-Bootstrap-dashboard_%7E01dc71990096a30cdb?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are working on a Bootstrap dashboard template and need to replace the static html with data coming from our DB (MSSQL). Currently it uses RESTapi.
Data is refreshing every 1-2 seconds and we need a solution using long-polling / signalR etc.
There will be several dynamic pages of that dashboard, including tables, charts, KPIs and maybe more.
We provide all SQL queries/WebAPI.
No need for graphic design. This is a ready template customized by our Graphic Designer.
Success delivery will gain more projects.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Bootstrap,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     Performance Tuning,                     React.js,                     SignalR,                     Websockets            Country: Israelclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 12:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Full time Php Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Full-time-Php-Developer_%7E01a1d23713e25eecc8?source=rss</link>
    <description>PHP Developer 
No. of Vacancies: 02 
Experience: 1-2+ years
Salary: (depend on expertise)
JOB BRIEF...
We are looking for a PHP Developer responsible for managing back-end services and the interchange of data between the server and the users. Your primary focus will be the development of all server-side logic, definition and maintenance of the central database, and ensuring high performance and responsiveness to requests from the front-end. You will also be responsible for integrating the front-end elements built by your co-workers into the application. Therefore, a basic understanding of front-end technologies is necessary as well.
YOUR MISSION&amp;hellip;
# Integration of user-facing elements developed by front-end developers
# Build efficient, testable, and reusable PHP modules
# Solve complex performance problems and architectural challenges
# Integration of data storage solutions
SUPERPOWERS YOU&amp;#039;LL NEED...
# Strong knowledge of PHP web frameworks {â€‹â€‹{â€‹such as Laravel, Wordpress, Magento Yii, etc depending on your technology stack}â€‹â€‹}â€‹
# Understanding the fully synchronous behavior of PHP
# Understanding of MVC design patterns
# Basic understanding of front-end technologies, such as JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS3
Knowledge of object-oriented PHP programming
# Understanding accessibility and security compliance {â€‹â€‹{â€‹Depending on the specific project}â€‹â€‹}â€‹
# Strong knowledge of the common PHP or web server exploits and their solutions
# Understanding fundamental design principles behind a scalable application
# User authentication and authorization between multiple systems, servers, and environments
# Integration of multiple data sources and databases into one system
# Familiarity with limitations of PHP as a platform and its workarounds
# Creating database schemas that represent and support business processes
# Familiarity with SQL/NoSQL databases and their declarative query languages
# Proficient understanding of code versioning tools, such as Git
EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION...
There is no binding in educational qualification, we care about skill and will.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        AngularJS,                     CodeIgniter,                     HTML5,                     jQuery,                     Laravel Framework,                     PHP,                     Shopify,                     Web Design,                     Website Development,                     WordPress            Country: Netherlandsclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data engineer wanted to write technical blog posts: Kafka/Kinesis, Hadoop, AWS, Athena/Presto - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-engineer-wanted-write-technical-blog-posts-Kafka-Kinesis-Hadoop-AWS-Athena-Presto_%7E015c09c7a834246893?source=rss</link>
    <description>We&amp;#039;re a big data company that&amp;#039;s looking to level up the content we produce. We&amp;#039;re looking for an engineer / DBA / software architect who:
- Has deep knowledge and experience with big data tools and architectures
- Can present this knowledge in a compelling fashion by writing articles and creating diagrams
The job will be to write educational content such as best practices guides and tool comparisons on technical aspects of working with big data, including: Lambda architecture, working with Apache Kafka, ETL tools, AWS/Azure ecosystem (esp. Kinesis, Athena, S3), Hadoop ecosystem (Spark, MapReduce), real-time databases (Cassandra, Redis, DynamoDB).
Examples of the type of content we&amp;#039;d like to see:
https://engineering.depop.com/data-swamp-to-data-lake-on-aws-part-2-12b2bf80ba7a
https://medium.com/teads-engineering/spark-performance-tuning-from-the-trenches-7cbde521cf60
https://blog.timescale.com/sql-vs-flux-influxdb-query-language-time-series-database-290977a01a8a
Our goal is to produce materials that a software engineer with 5-10 years of experience would find helpful and engaging. This means that the technical skills are required and non-negotiable - we&amp;#039;re looking to hire engineers, not technical/content writers, and are willing to pay accordingly.
Job has the potential to turn into long-term collaboration.Budget: $400
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        Big Data,                     Data Engineering,                     Data Science,                     Distributed Computing,                     Hadoop,                     Software Architecture            Country: Israelclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 07:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior WordPress Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-WordPress-Developer_%7E0196ec402888758d00?source=rss</link>
    <description>PLEASE ONLY SERIOUS DEVELOPERS - WE WANT THE BEST
We are looking for a Senior WordPress Developer with many years of experience in complex areas.
MUST know how to work with GIT, if you don not know PLEASE DO NOT BOTHER TO APPLY. A
Code needs to be CLEAN and optimize - our Senior Devs will verify code!
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL
- Front-end technologies, including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery
- CSS preprocessors like Sass or LESS
- SQL experience, including complex query writing and database design
- Backend payment processing
- Git repository like GitHub or GitLab
- Libraries like jQuery for additional interactivity
- Experience with plugins and create custom plugins if needed
- API integrations
- Working with Adobe XD, Sketch, Adobe PSD and Zeplin
- Amazon and Digital Ocean Cloud Server
- PM tools like Trello, Asana, Jira
Only amazing devs that can show examples of work
Can create amazing interactive websites in WP
Well motivated, they can work fast, team players
Agency experience even better
Good EnglishPosted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        CSS,                     CSS3,                     HTML,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     jQuery,                     MySQL Administration,                     PHP,                     Web Design,                     Website Development,                     Woocommerce,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>MYSQL time based optimization | Joining phone dates between tables on # &amp;amp;amp; most recent occurrence. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/MYSQL-time-based-optimization-Joining-phone-dates-between-tables-amp-most-recent-occurrence_%7E0132bcbeb4402da6e6?source=rss</link>
    <description>This job is to transform the function of the below query into one that will execute quickly as our current logic is far to slow, (has an overall 24 + hr run time). Please note that the respective columns have already been indexed.
The size of our tables are as follows; 
Table 1 - 300,000 rows 
Table 2 - 15,000 rows
This query matches phone call dates between two tables based on the phone number uid along with closest proceeding date. The first table (Phone Call Table 1) phone calls are outbound marketing phone calls made while the phone calls from the second table (Phone Call Table 2) contain the same phone number but are in the context of inbound calls made to numbers displayed within our marketing campaigns. The logic matches the most recent outbound phone calls to the inbound phone call table based on those respective times and UID
The query is as follows;
SELECT `Phone Number 2`, `Time of Call` FROM `Phone Call Table 2` 
JOIN 
`Phone Call Table 1` 
ON `Phone Call Table 1`.`Phone_Call_Start_1` = 
(SELECT MAX(`Phone_Call_Start_1`) 
FROM `Phone Call Table 1` 
WHERE `Phone_Call_Start_1` &amp;amp;lt; `Phone Call Table 2`.`Phone_Call_Start_2` 
AND `Phone Number 1` = `Phone Number 2` 
) ;Budget: $50
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        MySQL Administration,                     SQL            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 23:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Sr. iOS Developer with bug-fix expertise - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/iOS-Developer-with-bug-fix-expertise_%7E01e96aad4372966244?source=rss</link>
    <description>We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a seasoned iOS Developer. 
Our app has all new code written in Swift and moving away from the traditional MVC architecture to a more clean architecture which will enable us to increase the testability of our code and help us maintain the excellent stability that our app enjoys. 
Need the following skills effort:
Full-stack iOS development including Swift, Objective-C, Foundation, UIKit, XCTest, Core Animation
Experience developing with payment based applications, working with payment methods
Deep understanding of both MVC and alternative architectural UI design patterns
Test driven development (TDD)
Interact with RESTful APIs
Backend APIs
Experience working with SQL queries
Independent thought process and expression to teamBudget: $100
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Apple programming languages:Swift,         Objective-C            Platforms:iOS            Databases:MongoDB,         MySQL            Devices:Phone            App features:In-App Purchases,         User Authentication,         Augmented Reality,         Social Media Account Integration            
Other Skills:        Apple Xcode,                     iOS Development,                     iPad App Development,                     iPhone App Development,                     JavaScript,                     Mobile App Development,                     Objective-C,                     PHP,                     Swift            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 21:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Lambda_DynamoDB - Parsing 100 web pages/sec - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Lambda_DynamoDB-Parsing-100-web-pages-sec_%7E018a85a248083b00f5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi! Please read the below RFP carefully. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to include answers to most of the most popular questions
END RESULT: 
web-based solution that 
1.	parses batches of web pages (1000-2000&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;random domain/urls each) via AWS Lambda script
2.	loads all text from the web page into AWS DynamoDB at 100 pages/sec
3.	shows keyword count and stored page text preview and counts keywords in each of the pages behind the URL
The faster the better. Not using third party services that can be banned, stopped or restricted or which are paid (other than AWS).
FRONT END GUI: 
Page 1: 
Input fields
-	Field where a user pastes the list of URLs (1000-2000 at a time)
-	Field where user pastes a string of keywords&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(same for each URL)
Page 2: End result 
2 frame Page with 
Left Frame: a table, showing the parsing results featuring the following fields
-	URL that was parsed (clickable as link)
-	Title of the page behind the URL
-	Status of parsing: success, not-parsed &amp;ndash; Error, not-parsed timed out
Controls: URL.onMouseOver =Load Text To Right Frame From Dynamo AND highlight all words typed in the Keywords text field
Fields:
-	Text field where a string of keywords can be entered 
Right frame
-	Text stored from the page behind the URL
-	Keywords in that text highlighted with different colors (one per keyword)
Example of the URL list. See attached. Assume it can be a random set of any URLs
HOSTING ENVIRONMENT
Amazon AWS Lambda, Dynamo DB (S3 if needed)
USER ENVIRONMENT
This is a boutique solution for a small company. 2-6 users at a time doing several batches in parallel
Browser support: Firefox or Chrome
Mobile support - no
PROPOSAL REQUIREMENTS
Please provide with your answer
- your full fee and time for completion including 
a) development debugging and Q&amp;amp;amp;A. 
b) implementation and support for a couple of weeks on my hosting platform. (Can write it on your premises, but then show it works on my server). Server comes &amp;ldquo;clean&amp;rdquo;, so if you want to the tool to run on some specific libraries or modules &amp;ndash; expect to bring them on with you.
- proposed solution architecture &amp;ndash; language, libraries, etc&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(VB.NET developers are welcome, but optional)
- your experience in similar tasks. Specifically with Amazon EC2 and Windows based hosting environment
- your resume with qualifications: web development tenure in years, languages fluent in, formal education, etc.
COLLABORATION REQUIREMENTS
Start: At the start of the project please be ready to provide a high-level workplan with key milestones and deadlines and be ready to meet them
Mid: if we agree that delivery takes more than one day - provide progress update (all work in progress materials) at the end of each day
End: put it on my server yourself, configure, debug and start, then support for a couple of weeks
(not just send file with the Lambda code)
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY REQUIREMENTS
End product should include full source code of the project
By agreeing to deliver this project you agree to give up all the intellectual property rights for the end product of your work within this project
Happy to answer questions that are not covered above
Deadlines: fee and deadline is not negotiable after contract signing. Be careful with committing to the deadline. If we agree on a deadline and you do not deliver full scope - you do not get paid!Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        AWS Lambda,                     Python,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 07:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer needed for an application 1) maintain a database 2)generate files in the required format - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developer-needed-for-application-maintain-database-generate-files-the-required-format_%7E0197271ef8f3999486?source=rss</link>
    <description>Background:
1.	Our accounting system (Xero) cannot generate Zengin file (banking payment file, containing Japanese characters) which can be uploaded to Japanese online banking system for batch payments. 
2.	Xero can generate payment list in excel file, but the list doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain all information required for Zengin file. (sample export from Xero uploaded)
3.	We would like to develop an application to convert payment list from Xero to Zengin format. (sample Zengin file uploaded)
Purposes of the application: 
1)	Maintain vendor bank account information for each client
2)	Generate standard Zengin file with payment list from Xero and vendor list 
Function / Workflow
- Maintain vendor bank account information
ïƒ˜	Review/export vendor list for each client with details
ïƒ˜	Manually add / revise / delete vendor for each client
ïƒ˜	Import vendor list (xlsx, csv, etc.) to the application (run error checking on the file before importing)
- Generate standard Zengin file
1)	Upload Xero data (payment amount and identifier) to the application
2)	Map vendor bank information to each transaction using an identifier
3)	Generate standard Zengin file (csv file) which can be exported from the application.
Requirements:
1)	English interface
2)	The application should be able to handle Japanese Katakana (half-width)
3)	The application can transfer small ãƒ¤ã€ãƒ¦ã€ãƒ¨, etc. to big ones (bank requirements) and remove any full-width blanks between characters when generating Zengin file.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Country: Japanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 05:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Dev Ops Engineer position for workforce management platform with over 300,000 daily users - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Dev-Ops-Engineer-position-for-workforce-management-platform-with-over-300-000-daily-users_%7E01eff5ef9db15a0b51?source=rss</link>
    <description>Level: Intermediate
Technologies: 
&amp;bull;	Experience or working knowledge in configuring and maintaining CI servers 
(preferably Jenkins)
&amp;bull;	Hands-on experience in configuring and working with Windows Server
&amp;bull;	Hands-on experience with Windows installers
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of scripting (Windows batch scripting, Powershell etc.)
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of container technologies like Docker
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of using &amp;amp;amp; integrating versioning systems like Git, BitBucket, SVN etc.
(Preferably also RoundTable SCM versioning system)
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of 3-tier architecture, incl. Relational databases and application servers (webservices and webportals, IIS/Tomcat, windows services) 
&amp;bull;	Configuration management knowledge (Chef, Ansible, Terraform etc.)
&amp;bull;	Knowledge about container management tools like Rancher or Kubernetes
Start date: ASAP 
Duration: Current tasks are estimated at 200 - 300 hours; could grow into a much longer engagement. This will depend on delivery and client satisfaction.
Project description and details:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;existing workforce management platform with over 300,000 daily users 
&amp;bull;	Extend continuous integration architecture based on Jenkins
&amp;bull;	Automate code checking actions in repositories like bitbucket to integrate with test automation efforts and updating task mgmt system (JIRA)
&amp;bull;	Automate deployments into a MS Windows server / Docker setup 
&amp;bull;	Manage relevant notifications via Jenkins upon various events
&amp;bull;	Modernize product installers
Work allocation: F/T = 40 hours/week 
Work location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working with the team in our office in Bucuresti is preferable.
However, remote work is acceptable. Person will need to be willing to travel to Bucuresti for ramp up and occasionally for team meetings.
Team location and setup: English speaking mixed team in Denmark and Bucuresti.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Country: Romaniaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 11:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Spring Batch and Java based  Back-End Utility - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Spring-Batch-and-Java-based-Back-End-Utility_%7E01ff2c8513a55145f8?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a very small Java/Spring Batch based utility that can read .csv and .xml files from an input directory and perform 2 step validation on the data read from the .CSV and XML and finally write the records to a report into an output directory. Those records that fail the validation only should go into the output report. Need unit tests and production level coding with clean comment and formatting.
Prefer using latest technologies like: Spring batch for csv processing, Jackson for xml, Java8 features.Budget: $60
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        J2EE,                     Java,                     Spring Framework            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>(JS/React) SVG exporter for Illustrator that lives in the browser - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/React-SVG-exporter-for-Illustrator-that-lives-the-browser_%7E01a969c72539a88a5e?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need help to build an awesome export script for Illustrator. Mission is to generate optimized and clean SVG with one click, and show it as a gallery in HTML. For Mac.
1.) Saves out all artboards as SVGs with names. The extension needs one button &amp;amp;quot;Export&amp;amp;quot;.
2.) Batch renames the filenames (Illustrator adds an annoying prefix)
3.) From there the browser opens with a preloader. We optimize SVG code using SVGOMG service.
https://jakearchibald.github.io/svgomg/
https://github.com/svg/svgo/blob/master/docs/how-it-works/en.md
4.) In the same browser window and when done processing, we show a gallery layout in HTML of all the exported SVGs, with buttons to download/show code.
5.) The gallery will have a button to download the whole set.Budget: $300
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        CSS,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript            Country: Swedenclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 12:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Murex Application Developer (Banking Industry) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Murex-Application-Developer-Banking-Industry_%7E015d474f6db066732d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Responsible for Design, installation, implementation, application management and support of new Treasury solution for Murex.
&amp;bull;	Knowledge in Murex V3.1 module, experience in Murex V3.1 support &amp;amp;amp; development. 
&amp;bull;	Provide technical support, implementation &amp;amp;amp; Infrastructure support
&amp;bull;	Design, develop and maintain configuration of application systems and services involving reports and interfaces
&amp;bull;	Analyses and design reports, interfaces and templates based on user&amp;rsquo;s requirement and conversion of existing reports/interface.
&amp;bull;	Investigate &amp;amp;amp; resolve application supports queries or problem in a timely and effective matter.
&amp;bull;	Familiar in dynamic table, data mart, horizontal field, feeder, MXML workflow.
&amp;bull;	Support EOD batch run
&amp;bull;	Minimum 4 years working experience as a programmer/analyst that covers system analysis, design, programming and software testing. 
&amp;bull;	Ability to do programming in Visual Basic, Java, Crystal Report &amp;amp;amp; SQL (ie ability to design/write and troubleshoot), UNIX Scripting.
&amp;bull;	Support users in any of testing (i.e. guidance info during SIT,UAT, etc.)
Immediate joiners and locally available in Kuala Lumpur, MalaysiaBudget: $5
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Mobile Development    Devices:Phone            
Country: Malaysiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch script for MULTIPAR parity files creation - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-script-for-MULTIPAR-parity-files-creation_%7E0159e241f5edaa9b07?source=rss</link>
    <description>3 batch .bat files containing automation script must be done. The goal is to recursively create parity files on all children folders using a program called multipar. Script must be done in batch .bat files runnable unantended on a windows machine. See complete requirement in attached file.Budget: $60
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        Bash Shell Scripting,                     Scripting            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>.NET Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/NET-Developer_%7E0126ba250973cc4057?source=rss</link>
    <description>Required Skills &amp;amp;amp; Experience
&amp;bull;	SQL
&amp;bull;	T-SQL
&amp;bull;	.NET (C#)
&amp;bull;	PowerShell
Responsibilities
&amp;bull;	Supporting a vendor application by creating, maintaining, and updating scheduled tasks, Windows Services, SQL scripts, PowerShell scripts, batch files, C# programs, and VB programs.
&amp;bull;	Utilize Windows Server 2008 R2 to check error logs and Event viewer, as well as install service packs and patches.
&amp;bull;	Make use of SQL Server Management Studio to view database tables, schedule SQL jobs, create SQL code files, and track database errors.
&amp;bull;	Create, maintain, and update custom reports via the use of SQL scripts, PowerShell scripts, and C# code. These reports are populated with new data every day and dispersed via EBO, email, or FTP.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        C#,                     Windows PowerShell,                     SQL,                     Transact-SQL            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch program for Whitepages API - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-program-for-Whitepages-API_%7E019066efe416ff8f36?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a simple windows based program which will loop through a list with names/city/state and for each entry make a REST API call to the whitepages API.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The program should take the JSON based responses and format them to return address for each input entry and then export the list of responses to a spreadsheet.
This can be done either with excel, VB, or any other technology which makes sense.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;#039;m looking for something very simple to perform only this one function.
Here&amp;#039;s a link to a thread on excel forum which contains an example spreadsheet that sort of does what is needed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;#039;m looking for something slightly more reliable and possibly faster.
http://www.excelforum.com/excel-programming-vba-macros/788072-loop-to-do-whitepages-api-calls.html
I also have a windows program that I can provide which provides an example of what is needed but no longer works perfectly after whitepages has changed the order of their response fields.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into Romanian - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-Romanian_%7E018a18548ef129da92?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into Romanian. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Two basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: Romanian ( bilingual is preferred: Romanian and English)
2. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to Romanian.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Film Dubbing,                     Music,                     Poetry,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English Romanian            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into French - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-French_%7E01c27961099f1c7b8c?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into French. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Three basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: French ( bilingual is preferred: French and English)
2. The translators should be French natives who can speak standard French.
3. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to French.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Christian Theology,                     Editing,                     Music,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English French            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Wanted:	Bada$$	Virtual Assistant	with	Real	Estate Experience - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Wanted-Bada-Virtual-Assistant-with-Real-Estate-Experience_%7E019a978fc00b5c4965?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m	a	looking	for	a	full-time	VA	to	help	with	my	real	estate	business.		
**	Responsibilities	Include	**	
Screening	buyer	&amp;amp;amp;	seller	leads	daily
Addressing,	stamping,	and	stuffing	batches	of	100	mailers	on	a	regular	basis
Running	comparable	sales	and	determining	value
Understanding	my	buying	criteria	&amp;amp;amp;	recommending	a	course	of	action
Receiving	inbound	calls	and	making	outbound	calls	(I&amp;rsquo;ll	provide	the	call	script)
Coordinating	paperwork	and	closings
**	Must	Have	**
Hawk-like	attention	to	detail
Dog-like	dependability
Ox-like	work	ethic
Cat-like	reflexes
Please	respond	with	your	availability,	samples	of	past	work,	and	favorite	&amp;lsquo;80s	movie.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Internet Research,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Burmese Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Burmese-Reading-Audio-Review_%7E01785ced4855cdb7dc?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are launching Burmese Christian Narration Project and hope to hire some excellent Burmese native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Burmese audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Burmese Yangon Standard Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Background Music: overall tone and the volume of the soundtrack need to be compatible with the related content, and quieten people&amp;rsquo;s heart to ponder over the words.
NOTE: we just accept Unicode Font (Myanmar 3).
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Audio Production,                     Burmese,                     English,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Translation English Burmese            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Civil Maps is Hiring for freelance consultant - DevOps Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Civil-Maps-Hiring-for-freelance-consultant-DevOps-Engineer_%7E019e79d6f1ec4273af?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi ,
We are Civil Maps .
Civil Maps, provider of 3D mapping technology for fully autonomous vehicles, has raised a $6.6 million seed funding round from Ford Motor Company, Motus Ventures, Wicklow Capital, StartX Stanford and Yahoo cofounder Jerry Yang&amp;rsquo;s AME Cloud Ventures.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; mission is to make it possible for fully autonomous vehicles (SAE Levels 4-5) to drive anywhere smoothly and safely. Through artificial intelligence and vehicle-based local processing, Civil Maps converts sensor data into meaningful map information built specifically to direct fully autonomous vehicles. The company will use the seed investment to accelerate product development and deployment with a number of leading automotive companies and technology partners.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; artificial intelligence software aggregates raw 3D data from LiDAR (high-resolution laser imaging), camera and other sensors onboard autonomous vehicles and organizes the information into machine-readable maps. The information is vastly more actionable information than today&amp;rsquo;s mapping systems and requires a fraction of the data storage and transmission for existing technologies. Thanks to this light data footprint, Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; spatial information is far less costly to transmit over cellular networks, enabling the company to more easily crowdsource, update and share road data in real time&amp;mdash;a major improvement over the lengthy processes that require human annotation in current use. As a result, the company can quickly generate and maintain maps that give fully autonomous vehicles the comprehensive and precise knowledge to autonomous operate safely and smoothly on all roads.
About the Opportunity : 
This is an opportunity to work on some of the most exciting problems in the autonomous vehicle industry. Civil Maps is looking for a Devops engineer to grow its overall infrastructure. You will be interacting with a completely custom-made distributed computing framework, handling terabytes and petabytes of machine vision data, and millions of requests from robotic platforms.
In our interdisciplinary teams, you will get acquainted with the many facets of 3D map creation: data collection, geospatial registration, feature extraction, auditing.
Come work on novel challenges, learn and grow while helping Civil Maps achieve on-demand perception of the world around us.
We are hiring the professionals for the below skills:
Work Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;: Hyderabad
Job Description for DevOps Enginner:
Experience : 3-15 yrs 
Responsibilities : 
Deliver next generation distributed applications using a variety of tools to include Kubernetes, Ansible, RHEL, Openshift, Atomic, Mesos, Openstack and Docker.
Build solutions and provide a framework for Microservices and DevOps.
Bring knowledge and help with continuous integration, deployment and security.
Automating the Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment environment with relative tools.
Troubleshooting Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment issues.
Experience with the following : 
Deploy, manage Continuous Integration tools (Jenkins, Travis etc..).
Cloud-based deployments (AWS, Azure, OpenStack).
Linux administration, usage, and bash scripting (Bash, Batch, Powershell)
Deploying MEAN stack applications.
Security tools like Fortify, Nessus.
Network architecture (routing, load balancing, firewalls, VLANs).
Virtualization (VMWare, XEN, KVM, Openstack).
Container technologies (Mesos, Docker, Rocket, etc.).
Experience in setting up backup and restore mechanism for the DB and other relevant systems.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Photoshop editor for repeated work adding text using actions - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Photoshop-editor-for-repeated-work-adding-text-using-actions_%7E01956d4abb6db9599d?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for entry level Photoshop editor with basic Photoshop skills. We are developing a portfolio of imagines where we require to do following:
Change text in the photo using action script (around 30-40 different photos)
Adjust the text in the imagine to suit the text box.
Save the file using batch function as .jpg.
Scripts and necessary instructions will be provided.
The job may require basic editing skill like removing trade names adding light to the imagine...
You should be familiar with design and good feel for colour composition.
I am looking for fast worker, and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;quick learner since the time to perform the job will be limited.
We will post the Photoshop projects on the shared drive like onedrive. After the job is done the ready photo will be uploaded to the same share drive by you.
Required number of hours weekly is min 30.
I am looking for freelancers with the lowest rates
Pay is $3 an hour.Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Photoshop,                     Photo Editing            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 22:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Dutch Christian Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Dutch-Christian-Reading-Audio-Review_%7E01602c2b88ee568672?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are launching Dutch Christian Reading project and hope to hire some Dutch native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Dutch audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Standard Dutch Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Post-production: if vocals and reverberation are pleasant to hear; if the overall tone and the volume of the background music is soft, and will not impair people&amp;rsquo;s ability to hear God&amp;rsquo;s words.
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: October 16, 2018 19:50 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Audio Engineering,                     Audio Production,                     Dutch,                     English,                     Voice Over Dutch            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
</ArrayOfFeedItem>