<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfFeedItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Simple data entry task copy past from website - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Simple-data-entry-task-copy-past-from-website_%7E01ba9f324cbeba85d3?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need freelancers who can stacify me and give me 100% result
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word            Country: United Arab Emiratesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant Plus Accountant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant-Plus-Accountant_%7E01ff4248948964113c?source=rss</link>
    <description>*Availability: Must be able to respond quickly through Emails &amp;amp;amp; Chats (Google Hangout) during working hours *Communication: Must be good with English, (Oral, Written) 
*Skills: Must be skilled in MS Excel, MS Word &amp;amp;amp; other online tools must also have prior experience working with Excel and Google Docs and other online tools (Advance level) 
*Attitude: It must be problem solving, you will be trained but you must show a problem solver attitude. 
*Experience:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;LOOKING FOR EXPERIENCED PERSON WORKING AS VIRTUAL ASSISTANT Plus Accountant and have GOOD COMMAND ON EXCEL (Advance level)
*Extra Ordinary: I am expecting you EXTRA ORDINARY skilled with online portals, tools &amp;amp;amp; relevant software. Strong self-learning skill will be appreciated. 
*Efficiency: Must be able to handle multi task, must be very meticulous and attentive to details 
TIMING &amp;amp;amp; SALARY : 9 AM EST to 7 PM EST (1 Hr break) Monday to Saturday&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Handsome salary will be offered to the right candidate, $400 Monthly
Applications will only be accepted from those who answer the following questions:
1-Do you know what is your working hours going to be? 
2-what is the salary we offer
3-what type of work will you be doing for us
4-how will we communicate with you.Budget: $400
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     Google Sheets,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant Plus Accountant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant-Plus-Accountant_%7E01ff4248948964113c?source=rss</link>
    <description>*Availability: Must be able to respond quickly through Emails &amp;amp;amp; Chats (Google Hangout) during working hours *Communication: Must be good with English, (Oral, Written) 
*Skills: Must be skilled in MS Excel, MS Word &amp;amp;amp; other online tools must also have prior experience working with Excel and Google Docs and other online tools (Advance level) 
*Attitude: It must be problem solving, you will be trained but you must show a problem solver attitude. 
*Experience:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;LOOKING FOR EXPERIENCED PERSON WORKING AS VIRTUAL ASSISTANT Plus Accountant and have GOOD COMMAND ON EXCEL (Advance level)
*Extra Ordinary: I am expecting you EXTRA ORDINARY skilled with online portals, tools &amp;amp;amp; relevant software. Strong self-learning skill will be appreciated. 
*Efficiency: Must be able to handle multi task, must be very meticulous and attentive to details 
TIMING &amp;amp;amp; SALARY : 9 AM EST to 7 PM EST (1 Hr break) Monday to Saturday&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Handsome salary will be offered to the right candidate, $400 Monthly
Applications will only be accepted from those who answer the following questions:
1-Do you know what is your working hours going to be? 
2-what is the salary we offer
3-what type of work will you be doing for us
4-how will we communicate with you.Budget: $400
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     Google Sheets,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Big Data Engineer should have the experience of Informaitca Big Data Manager, Teradata, Mainframe - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Big-Data-Engineer-should-have-the-experience-Informaitca-Big-Data-Manager-Teradata-Mainframe_%7E01b1a43b74a12b9bf6?source=rss</link>
    <description>Should have the knowledge of Data extraction with Informatica Big Data Manager, HDFS, Spooq, Spark, Teradata and Mainframe.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Apache Spark,                     Hadoop,                     Informatica,                     Informatica Data Quality,                     Sqoop,                     Teradata            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Lead Generation &amp;amp;amp; Prospecting Virtual Assistant Needed - Contact Verification from LinkedIN - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Lead-Generation-amp-Prospecting-Virtual-Assistant-Needed-Contact-Verification-from-LinkedIN_%7E01c0bfe0e259ae1c8c?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello - need help with ongoing prospecting and contact information (email, phone, Skype, LinkedIN) using my email-verify.org, LinkedIN &amp;amp;amp; Spokeo accounts. Must be efficient, organized and a quick learner. Eventually this personal will be sending pitch emails and setting up phone calls for me to close. Ongoing work for the best candidate.
Please see example screen-shot of how the date is housed via Google Docs.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Market &amp;amp; Customer Research
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Lead Generation,                     Market Research,                     Marketing Strategy,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Research,                     Sales Strategy,                     Virtual Assistant,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Administrator - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Administrator_%7E010438ca772c3ae302?source=rss</link>
    <description>&amp;bull; Preparing and sorting data for customer accounts.
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Entering data into software and checking to ensure the accuracy of the data that has been inputted. 
&amp;bull; Resolving discrepancies in information and obtaining further information for incomplete data of accounts. 
&amp;bull; Responding to information requests from team lead.
&amp;bull; Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.Budget: $5
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Other - Admin Support
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     English Grammar,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>SQL Developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-Developer_%7E0113263b53bd10c2d1?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a reliable, trustworty individual to use on an ongoing basis to build &amp;amp;quot;data cubes&amp;amp;quot; for business intelligence applications.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We can teach you how to use our business intelligence tool. You will build OLAP cubes by building data cubes using SQL statements. There is a GUI tool that let&amp;#039;s you create the SQL (rather than handwriting SQL). In some cases you will manually write SQL scripts when a lot of data preparation is required.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Often this task is called &amp;amp;quot;Extract Transform and Load&amp;amp;quot; but at it&amp;#039;s core it is about SQL.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The tool we use is called Dundas but again no special knowledge is required.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Microsoft SQL Server Programming,                     SQL            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Social Media Spreadsheet Creation - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Social-Media-Spreadsheet-Creation_%7E01259d8b4f9e181f27?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for someone to go through Google and Yelp and search for all locations in a specific market and check to see if they have a social media presence and add to a spreadsheet. Very simple task. Must have access to the internet and google sheets spreadsheet experience. Should be less than 5 hours total task length if working efficiently. Only need someone with understanding of task and serious work ethic. Thank you!
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Budget: $20
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 20:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Analytical accounting help needed for Turbo-charged client base - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Analytical-accounting-help-needed-for-Turbo-charged-client-base_%7E0104d35778249c6742?source=rss</link>
    <description>The Associate is responsible for performing accounting and analysis functions (such as recording transactions, preparing reconciliations, account research &amp;amp;amp; analysis, financial modeling and the like) for various not-for-profit and for-profit clients.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Previous experience working inside an organization&amp;rsquo;s accounting function is REQUIRED.
The minimum requirement for this position is to be an EXPERT in Excel and QuickBooks, and excited to learn new things and share them with us.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You MUST know accounting.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know something, you enjoy figuring it out.
The PERFECT person would also know (or be excited to learn):
&amp;bull;	QuickBooks, QBO, Sage, Jonas, NetSuite, INTAACT, among others
&amp;bull;	How ERP &amp;amp;amp; Payroll systems impact financial systems
We have a terrific team that includes full-time and part-time members throughout the U.S.
Everyone on our team MUST:
&amp;bull;	Communicate in very good English (mostly written, but also via webvideo apps)
&amp;bull;	Be responsive &amp;amp;amp; accountable
&amp;bull;	Want to GROW with us
&amp;bull;	Uphold client confidentiality and your own personal ethics
&amp;bull;	LOVE what they do
&amp;bull;	Be a positive, happy person
&amp;bull;	Work FAST and ACCURATELY
&amp;bull;	Enjoy solving problems yourself, so no one else has to
&amp;bull;	Be able to work with anyone on the team, not just the &amp;ldquo;boss&amp;rdquo;
&amp;bull;	Meet deadlines
&amp;bull;	Show up to work reliably
SOUND LIKE YOU?
Great!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Here is how to apply for the job:
1.	The very first word of your reply must be &amp;ldquo;Pixie&amp;rdquo;
2.	You must have at least 30 hours of experience and at least 3 different feedbacks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;To be honest, if your overall rating is less than 90%, I will not hire you.
3.	Please provide a flat rate price per hour or, if you&amp;rsquo;d like to work full-time for us, provide a monthly rate.
4.	At the end of your reply, please write the words &amp;ldquo;yellow cat,&amp;rdquo; so I know you read the whole thing.
5.	If you&amp;rsquo;d like to tell me a bit about why you think you are a perfect fit for our team, please do!
Thanks and have a nice day ðŸ˜ŠPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Analytics,                     Budgeting &amp;amp; Forecasting,                     Financial Accounting,                     Financial Modeling,                     Financial Reporting,                     Intuit QuickBooks,                     Management Accounting,                     Microsoft Excel            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 18:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Voice Over - Southern US Accent - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Voice-Over-Southern-Accent_%7E01489c86e367dbed39?source=rss</link>
    <description>Voice over for meditation titles for behavioral health non-profit.
Soft, soothing, compassionate, genuine voice and gentle tone.
Native southern US accents only.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;No acting please - we need genuine speakers with distinct regional accents to add to the diversity of our sound.
Opportunity to work with nationally-known voice coach.
Please attach a sample of your work or link to audio samples.
DETAILS
Scripts average 225 words in length and represent approximately two minutes of finished audio.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Finished audio includes audio engineering and production services.
Complete instructions, guidance, and direction will be provided outside of Upwork.
General Terms and Rates
&amp;bull;	All work-for-hire rates are &amp;ldquo;buy-out&amp;rdquo; (unlimited usage, licensed in perpetuity, national/global) for Internet, app and smart speaker delivery, radio, and television.
&amp;bull;	Non-broadcast rates.
&amp;bull;	Non-exclusive.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We do not restrict your ability to work on other meditation voice overs.
&amp;bull;	Non-union only.
&amp;bull;	No royalty share &amp;ndash; no direct revenue from audio.
&amp;bull;	Flat rates per meditation script.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Timings of approximately two minutes for 200-250 words are provided as general guidance.
&amp;bull;	Current rates as of fall 2018: $10/script
Delivery/Editing/Syncing
&amp;bull;	Voice recordings are delivered dry (raw) with no music. 
&amp;bull;	No syncing required.
Re-Recordings &amp;amp;amp; Revisions/Script Changes
&amp;bull;	Rate covers one initial recording, then up to two full re-records for changes in tone and style. 
&amp;bull;	Scripts are set based on existing content.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Therefore, there will be no script revisions.
Bulk/Batch Work 
&amp;bull;	Work on your own time within a given number of calendar days/weeks.
&amp;bull;	Consistent work opportunityPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Voice Talent
Skills:        Audio Recording,                     Narration,                     Voice Over,                     Voice Recording,                     Voice Talent            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 18:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Research - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Research_%7E01b4b3c17f19709838?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello,
I&amp;#039;m looking to gain a list of at least 100+ dance teachers and instructors in the Southern California area.
Must be good with Google Sheets or Excel. 
I&amp;#039;m looking to get this delivered by tomorrow morning if not evening Pacific Standard Time. 
Thank you!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Web Research
Skills:        Google Search,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Mail Merge Document Needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Mail-Merge-Document-Needed_%7E017e48fec055949911?source=rss</link>
    <description>I would like a mail merge excel/csv/word that I can use to generate mailing labels.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Anyone who is proficient at excel/word can complete this task.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;All of the information is on one website. I need the name, address, and phone number of all the homeless shelters listed for the state of new York on shelterlistings.org.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The phone number should not print on the labels it should just be an excess field that I can use to make follow up calls. The information is all on shelterlistings.org.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I need every listing in the state of New York.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If this goes smoothly I will need other lists and possibly other marketing assistance.Budget: $75
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Other - Sales &amp;amp; Marketing
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 18:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>LinkedIn Research - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/LinkedIn-Research_%7E01c7cc85ac56bd120c?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have 300 people for you to look up on LinkedIn and identify the names of their current company and the title of their current position.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I will be providing you the names of past companies that they have worked for so you can more easily identify them.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Lead Generation
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Lead Generation,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 18:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Quickbooks Bookkeeper eCommerce Amazon Shopify Paypal - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Quickbooks-Bookkeeper-eCommerce-Amazon-Shopify-Paypal_%7E013ed92cc665c35b4c?source=rss</link>
    <description>We need a freelance bookkeeper for monthly reconciliation of income and expenses using Quickbooks online. Includes one business banking account and one business credit card.
I am not looking for a CPA but someone that has a background in accounting principles most importantly knows the ins &amp;amp;amp; outs of Quickbooks. I do have some very specific questions but we can discuss if we move to the next step in the hiring process. lessPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Amazon Seller Central,                     Bank Reconciliation,                     Bookkeeping,                     Intuit QuickBooks,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Stripe            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 17:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant Needed for Email Data Entry - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant-Needed-for-Email-Data-Entry_%7E01b23503cfc7b18aba?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi there,
I need a reliable virtual assistant for a paid test task that might result in a long-term agreement with the suitable candidate. It is pretty straightforward - extract emails from a website and fill them in a spreadsheet. This is pretty much all that is expected:
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1_YtMc7fSNe-Fq4iVsaRHT4IVrbIshCXUq9Gw1H2bJTE/edit?usp=sharing
Let me know if you are interested.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Google Docs,                     Google Sheets            Country: Spainclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 17:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Recruitment Researcher - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Recruitment-Researcher_%7E01a9dae933b99f29bb?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a Talented recruitment researcher to join our team,We are looking for three temporary workers to join a busy recruitment team within a large national organisation on the lead up to the Christmas period. This role will be working primarily to screen applicants for a variety of vacancies across the business and the UK.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Human Resources
Skills:        Customer Service,                     Email Handling,                     Human Resource Management,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     LinkedIn Recruiting,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Sales Strategy,                     Social Media Marketing            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Seeking Excel/Data admin to help organize data for email campaign - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Seeking-Excel-Data-admin-help-organize-data-for-email-campaign_%7E01a0e353112f049294?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have data on our customers in several excel docs and also would like to collect data from other platforms. It is time sensitive so we would prefer if you had experience with this work so you can incorporate your methods into the process.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Mining,                     Email Etiquette,                     HubSpot,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 15:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Website Research and Categorization - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Website-Research-and-Categorization_%7E01f631aad8e99ef573?source=rss</link>
    <description>Deliverable:
- Research websites and categorize based on a set criteria. 
- Input contact information and links to social media.
Ideal Candidate:
- Detail oriented
- Can work diligently and accurately 
- Familiar with Excel/SheetsPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Web Research
Skills:        English,                     English Grammar,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Web Research            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Accountant/Bookkeeper needed for an E-Commerce Business - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Accountant-Bookkeeper-needed-for-Commerce-Business_%7E0110c95c732e208746?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi there, We are looking for a QuickBooks Expert, that also has experience with multicurrency Amazon accounts and multicurrency bank* accounts (we sell on several different Amazon platforms, and use GBP, EUR, USD &amp;amp;amp; CAD). We are going to need you to help us get our Quickbooks up to date and tidied up, and also consult with me and show me how to correctly use and update Quickbooks (as I will doing our bookkeeping).Budget: $25
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Amazon Seller Central,                     Bank Reconciliation,                     Intuit QuickBooks,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Shopify,                     Stripe            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Part-tme CFO - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Part-tme-CFO_%7E0128fe3a05da5a5f8a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need financial forecasts and insights completed on a monthly basis ie. Income Statement, Balance Sheet, Projections, Cash Flow.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Financial Planning
Skills:        Business Analysis,                     Financial Analysis,                     Financial Forecasting,                     Financial Modeling,                     Financial Reporting,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 14:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry / Copy Paste - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-Copy-Paste_%7E01c4e3105a4e0afb8a?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need someone to copy information from the database to excel/google sheets.
If you are a NEWBIE and looking for awesome REVIEW you are most welcome.
Payment is $1 for every 100 datasBudget: $5
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Google Sheets,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Philippinesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 13:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Magento Product Manager - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Magento-Product-Manager_%7E01ede769471940187e?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a new product manager to manage a multi store Magento environment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Site wide product cleansing from descriptions to attributes to titles to categories, basically everything product related retrieval of manufacture information to custom information addition.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are currently around 1000 products.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If you are experienced with multistore management and you know Magento then we would like to hear from you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will be working with a team on this project in GMT. 
Required Experience
--MultiStore Magento
--Exceptional Excel Skills
Other skills that would be an advantage; 
--A/B Test frontend 
--General store management
Mention anything else you feel relevant in your coverpage.
How to Apply
Start your application with &amp;amp;quot;This is why I am a Magento Ecommerce rockstar&amp;amp;quot;
-- Include 1 x speedtest.net results link
The questions we ask are important and designed to weed out the copy paste applicants, please take them seriously this is a true long-term position.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;There are always 30+ applications but most of the time the skillset is not where it need to be to join our team.
Successful applicants will be interviewed after this application process.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Product Management
Skills:        Magento,                     Magento 2,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Product Descriptions,                     Product Management            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>UK Irish Account Management/Bookkeeper Applicants - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Irish-Account-Management-Bookkeeper-Applicants_%7E01abfb2062f2e2ee7a?source=rss</link>
    <description>This is a part time role so when stating your rate, keep this in mind. 
We are in need of some account management love, we need someone capable of bringing some organization to a small firm and controlling the account management and financial preparations and projections.
Experience with experience of UK Tax, VAT and HMRC or Revenue is essential so would prefer and UK or Irish applicants.
Remember this is a Part Time position for a full time commitment so dedicated remote workers only.
These are essential 
-Trustworthy 
-Good Friendly Attitude 
-On the ball at all times
-Native EnglishPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Accounting,                     Accounts Payable Management,                     Accounts Receivable Management,                     Bookkeeping,                     Financial Accounting,                     Financial Reporting,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 12:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry // Age andâ€‹ Gender - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-Age-and-Gender_%7E01b47180a9ed38d9fa?source=rss</link>
    <description>You will get 5000 links with two profile pictures of a person and you have to guess the age and estimate gender (male/female).
Data entry into excel spreadsheet.Budget: $60
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Germanyclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 12:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web/LinkedIn research retail Buyers for food brand - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-LinkedIn-research-retail-Buyers-for-food-brand_%7E019d198214dd36a662?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Co-founder of food brand Ambronite &amp;mdash; we do Complete Meal Shakes. You can Google us.
We have ramped up our sales online, where 80% of our current sales come from. We have recently started expanding to specialty food store chains and premium supermarkets around Europe.
We are building up retailer CRM from all Western Europe countries right now and need help. We need an Expert to source the names of potential retailers, Purchasing managers, their emails, phone numbers etc to support our hungry sales team.
The work will include web research and cold calling. We are looking into 10 - 20 h project. If you perform well, even more
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Lead Generation
Skills:        Cold Calling,                     Data Entry,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Nutrition,                     Procurement,                     Sales            Country: Finlandclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Freelancer pour saisie de donnÃ©es dans Excel - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Freelancer-pour-saisie-donn-dans-Excel_%7E01ea6050dadf7521ab?source=rss</link>
    <description>Je cherche un freelancer francophone pour saisir des donn&amp;eacute;e dans un tableau excel.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     French,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Switzerlandclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 08:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data entry for {â€‹Financial Accounting or cost Accounting}â€‹ - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-entry-for-Financial-Accounting-cost-Accounting_%7E01f8da1f8553ecdad7?source=rss</link>
    <description>About us:
{â€‹Description of your company and type of data entry work needed}â€‹
We&amp;#039;re looking for an experienced data entry specialist to transfer data into our main database. We anticipate that this project will require {â€‹#}â€‹ hours per week for {â€‹#}â€‹ weeks.
Deliverables:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Transfer invoices and customer data into our content management system
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Enter notes into database (when appropriate) to clarify any changes
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Compile all our past/current marketing campaigns into one central file
Requirements for the project:
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Experience with Microsoft Suite (Word, Excel, etc.)
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Excellent grammar and a high attention to detail
In your proposal, please share a brief summary of your experience.Budget: $12
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        AccountAbility,                     Accounting,                     Automated Call Distribution,                     Ecrion Software EOS,                     Fision,                     Grovo Learning,                     Merrill DataSite,                     Octane Render,                     PostCSS,                     Python Pandas,                     Sales Strategy,                     Union Square Software            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 08:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Programming/Excel - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Programming-Excel_%7E017dc25bde5c12568f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have excel file with 5 lac records. I need to extract fields/data based on following criteria:
Same Agency, Same Remitter (80 to 100% match), Sane Bene (80 to 100% match), Same Date.
I will count them as duplicate.
Program should pick first field and apply the above criteria to all other record and extract all the fields matches this criteria.
For example:
Pick first field, match the date, if date matches, match the agency name, if it matches, match the remitter, if it matches 80 to 100%, match the bene, if bene matches 80 to 100% - I want this field separated. Move to next field and apply this again. Please note, keep excluding those fields from further searches those are already identified as duplicate.
If you have better idea or logic in mind pls apply, I just want duplicate entries from 500000 record based on this criteria:
Same Agency, Same Remitter (80 to 100% match), Sane Bene (80 to 100% match), Same Date.
Final output sheet should contain all duplicate entries including original stance.
Attached is excel file as review.Budget: $10
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Excel VBA,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 06:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Programming/Excel - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Programming-Excel_%7E017dc25bde5c12568f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have excel file with 5 lac records. I need to extract fields/data based on following criteria:
Same Agency, Same Remitter (80 to 100% match), Sane Bene (80 to 100% match), Same Date.
I will count them as duplicate.
Program should pick first field and apply the above criteria to all other record and extract all the fields matches this criteria.
For example:
Pick first field, match the date, if date matches, match the agency name, if it matches, match the remitter, if it matches 80 to 100%, match the bene, if bene matches 80 to 100% - I want this field separated. Move to next field and apply this again. Please note, keep excluding those fields from further searches those are already identified as duplicate.
If you have better idea or logic in mind pls apply, I just want duplicate entries from 500000 record based on this criteria:
Same Agency, Same Remitter (80 to 100% match), Sane Bene (80 to 100% match), Same Date.
Final output sheet should contain all duplicate entries including original stance.
Attached is excel file as review.Budget: $10
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Excel VBA,                     Microsoft Excel            Country: Pakistanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 06:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need someone to extract/scrape data from Instagram using a script we have - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-someone-extract-scrape-data-from-Instagram-using-script-have_%7E0186d573f2a67a94c8?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a database set up in MongoDB and have a script we found that should get us the data that we need (https://instaloader.github.io/). We need to get the tagged media from several profiles and house them in our database, as well as enter them on an ongoing basis (you will be paid every time we use you to do this). 
***The job is urgent as we need someone to get the data and upload it by Tuesday 10/23***
 - Price is negotiable depending on your skillset. we have additional things we need help fixing if you have experience with PHP/backend solutions
It should be pretty easy for anyone who is good with Python and Mongo. If you have PHP experience that would be extremely helpful too as we need to test the delivery of data to our database.Budget: $150
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Database Design,                     Database Management,                     Database Testing,                     MongoDB,                     PHP,                     Python,                     Quality Control,                     UX Design,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 05:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Create a google chrome EXTENSION that works Facebook + Google Sheets (Explaination Video Included) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Create-google-chrome-EXTENSION-that-works-Facebook-Google-Sheets-Explaination-Video-Included_%7E0177125ecabfe21304?source=rss</link>
    <description>*** Hiring THIS week ***
I created a video for this job.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It&amp;#039;s 5 minutes. 
PASSWORD: upwork
https://vimeo.com/296143811
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Google Chrome Extension that works with Facebook Api + Google Sheets
Features:
1) Pull from facebook group questions and answers
2) Extract information into google sheet + create another column where only first names are extracted
3) Auto-adds facebook group requests to join
Answers from questions I got so far:
1) Is data automatically pushed to google sheet?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;No.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;On chrome extension dashboard (open tab), there is a button that says &amp;amp;quot;push data to sheet&amp;amp;quot; and you choose which google sheet you want to push data to. **Screenshot attached**
2) Is there more than 1 group or only work with 1 group?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The chrome extension works with more than 1 facebook group and can push data to more than 1 google sheet. **Screenshot attached**
3) Is there a facebook app involved where it has to be connected with an app?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Currently I do not see it needs to be connected with any facebook app but it does need to communicate with facebook somehow as I see the google sheet link is within facebook group Settings dashboard.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;**screenshot attached**
4) How do I connect to facebook with google chrome extension?
Looks like they did it by the google sheet URL. **screenshot attached**
5) What is the workflow of a user look like? From a similar chrome extension point of view?
1) Group funnels is purchased with an email2
2) Extension downloaded
3) Someone on the backend (worker at groupfunnels) MANUALLY connects something to your email address so you are approved to use groupfunnels
4) Create blank google sheet --&amp;amp;gt; upload their CSV file into google sheet to match format of facebook
5) After chrome extension is downloaded... go into Facebook Group Settings... there will be a BLANK bar.
6) Copy and paste URL of google sheet (share link) into the blank bar within Facebook Group dashboard where you approve members
7) Click &amp;amp;quot;approve all&amp;amp;quot; and data is transported into Group Funnels Dashboard (another tab in browser)
8) Data is shown within Group Funnels Dashboard like an excel sheet format --&amp;amp;gt; we choose from a drop down which Google Sheet to push data into. --&amp;amp;gt; then we push a button that pushes data into correct google sheet.
9) There is another button where we can &amp;amp;quot;Clear data&amp;amp;quot; so that we do not end up pushing same data twice into same google sheet (causing repeat data)
I created a video for it.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It&amp;#039;s 5 minutes. 
PASSWORD: upwork
https://vimeo.com/296143811
Company that does a similar thing:
Groupfunnels
https://www.groupfunnels.com/start
I have attached all of Groupfunnels&amp;#039; documentation for your use as well as screenshot of the google extension dashboard.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        Facebook Development,                     Facebook Javascript (FBJS),                     Google Sheets            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 05:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Create two reports  using Microsoft Excel.profit and loss summary for last 12 months - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Create-two-reports-using-Microsoft-Excel-profit-and-loss-summary-for-last-months_%7E01f2e278f2df5cda1a?source=rss</link>
    <description>This job is for creating two basic financial reports using a recent version of Microsoft Excel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The two reports we need are:
1. Profit and loss summary for last 12 months
2. Year to date profit &amp;amp;amp; loss statement.
All data will be organized and provided in a PDF that you can copy text from and paste into Excel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Reports must be editable and formatted like attached example.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
This job must be completed in the next 24 hours.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Thank youBudget: $50
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Microsoft Excel            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 05:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Conduct a Valuation Analysis for technology company and develop a financing strategy and pitch. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Conduct-Valuation-Analysis-for-technology-company-and-develop-financing-strategy-and-pitch_%7E01d05f8559a8e6ea99?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for a freelancer with financial valuation and capital raising background to run a valuation analysis for our professional services company.
We are looking to firstly put a value to our company and secondly to create a pro-forma valuation for the next few years leading up to an IPO so that we can price our shares for a private placement sale. 
Looking for someone who has experience in investment banking, technology, SAAS, professional services, M&amp;amp;amp;A to advice on this valuation. 
Following the valuation exercise, to discuss plans to structure the company and to prepare slides for pitching.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Financial Planning
Skills:        Business Analysis,                     Business Planning,                     Business Valuation,                     Financial Forecasting,                     Financial Modeling,                     Google Slides,                     Investment Banking,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft PowerPoint            Country: Singaporeclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 04:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant_%7E0159aaf503516843db?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a Virtual Assistant to help with web research, small data entry tasks, updating excel documents, sorting and filing and general admin support.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Email Handling,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 03:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Electrical Schematic Development - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Electrical-Schematic-Development_%7E01128861d9fdb3612e?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a set of 3 x single line diagrams... Simple sketches created in Microsoft Excel... Would like them turned into 3 x separate Electrical AutoCAD Schematics... Can email documents to successful candidates for review and quoting...Budget: $250
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Engineering &amp;amp; Architecture &amp;gt; Electrical Engineering
Skills:        Electrical Drawing,                     Electrical Engineering            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 03:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistants needed for VA agency. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistants-needed-for-agency_%7E019f82206b4a533fe1?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are a Virtual Assistant agency looking that complete all types of administrative duties, and long and short-term tasks.
Our agency is looking for skilled virtual assistants to join our team. We need competent, consistent, and motivated workers.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Human Resources
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Content Writing,                     Customer Service,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     Marketing Strategy,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 03:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Web Researcher and Data entry Expert Needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Web-Researcher-and-Data-entry-Expert-Needed_%7E013108f5ea7b6375d9?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are in need of a very dependable and reliable, experienced web researcher and Data entry professional for our growing real estate company. 
MUST HAVE RELIABLE VPN ACCESS
MUST BE ABLE TO WORK 9:30AM - 12:30PM (3 HOURS) EASTERN TIME ZONE, USA. DON&amp;#039;T APPLY IF YOU CANNOT. 
We will need you to look up specific information and put that information into a spreadsheet.
We are looking for a team member that is reliable and will not be late, must be a good communicator and keep in contact with us through emails, texts, calls and upwork.
We will also need you to be flexible and be able to do other VA related tasks (Sending emails,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;texts, Data entry, writing your progress down for us to track numbers).
AGAIN, PLEASE DO NOT APPLY UNLESS YOU HAVE A GREAT AND RELIABLE VPN ACCESS TO US WEBSITES. We&amp;#039;ve had a few issues with freelancers that said they could access sites, then cannot.
Ultimately we will need leads generated for our real estate investing company. A bonus will be given equal to 1 full months pay for any lead you find us that turns into a deal!!!
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Google Docs,                     Google Search,                     Google Sheets,                     Google Spreadsheets,                     Internet Research,                     Lead Generation,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant,                     VPN            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 02:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Assistant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Assistant_%7E01df66c9a0619485d7?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a Virtual Assistant to help with web research, small data entry tasks, updating excel documents, sorting and filing and general admin supportPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Email Handling,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 01:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry Specialist needed for a quick Excel job. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-Specialist-needed-for-quick-Excel-job_%7E01e1982d4827d10484?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for an efficient Virtual Assistant. Must be a native English speaker. In depth knowledge of MS Excel will be an added advantage.Budget: $10
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft PowerPoint,                     Microsoft Word            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer for email parsing and extracting negative sentiment - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developer-for-email-parsing-and-extracting-negative-sentiment_%7E0127e56c170fd6ee78?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hello,
I am looking for one, two or three developers to do the following. Please respond if you have experience with one or more, machine learning, sentiment analysis, web development, email parsing. Only applicants with relevant experience will be considered. Thank you
1) Periodically parse through an email inbox (Outlook 365)
2) Periodically parse through Amazon reviews via Amazon APIs
3) Extract only emails with negative sentiments and save all such emails along with the below listed fields to a database. 
4) Extract all reviews with 3 stars, 2 stars and 1 star review and save the review along with the below fields to the same database.
5) Publish the new list on a web page for my customer service team to review
6) Make this list editable from the web page so the customer service team can remove any false flags
7) Make the entire list available for my customer service team on a web page with different filters and search options so the team can update the list as needed.
8) Create a web form for the customer service team to update the database&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;manually
9) Make the list searchable with multiple search criteria. make the search results downloadable in CSV, Tab delimited and Excel format.
List of fields in the database list
Purchase Date
*Complaint Month/Year
*Complaint Date
*Brand
*ProductName
Original order #
Color
Asin
*Customer name 
Marketplace
*Channel
*Complaint (email body or actual Amazon review)
Action taken
Replacement item
Replacmnt/ Refund Date
Status
Received Date
Replacement Amazon Order/USPS/UPS #
Follow up
Issues
Refund
Comment
Black listed in FG
Return Label
Addressed by 
Followed by 
* denotes required fieldPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Database Programming,                     Machine Learning,                     PHP,                     PostCSS,                     Python,                     Python Pandas,                     Sentiment Analysis,                     SQL            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 23:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Devops Lead - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Devops-Lead_%7E019e172d22810a2d48?source=rss</link>
    <description>jenkins, git, svn, Urban code deployment, Tfs, visuals studio and patching vulnerabilities on Kenna.Budget: $450
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        DevOps,                     Git,                     Jenkins,                     Python,                     Tortoise SVN            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 23:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data mining professionals wanted - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-mining-professionals-wanted_%7E0193452df93a6ca738?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking for data mining and extraction experts for some extraction and filtering... If you have samples of what you have done, let me know. We can also discuss more on chat.Budget: $300
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Lead Generation            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 22:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Business Intelligence Developer for Interesting Trouble Shooting Project - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Business-Intelligence-Developer-for-Interesting-Trouble-Shooting-Project_%7E018eccfdb14e44864e?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are currently experiencing trouble with an ETL script that feeds into an AWS instance and then is displayed in Klipfolio. 
We are looking for an experienced business intelligence developer to examine the datasources, ETL structure and process, diagnose the problem and fix it. 
Feel free to message me with:
- An overview of your business intelligence experience, including how you&amp;#039;ve diagnosed and fixed problems in complex systems
- Have any questions about the data sources, script or data visualization tools used
A great performance on this project will lead to additional work.
Thank you!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        AWS ECS,                     Business Intelligence,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Klipfolio,                     SQL            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 21:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Desktop, Server and Network Technician for Managed Services Provider - U.S. Eastern Time - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Desktop-Server-and-Network-Technician-for-Managed-Services-Provider-Eastern-Time_%7E012ec0c5ed2d80695f?source=rss</link>
    <description>Managed Services Provider seeking an outstanding experienced Desktop / Server / Network support technician to work Eastern Standard / Daylight Time schedule (GMT -5).
Fluent English speaking is absolutely required.
The position&amp;#039;s tasks include: 
- Working directly with clients via phone on help desk tickets 
- Working on technical project related tasks
- Remote installations and configurations of Windows Desktops &amp;amp;amp; Server based operating systems and software via Dell DRAC or HP Advanced iLO 
- Windows Server / Active Directory setup, configuration, migrations.
- Maintenance and troubleshooting of Microsoft Servers and Workstations 
- Maintenance and troubleshooting of network devices such as NAS, Access Point, Printers, Copiers, etc.. 
- Configuration, maintenance, and troubleshooting of Sonicwall, Cisco, Netgear, and other similar firewalls or network equipment.
- Configuration, maintenance, and troubleshooting of Windows based workstations and software. 
- End user support for Microsoft and other 3rd party software via phone and ticketing system
- End user mobile device support (iPhone / Android / Windows)
This position is on a schedule according to business hours within the U.S. Eastern Standard / Daylight Time (EST/EDT) zone:
8am - 5pm EST / EDT (GMT -5) 
Applicants must be familiar with technical support roles in a managed I.T. services environment and able to perform technical tasks and research solutions without assistance. It is also important to be a team player able to work with other technicians and / or mentor those in a more junior role. Team Lead experience is a plus.
We use an ticketing system (Kaseya) so you must also be familiar with keeping detailed notes about communications, technical troubleshooting, and setup steps you take when performing assigned duties. 
We also use the Continuum RMM platform.
You must also have strong communication skills and be able to communicate in clear English via phone (calls to U.S. based clients), e-mail, and chat. - ability to provide support via phone is required.
Critical thinking, decision making, and troubleshooting skills will be needed on a daily basis - our technicians frequently research solutions on their own using Google and other available resources.
Job applicants must have strong experience with:
Managed Services Provider environment
Windows Server 2012/2008/2003
Microsoft Exchange (or hosted Exchange)
Microsoft Outlook configuration
Windows 7 Professional
Windows 10 Professional
Microsoft Hyper-V (or other virtualization platforms)
Active Directory setup and maintenance
Active Directory, user and computer management
Windows Server based remote access (RWW, RDS, RDP, Terminal Services)
DNS / DHCP Services
NTFS File and Share permissions
Windows Server Migrations
New Server deployments
Storage Management (hardware RAID)
Server Troubleshooting
Workstation Troubleshooting
TCP/IP Networking
Firewall configurations (including NAT, ACLs, inbound/outbound rules)
Windows Desktop support in Active Directory domain environments
Microsoft Office suite
Virus / Malware detection and removal
A plus to have experience with the following:
Customer Service training (e.g. BPO Call Center training)
Office365 / Hosted Exchange
MigrationWiz
Dell DRAC/ HP iLO remote access controllers
Dell or HP Server Hardware
MS SQL server maintenance
Batch file and scripting
Server performance monitoring
Network performance monitoring
Network Switch configuration including VLANs
Kaseya experience
Business-Grade Anti-Virus platform experience
Business-Grade Backup software (BackupExec, etc..)
Barracuda
VMWare
Citrix
Azure
Amazon Web Services
Amazon Workspaces
DaaS / SaaS / IaaS
Service Desk / Help Desk Management
Microsoft, Sonicwall, or Cisco certifications 
ITIL knowledge or certification
Customer Service Skills
The ability to provide prompt and friendly service to clients is critical so we are looking for applicants who enjoy resolving issues and being pro-active to help users enjoy the support experience.
This position will be a contract based position but for the right applicant it is expected to be steady and require &amp;amp;quot;full time hours&amp;amp;quot; for an extended period of time.
Thank you for your interest!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Active Directory,                     BPO Call Center,                     BPO IT Services,                     Cisco IOS,                     Computer Networking,                     Customer Service,                     Desktop Support,                     DevOps,                     Firewall,                     Microsoft Active Directory,                     Microsoft Exchange Server,                     Microsoft Hyper V,                     Microsoft Office 365 Administration,                     Microsoft Windows Server,                     Network Administration,                     Phone Support,                     Scripting,                     Storage Area Networks (SAN),                     Technical Support,                     VMware ESX Server,                     VPN,                     Windows 10 Administration,                     Windows 7 Administration,                     Windows Administration,                     Windows NT Administration            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 19:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Technical Translations Project Manager - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Technical-Translations-Project-Manager_%7E012646224c1e1353ec?source=rss</link>
    <description>The Project Manager coordinates the completion of language translation projects on a freelance basis and assists with the management and expansion of the company&amp;#039;s network of translation talent.
Position Responsibilities: 
&amp;bull;	Manage multiple translation projects
&amp;bull;	Collaborate with others, including account managers and clients, to clarify project parameters
&amp;bull;	Expand the company&amp;#039;s network of translation talent by identifying, vetting, and formalizing relationships with translators. 
Essential Skills: 
&amp;bull;	Excellent communication skills
&amp;bull;	Strong organizational skills
&amp;bull;	Ability to manage time effectively 
&amp;bull;	Highly-focused, detail-oriented, and client-centric mindset
&amp;bull;	Capable of setting and meeting deadlines
&amp;bull;	Proven problem-solving skills
&amp;bull;	Ability to work well in both independent and highly collaborative settings
&amp;bull;	Ability to excel in fast-paced work environment 
&amp;bull;	High degree of proficiency in relevant computer skills (MS Office)
Requirements:
&amp;bull;	Minimum of a bachelor degree
Preferred:
&amp;bull;	Minimum of 2 years experience in translation services
&amp;bull;	Experience working with remote, globally-distributed teams.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Project Management,                     Translation            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 19:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a tool that can extract data from Amazon AMS/AMG invoices - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-tool-that-can-extract-data-from-Amazon-AMS-AMG-invoices_%7E016b973f5d00190122?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need a tool that can extract Amazon AMS/AMG pdf invoices to excel with the exact data which can be specified in advance.Budget: $30
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Excel VBA,                     IMacros,                     Python Pandas            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 18:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Accounts Executive / Bookkeeper / Accountant (US Shift till 1am - Ahmedabad) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Accounts-Executive-Bookkeeper-Accountant-Shift-till-1am-Ahmedabad_%7E01e9c7a71c0ff920c5?source=rss</link>
    <description>US and Canada based Bookkeeping firm looking for smart, intelligent and talented professionals for its Ahmedabad office. 
Principal Accountabilities:
1.	Reconcile bank and credit card accounts for multiple clients 
2.	Conduct weekly/monthly reconciliation of all bank accounts
3.	Accounts payables/receivables management
4.	Report &amp;amp;amp; produce financial statements on a regular basis
5.	Liaison with external accountant &amp;amp;amp; CPA
6.	Assemble information for external auditors for audit, if required
7.	Help with budgets and calculate variances 
8.	Process payroll in a timely manner
9.	Provide clerical and administrative support to management as requested
10.	Other office duties as and when requested by the management
Essential: 
1)	3-5 years working knowledge of Quickbooks, Xero, SAGE accounting softwares
2)	Fluent written and spoken English to handle foreign clients
3)	Willing to work in US shift till 1am in Ahmedabad (Monday to Friday. Weekends closed) 
Desired Qualifications: 
1)	Bachelors/Masters Degree in Accounting, Finance or MBA
2)	3-5 years experience working for US based clients
3)	Knowledge of US sales and income taxes would be beneficial
4)	Excellent Excel and MS Office skillsPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Accounts Payable Management,                     Accounts Receivable Management,                     Bookkeeping,                     Intuit QuickBooks,                     Quick Books Online,                     Sage 50 Accounting,                     Xero            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>List building in a Google document - no looking up emails, just data entry! - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/List-building-Google-document-looking-emails-just-data-entry_%7E0105e103917e0ec597?source=rss</link>
    <description>This job consists of building a list of accredited healthcare education programs in the United States. All of the information required - University, first name, last name, address, degree, accreditation expiration date - is publicly available. All you need to do is extract this data and enter it into a Google spreadsheet that we will provide. This is basically a copying and pasting list building project.
To start, you will simply enter all the schools described in the &amp;amp;quot;CAPTE&amp;amp;quot; section of the attached document - these schools are members of the American Physical Therapy Association. There&amp;#039;s probably a few hundred schools on this list, and that&amp;#039;s where you&amp;#039;ll start. If you do a good job on this initial part of the project (we&amp;#039;ll check your work), then we have an almost endless supply of additional work for you.Budget: $100
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Lead Generation,                     Web Research            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 16:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Italian: Translate 1,500 phrases &amp;amp;amp; vocab - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Italian-Translate-500-phrases-amp-vocab_%7E0123dae0f595950dc1?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking for an English-Italian translator to help me with a small project.
I have a list of 1,500 English phrases. There are actually three parts to this project:
Part 1) Translate these English phrases
Part 2) Provide a &amp;ldquo;gloss translation&amp;rdquo; of these phrases back into English
Part 3) Translate the key vocabulary of these phrases
Due to character limitations in the Description section, I am uploading the full description of this project as an MS Word document called &amp;amp;quot;Project Description&amp;amp;quot;. I am also uploading the source / template with the translation work as an Excel file. 
Please let me know if you have any questions.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 16:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>MS SQL developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/SQL-developer_%7E01b862b2d29e68302b?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am need some one with strong MS SQL here I can extract data from multiple database and create a report.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     SQL Programming            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 16:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Recruiting Support - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Recruiting-Support_%7E01af2eed6877b6a6a0?source=rss</link>
    <description>Recruiting support for administrative and professional services projects across the U.S. The Recruiter will be expected to perform the following tasks/activities:
1. Post anonymous job ads; 
2. Review applicant resumes;
3. Review resumes of potential candidates on relevant job boards (e.g., indeed);
4. List all qualified candidates in an MS Excel spreadsheet;
5. Using a company-provided list of questions, screen qualified candidates via phone;
6. Note candidate responses to each question;
7. Rate the strength of each candidates&amp;#039; match for subject position;
8. Provide an organized package of resumes, candidate responses to questions, ratings, and a contact listing for all applicants/candidates regardless of whether they participated in a phone screen. The objective is to screen all qualified applicants/candidates. Unscreened candidates must be identified on the candidate listing.
Job requirements will be provided on Fridays and the results/deliverables (item 8) will be due by the following Friday.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Human Resources
Skills:        Automated Call Distribution,                     Interviewing,                     Recruiting,                     Sourcing,                     Writing            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 15:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data schema for reference data, and matching - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-schema-for-reference-data-and-matching_%7E010e2590432903fd63?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for help in 
- creating a schema for reference data taxonomy
 - keyword extraction
- free text search
- ranking
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Budget: $100
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     Full-text Search Engines,                     Textpattern            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 14:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Create a My Orders page with detail view for my new component. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Create-Orders-page-with-detail-view-for-new-component_%7E01834c4438d2af156b?source=rss</link>
    <description>MUST be done this weekend.
give a quote.
I need a very experienced PHP developer that is great with SQL.
The task is to extract all of a users orders from the dbase and put them into a list.
when the item in the list is clicked, it needs to open in details view to look like an invoice, with a generate PDF option.
The pdfdoc class is already present in the system, so you can hook into it.
To create sample data, you just need to go through the checkout process for free products and generate dbase content for your new user that you will use to test.
This isn&amp;#039;t a hard task for an experienced developer.Budget: $20
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Ecommerce Development
Skills:        Joomla            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Help with Code in R - Statistical - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Help-with-Code-Statistical_%7E010f6a599bff01debd?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need someone to add asterisks to my Matrix Tables see code for reference line 313 onwards. I want to put an asterisk (*) (**),(***) on the constant and Beta values if something is significant or not. I want this done as soon as possible. I want it done such that when the matrix is extracted it has beta value and the relevant *** next to it. Please need help ASAPPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        R,                     Statistical Analysis            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 10:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>A script or tool to search OLE files using author and last saved by attributes. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/script-tool-search-OLE-files-using-author-and-last-saved-attributes_%7E012423d778ab58892c?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want a search tool or script that search OLE files (Ms Word, Ms Excel, PDF) using the author and last saved by attributes in the metadata. I prefer a script written with python or php.Budget: $20
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Scraping,                     PHP,                     Python,                     Python Pandas            Country: Ghanaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 08:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>GitHub - SVN - Maven - Jenkins - - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/GitHub-SVN-Maven-Jenkins_%7E01fab53119ce316f40?source=rss</link>
    <description>Code deployment installation GitHub - Maven - Jenkins - SVNPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Apache Maven,                     Apache Tomcat,                     Java,                     Jenkins,                     Apache Subversion (SVN)            Country: Philippinesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 07:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>VA NEEDED FOR EMAIL DATA ENTRY ($200/MO SALARY) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/NEEDED-FOR-EMAIL-DATA-ENTRY-200-SALARY_%7E016930f9f313f3050b?source=rss</link>
    <description>Upon being hired, you will be helping me to export data entry for customers from a store using the Shopify platform onto an excel/google sheet that I will then need to be sent over to me. This will turn into a long-term job opportunity so long as the Data Entry Admin Assistant shows that they can perform the job without any issues and have all data exported according to the given instructions within a short period of time. 
Time efficiency is a very key aspect of this job, as I will need to have the data readily available and extracted within a very short amount of time. 
All skills and expertise when working with this sort of work as well as with Microsoft Excel &amp;amp;amp; Google Sheets will be taken into consideration as a plus and benefit all that choose to apply. 
With that being said Thank You and I look forward to working with you!
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Scraping,                     Google Docs,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 01:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Azure Function ETL Development - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Azure-Function-ETL-Development_%7E017d0b95b665fecbd1?source=rss</link>
    <description>We need an Azure Function to connect to an API, and get the data from the previous day, and insert this into our data warehouse which is a Azure SQL Database.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        .NET Core,                     API Development,                     Microsoft Azure App Services,                     C#,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     REST,                     Microsoft Windows Azure            Country: South Africaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 18:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need Support from Data Analyst - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-Support-from-Data-Analyst_%7E017ac07abc211e1e4a?source=rss</link>
    <description>CCS Data Analyst Role
CCS Fundraising, a strategic consulting firm serving the nonprofit sector, is searching for consultative support from a data analyst.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
The scope of the role at the outset will be tightly defined.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The analyst will work in MS Excel with a file containing:
1.	Select fields of constituent data from the client 
2.	Predictive modeling scores
3.	Data appends estimating net worth and philanthropic giving capacity
Utilizing this MS Excel file, the data analytics will explore the data and build a series of charts and tables to develop a report in MS PowerPoint.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Each report will contain series of core summary views of the data that will be consistent from report to report.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Additionally, each report will have a series of unique summary views of the data based on exploration and analysis.
Once the analyst is orientated to the format of the data and report structure, additional insights and deeper exploration to identify new findings and trends will be a valued skill set.
Skills needed:
1.	Strong analytical skills with the ability to collect, organize, analyze, and disseminate significant amounts of information with attention to detail and accuracy
2.	Ability to explore and explain varying types of data sets
3.	Experience with data mining and segmentation
4.	Story telling through data visualization
5.	Knowledge of statistics
Software requirements:
1.	Higher performer and user of Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint
2.	Tableau
Time and Schedule:
1.	Flexible scheduling is helpful
2.	Ability to turn around analysis timely and promptlyPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Quantitative Analysis
Skills:        Data Visualization,                     Exploratory Data Analysis,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft PowerPoint,                     Tableau Software            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 18:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Scraping required on Property Portals for Marketing Campaigns - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Scraping-required-Property-Portals-for-Marketing-Campaigns_%7E01b9a7e01d13bb6067?source=rss</link>
    <description>Our goal is to find the addresses of certain properties that are for sale on UK property portals. We want the data to be from specific postcodes and extracted on a monthly basis. 
We are looking for properties that meet any of the following criteria:
- Have been reduced in price
- On the portal for over 6 months
- On the portal with multiple agents
- Have the least number of views
- Contain keywords in the description such as &amp;#039;investor&amp;#039; or &amp;#039;no-chain&amp;#039; (A keyword list will be provided)
The addresses will then be entered into a spreadsheet which we will check over and upload to a mailing website - from where we can send out tailored marketing to these addresses encouraging them to sell their property via us. A flowchart is attached to show the process more clearly (with your part being green).
The portals will be Rightmove and Zoopla, however, they do not put information regarding the property number which is essential. We know how to find this information manually although it requires various websites/searches/checks - if there is a way to automate we&amp;#039;re open to suggestions.
We know how to do all of this manually, but we&amp;#039;d like to automate it and we lack the knowledge to do it ourselves. At this point, we&amp;#039;re just interested to see if this is possible and if so, we&amp;#039;re looking for somebody to work with long-term, ideally with good English and can offer creative solutions.
Happy to chat this over for anyone interested! I know a lot is still to be figured out.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Recruiter/ assistant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Recruiter-assistant_%7E014af2da141930d7e1?source=rss</link>
    <description>Technical Recruiter Job Description
The technical recruiter need not only to have the ability to realistically source, screen, and present qualified candidates, but the confidence to communicate unrealistic technical requirements goals to hiring managers. This is the technical recruiter&amp;rsquo;s profile description.
The areas of responsibilities/skills for the Technical Recruiter include:
Review. Successfully review job descriptions in to understand the needs of the hiring manager as well to ask questions that&amp;rsquo;ll help you identify the right candidate(s). This is by far the most important skill a technical recruiter needs.
Understand technology, technical roles and technical skills. Learn and evaluate your technical skills
Identify. Sourcing and uncovering candidates
Screen. Ascertaining the competence of candidates against a technical job description
Interview. Meeting candidates in person, telephone, or video conference etc to assess their qualifications
Following up. Keep your candidates in the loop. This goes a long way to build your credibility and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;keep your candidates either coming back to you or sending referrals to you. Read my article on following up with candidates and also why candidates are rude to their recruiters
Present. Showing or offering candidate resume to hiring managers to scrutinize or consider
The end result needs to be the presentation of employ-able and qualified candidates for technical positions in various industries and for job roles such as in software development, systems administration, database, architecture, business processes etc.
To carry out these tasks the technical recruiter needs the following skills:
Technology knowledge &amp;ndash; Ability to understand technology and to keep abreast of technology trends at client company. See more on technology knowledge
Confidence &amp;ndash; The ability to be comfortable in who one is.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know the know it, learn it and do not try to fake it. It may be off-putting to your candidate when you try to fake technical knowledge.
Maturity &amp;ndash; Recruiter level needs to equal or above that of the candidate ( an example is a new recruiter with about 6 months experience trying to recruit a Director of IT). That being said, nothing is impossible. Technical knowledge, confidence, and maturity make up for the lack of specific recruiter experience.
Inquisitiveness &amp;ndash; Being able to ask questions of your sales/account managers (agency recruiters), clients (hiring managers) and your candidates
Relationship Building &amp;ndash; Start every conversation with the intent to build, develop and maintain relationships with your candidates.
For effectiveness the IT Recruiter should:
Continue in a area of strength: An individual technical recruiter may work best when recruiting efforts are focused on job titles in similar levels and expertise. For instance a technical recruiter who is comfortable with recruiting system administrators, desktop support engineers and other job roles in similar categories may not be as effective if required to recruit at higher (lower) levels and job roles &amp;ndash; this is often a requirement in technical recruiter job descriptions. Patience becomes a great virtue for a recruiter who after working with software developers for a number of years is now required to recruit desktop support engineers.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is in no way disparaging either the recruiter or the candidate but only to highlight the fact that recruiters, just like any other working professional have areas of strength that should be harnessed.
It takes time to learn and understand the lingo and requirements of different technical job roles in order to become effectual.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A technical recruiter familiar with candidates at a certain level may require meaningful on-the-job-training time to gain the confidence required to start recruiting senior level IT professionals. The expectation that recruiters should be able to recruit candidates at all levels of IT is a recipe for failure. Technical recruiters may attempt to recruit at all levels, but may not produce great results. Some recruiters are better suited in entry level jobs, others consulting, others business process systems, executive levels etc.
Duties :
Source, screen, interview, and evaluate candidates
Foster long-term relationships with candidates
Review and understand technical job requirement requirements
Review applicants to verify if position requirements are met
Format resumes 
Research new technologies
Create detailed job descriptions
Follow up with candidates
Requirements for Technical Recruiter
Ability to build strong relationships
Ability to learn technical information
Self-confidence and self starter
Office automation tools (MS Office etc) for proofreading, editing and formatting
Good written and verbal communication skillsBudget: $100
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Human Resources
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Internet Research,                     LinkedIn Recruiting,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Recruiting,                     Sourcing,                     Technical Recruiter            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data and Spreadsheet Admin - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-and-Spreadsheet-Admin_%7E01bc5478c4d48aa770?source=rss</link>
    <description>We&amp;#039;re looking for somebody who is great with numbers&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;and using spreadsheets. We have large amounts of data which needs to be extracted from various platforms, sorted and analysed. 
Must be good on Excel and not be afraid of number crunching.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Other - Admin Support
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Spreadsheets,                     Statistical Analysis            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Analyst - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Analyst_%7E01463797429457bf87?source=rss</link>
    <description>We believe smarter and stronger cities emerge if they aggregate reliable data &amp;amp;amp; 
deploy effective data tools so as to inspire astute decision making. 
The ideal candidate for this position will be inspired by this initiative, can undertake data analysis, has an enthusiasm for learning new things, and can work in a fast-paced team environment. 
Responsibilities and duties:
- Research new sources of data products
- Write web scraping scripts
- Perform and automate ETL tasks
- Create and manipulate data tables within a database environment
- Support the work of team statisticians
- Deliver data tables to visualization experts upon request
- Assist to maintain online visualization library
Qualities:
- Curious
- Diligent
- Creative
- Collaborative &amp;ndash; we don&amp;rsquo;t care who&amp;rsquo;s right &amp;ndash; we care what&amp;rsquo;s right
Preferred Skills:
- ETL
- Data scraping
- HTML
- Python (numpy, pandas, sklearn, matplotlib, seaborn)
- SQL
- API experience
- Google AnalyticsPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        Data Analytics,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Internet Research,                     SQL,                     Web Scraping            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Findy.com - Typescript html dom data developer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Findy-com-Typescript-html-dom-data-developer_%7E01cb2594a2db72acbc?source=rss</link>
    <description>Full description under NDA
JOB SKILLS
Use existing private framework to build modules that make requests by http and extract data.
Required Skills:
TypeScript 2.8 - basic level (Use existing typings, understand compiler errors)
HTTP(S) - Understand how data travels between the web app and backend, meaning of headers, various request and response encodings, redirects
Chrome Developer Tools - Analyze requests made by web app, analyze html page structure
Fluent Russian
Good to have skills:
HTML
CSS4 selectors
Ramda - easy to learn if you know lodash
Software requirements:
Linux/macOS
Chrome Browser
http://nvm.sh/ for specific node and npm versionsBudget: $250
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        HTML5,                     TypeScript            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>proofreader&amp;amp;amp;editor needed for a fiction novel - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/proofreader-amp-editor-needed-for-fiction-novel_%7E015524bc99033842dc?source=rss</link>
    <description>we need one or more proofreader and editor to help get our novels ready to publish,(depending on how good work you render, if you provide us with great quality, we will trust you with possibly all our books) they are contemporary romance, reverse harem and mfmm themed novels with word counts of about 25,000-50,000.
we prefer to work in a docx formatï¼ŒAmerican style English, and for a 25,000-word book, we usually have a turnaround time of 4 days, 50,000, 1 week. 
for the proofreading, we require that you to professionally:
correct grammatical, typographical and punctuation mark errors
ensure chapter titles match the list of contents
Use symbols which are standard and recognized by printing and publishing companies
Rephrase written text to ensure document structure and content are consistent
Ensure project is completed within set time constraints.
for the editing, we require you: 
rewrite and edit copy to improve readability.
Verify facts, dates, and statistics, using standard reference sources.
Develop story or content ideas, considering reader or audience appeal. and etc.
paraphrase and revise the novel according to the suggestions attached in the script file.
we usually set 2 milestones, the first one being the first 10% of the book, the second milestone being the remaining 90%. if we are not completely satisfied with the first batch of your work, we won&amp;#039;t hesitate to drop and switch to other proofreaders.
PLEASE CHECK THE DEMO ATTACHED TO SEE THE STYLE OF THE NOVEL. and please message me with a bid in a $/1,000 formatBudget: $5
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Editing &amp;amp; Proofreading
Skills:        Editing,                     English Grammar,                     English Proofreading,                     English Punctuation,                     English Spelling,                     Writing            Country: Chinaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 12:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for Xero bookkeeper for social enterprise - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-Xero-bookkeeper-for-social-enterprise_%7E0169bbfb909a72c7a9?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi,
For our social enterprise (an e-commerce brand selling handmade rugs), we are looking for someone to become our bookkeeper / accountant. 
The role will develop and grow over time, but responsibilities include:
- Setting up Xero (incl. connection with HSBC Hong Kong)
- Doing all our bookkeeping
- Checking incoming invoices and preparing payments in HSBC 
- Creating weekly overviews of all orders that have come in&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
- Creating monthly financial reports of our business 
- Making a quarterly overview of European VAT that we need to pay
- Etc.
We are looking for someone who:
- Shares our passion for social enterprise and our products
- Has highly relevant work experience
- Can work independently and professionally 
- Has deep knowledge of accounting and bookkeeping 
- Is very precise and concise (working error-free)
- Is great with numbers and MS Excel
- Is a good communicator (mostly via e-mail)
- Is a nice person to work with! :)
You&amp;#039;ll report directly to one of the co-founders. 
Initially it will probably require around 15-20 hours per week (3-4 hours per working day). 
Thank you!
WouterPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Bookkeeping,                     Xero            Country: Netherlandsclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Sharepoint developer, designer for customization &amp;amp;amp; automation - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Sharepoint-developer-designer-for-customization-amp-automation_%7E01bb7a7121118dd3c1?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am a trainer and I want to use Sharepoint for collaboration with my students. Each training batch will have some students. And I should be able to collaborate with them. 
So I&amp;#039;m thinking of having some scripting done so that I input details of students, course timeline events, sub grouping details of students and script automatically creates training batch environment for collaboration with following specifications. 
0) Layout should be like this. 
	I) Main Training Batch Site Page -&amp;amp;gt; 
		a) Timeline on top, 
		b) then announcements only from me, 
		c) then 2 columns with left column for highlights of conversations of main site with stats of number of messages and number of files in document library and right column for highlights of conversations of sub-group site with stats of number of messages and number of files in that document library of 		sub group site. Highlights will also have last top 5 conversation titles. 
		d) then document library of files I shared with all students. 
		e) then document library of files shared by others with sorting of my approved from those files on top and unapproved files at the bottom. Here if files were shared 		within the sub group then they will not be visible here until I approve that file. Those shared files within sub group will 		only be visible to that sub group members and only in sub group section and page. 
	II) Sub Training Batch Site Collaboration Page (When clicked on right side column as mentioned in c) above -&amp;amp;gt; 
		a) Conversations on top and 
		b) document library at the bottom.
		This page will only be accessible by sub groups. Including the shared files. Shared files will only be visible outside the sub group page when I approve file, which will then be visible under Team Site Document Library where other&amp;#039;s shared files are shown.
	III) Main Training Batch Site Collaboration Page (When clicked on left side column as mentioned in c) above -&amp;amp;gt;
		a) Conversation on top and
		b) document library at the bottom. Both my document library and student&amp;#039;s shared files document library.
		This page will be accessible by all from that training batch. Including shared files in document library. Document Library of my shared files as well as Document library of student&amp;#039;s shared files will be visible here same like on main training batch site page.
I&amp;#039;ll upload the scope file separately. The character limit here is not allowing to copy paste the scope content.
Go through it and provide your fixed price quote in AUD or INR and with accurate time estimate.
Note this work is about Microsoft Sharepoint custom design and scripting allowing me to create designed sharepoint sites, subsites and environment as per scope.
You must have done such work before.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        .NET Core,                     Microsoft SharePoint Development,                     PHP,                     Microsoft SharePoint Designer            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 09:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry,Data Extracter - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-Data-Extracter_%7E01bc841fd59d6b2a71?source=rss</link>
    <description>Help me&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;develop a power point presentation that will be presented to 150 people . I will needed to verbally describe my ideas so you must have good communication skills in English and be OK with some ambiguity at the beginning of the project
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Data Mining,                     Data Scraping,                     Google Docs,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Virtual Assistant,                     WordPress            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 08:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a DevOps job support (Jenkins/aws); urgent 8686983983. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-DevOps-job-support-Jenkins-aws-urgent-8686983983_%7E01db6f0d76791e6421?source=rss</link>
    <description>It&amp;#039;s a new project and I am recently joined I need hourly basis or full time to resolve minor issues like deployment and junit test reports for code quality checkPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        AWS CloudTrail,                     DevOps,                     GitLab,                     Jenkins,                     Python Pandas            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 07:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Marketing Associate - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Marketing-Associate_%7E014cfe9d8dc0c8815a?source=rss</link>
    <description>** NOTE ** - I am looking for a virtual assistant who can work during Business Hours in the United States Pacific Time Zone
I want someone who can help with managing day-to-day activities related to pre-sales and online marketing. 
Job Tasks:
1.	Research and build a list of potential sales leads based on defined criteria using tools such as LinkedIn
2.	Research data (competitor or otherwise) to help with sales, market trends, forecasts, account analysis, etc.
3.	Assist with building a list of guest-bloggers, reporters and journalists for PR outreach.
4.	Assist with market and potential lead/customer research
5.	Assist with other online research oriented tasks.
6.	Create and maintain a project management calendar for each project
7.	Create and manage project timelines, tasks, assignments and providing regular progress reports
8.	Assigning article to writers using TextBroker or similar tool
9.	Perform project co-ordination work &amp;ndash; assign work to team members, follow up with team members and clients, get review/approvals from client, etc.
10.	Submitting work to the client for review.
11.	Image search* -- finding relevant images for blogs.
12.	Publish blogs on HubSpot*/Wordpress, etc.
13.	Post Social Media Updates for clients using HubSpot or similar tool.
14.	Send out email campaigns via HubSpot, Salesforce, or other email marketing tool.
15.	Prepare reports using HubSpot, Salesforce or other tools.
16.	Research and build a list of stories for blogs and social media marketing.
Requirements:
1. Must have access to internet and necessary software:
2.	Working knowledge of MS Office Suite of products - MS Word (Basic skills), MS Excel (Basic skills)
Soft Skills required:
1.	Good written and verbal communication skills and an eye for detail
2.	Professional attitude towards work and ability to work remotely with minimal supervision. 
3.	Must be highly organized and flexible enough for the start-up environment.
4.	Be a self-starter with good time management skills
Please submit your resume with information about your past experience in the field with your application.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Email Handling,                     Internet Marketing,                     Internet Research,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Project Management,                     Project Scheduling,                     Social Media Management,                     Social Media Marketing,                     Virtual Assistant,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 06:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Newsletter writer with Excel Knowledge - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Newsletter-writer-with-Excel-Knowledge_%7E01038f6a30d9fc987e?source=rss</link>
    <description>We require a freelancer to assist with a series of newsletter articles on Microsoft Excel. It is important that applications demonstrate strong written ability as well as MS Excel knowledge.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You will be explaining the use of Excel at beginner, intermediate and advanced levels so knowledge of using the program is very important.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Article &amp;amp; Blog Writing
Skills:        Copywriting,                     Microsoft Excel,                     SEO Writing,                     Writing            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 05:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>DevOps Lead - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/DevOps-Lead_%7E0177256e0a07201bb2?source=rss</link>
    <description>About hoolah
hoolah is a Singapore-based fintech company, that offers a zero-interest instalment omni-channel payment solution to retail and travel merchants. hoolah&amp;rsquo;s unique offering allows consumers to buy from merchants in four equal instalments over two months with no additional costs. Hoolah is seed-funded by several VCs and angels including AccelerAsia Ventures and iGlobe Partners. 
hoolah is an equal employment opportunity employer and welcomes people from all walks of life. Our office is in the heart of the CBD beside Tanjong Pagar MRT, with full amenities. As an outcomes-based business, you will manage your time yourself with a goal of achieving your targets in a timely, high-quality manner.
Role
We are currently seeking a DevOps Engineer to help elevate our payments platform to become the payment platform of choice for consumers and merchants in Asia. 
Ready for a challenge?
We are Singapore based but a distributed team. We build solutions&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;for Asia - no just one market. In this role you really can work where you want.
Responsibilities
* Work with the Technology Team to design, develop and deliver scalable and automated services and architecture - Infrastructure as code
* Architect, design, and implement solutions with AWS Services
* Automate software delivery pipelines for various applications and services
* Ensure full-stack software solutions are architected and delivered using industry-leading DevOps best practices and technologies (immutable infrastructure, infrastructure-as-code, version control on everything, self-healing applications)
* Collaborate to define best practices and standards around DevOps and service resilience
* Create reusable automation libraries that can be applied across the business
* Develop usage standards, user self-service designs, and reporting on application KPIs
* Participate in deep architectural discussions to ensure solutions are designed for successful deployment in the cloud
The Ideal Candidate
* Has 2-4 years of operating on large scale production environments (AWS required) or someone who has built and run highly available AWS environments.
* Deals well with ambiguous or undefined problems; ability to think abstractly and guide others
* Has the ability to articulate technical topics to non-technical audiences both in writing, in diagrams, and in person
* Has demonstrable knowledge of DevOps in an Enterprise setting, specifically within AWS.
* Preferably has AWS Services (EC2, Beanstalk, RDS, Lambda, ElasticCache), AWS Networking and Security, *nix Administration, Automation Tools (Terraform, Packer, Gradle, Jenkins) 
* Is an energetic team player who works well across the business and readily adapts to change
* Confident of your skills, abilities and willing to share what you know, while learning from others
* Has familiarity with working in a remote/distributed team.
If you want to engage brilliant minds in a true start-up environment where ideas are rewarded regardless of who they come from, join us. This is a rapidly changing space so if you thrive on ambiguity, are hungry for a challenge, and have the guts to speak your mind it could be a perfect fit.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon EC2,                     Amazon Neptune,                     Amazon Web Services,                     AWS Lambda            Country: Singaporeclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data Entry Specialist Required - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-Entry-Specialist-Required_%7E01b5fb909559b74df1?source=rss</link>
    <description>We need a data entry specialist who will be able to generate list of 100 leads per day from Facebook containing atleast 5 columns mentioning Company Name, Contact Person, Phone, Email, Facebook ID, etc.Budget: $25
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Data Extraction,                     Data Mining            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 22:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Help with a Java UDP file transfer program - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Help-with-Java-UDP-file-transfer-program_%7E016219a14d254cdc8f?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi,
You are writing a file server based from my UDPClient and UDPServer files. The client connects to the server, requests a file and the server sends the file in 100 byte chunks to the client. The client writes the chunks into a file. Each chunk is wrapped in a header and trailer to make a packet.
You need to write a couple of classes first &amp;ndash; one that creates a packet &amp;ndash; see the diagram on the specification. It creates a string of ~105 bytes, made up of the things in the diagram. Get the 100 bytes of data from the file you are sending to the client., calculate the checksum (use a any algorithm which produces 1 byte of checksum &amp;ndash; your choice), add the checksum and trailer to the packet and send. You can have a method to create the packet, a method to extract the data and a method the calculate or verify the checksum. Both the server and the client will use this class.
You also need a class to implement error correction and provide RTD (v. 2.2 or 3). At the receiver (client): That means you have methods that set or check the sequence number (if it&amp;rsquo;s repeated, drop the packet and request the other sequence number[send a NACK]); if it&amp;rsquo;s expected, process (extract, write data to file) and request the next packet. Send an ACK (the ack character) if the expected sequence number is received and the checksum you calculate matches the one ion the trailer) or send a NACK character if you get either the wrong sequence number or if the checksum is wrong). At the server, if you receive an ACK, delete the old sent packet and create the next one (flipping the sequence number). If you get a NACK, send the packeket again. If you date to implement RTD3, you need to add a timer which re-sends the packet if the timer expires before receiving an ACK or NACK.
I have been provided a newBridge class that simulates packet and Ack loss when both noLoss=false AckLoss=false. The UDP server must send a file to the client and the client must receive all packets fully and without error.
My deadline is Friday 2:00pm AEDT.
Thanks,
AntonioBudget: $90
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        Java            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 21:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Ads-op for programmatic marketing firm - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Ads-for-programmatic-marketing-firm_%7E018eb89641e5b34cc2?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are new, small digital marketing firm looking to fill a key role. 
We are looking for an online marketing manager, who will operate ad operations and ad analytics by optimizing existing and initiating future campaigns to ensure successful delivery of digital advertisements, and to maximize campaign performance.
Responsibilities:
* Ad Analytics &amp;amp;amp; Trafficking: Perform ongoing analysis of campaign performance using 1st &amp;amp;amp; 3rd party data, and execute on action oriented outcomes aimed at increasing revenue growth and other success metrics
*Aggregate daily/weekly/monthly reporting, and identify opportunities for reporting efficiency improvement
*Proactively detect any inconsistencies or issues with each campaign, underperformance, over pacing, or any other campaign-related metrics, and resolve them after consultation with the manager
*Ad Operations: Secure creative assets via in-house creative team
*Ad-setup and monitoring of assets via ad server technology
*Provide publishers with timely delivery of creative submission, and communicate in a professional manner
*Cost Control: Invoice verification and pre-processing for payment
*Work colaboratly with our creative head on designing webpages, funnels, email campaigns, etc..
*Close collaboration with the internet team and creative department for best possible online advertisement performance
*Assist with offline and cross-channel campaigns and other special projects as needed.
Qualifications: 
*Passion for online advertising media and understanding how travelers interact with display advertising
*Very tech-savvy; experience using ad servers and/or web analytics platforms
*Must be extremely proficient with Excel and Outlook, solid in PowerPoint and other MS Office applications
*A high level of accuracy and attention to detail while operating in a fast-paced, constantly evolving team environment
*Proven ability to analyze and optimize opportunities to maximize ROI
*A passion for continuous learning, technology and creative problem-solvingPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Display Advertising
Skills:        Analytics,                     Campaign Management,                     Media Buying            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 21:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Personal assistant for LinkedIn and WIX updates &amp;amp;amp; posts - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Personal-assistant-for-LinkedIn-and-WIX-updates-amp-posts_%7E01c5a3a37ba6ba4c2a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Personal assistant to help with LinkedIn and WIX updates &amp;amp;amp; posts.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Also must be good with MS Word and Excel.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Initially I have a number of articles from other sites copied and pasted to my blog with references.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;These titles also need to be put on my website with links to the blog post.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I also need my Linkedin page updated and I want weekly posts done and new articles related to databases.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; SMM - Social Media Marketing
Skills:        English Proofreading,                     Social Media Design            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 20:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Python/Django backend developer needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Python-Django-backend-developer-needed_%7E01cbe192e552adc899?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a backend developer in Python, Django and Excel. Yes, Excel.
Initially you will need to help with everyday tasks. Process Excel files, create sign in credentials, fix minor bugs in Django app, set up tracking scripts, etc. Most of this is automated for batch processing with in-house tools but still requires human control, and we need someone to update these tools and write new ones. You also need to help with setting up domains, SSL, etc. for our landing pages. So it&amp;#039;s kinda jack of all trades job.
As you become more familiar with the app, you can help with implementing new functions, migrating to new tech, updating to new versions of libraries we use, or just improve application quality by writing automated tests.
You will need to sign NDA as job includes working with personal data.
Requirements:
- Good English skills
- Good soft skills, you&amp;#039;ll have to communicate with the team a lot. A LOT.
- Python 3 (strictly 3)
- Django 1 (we plan to migrate to 2 but there are some blockers atm)
- PostgreSQL 10 knowledge, ability to write and understand raw SQL
- Careful and never crash production or make un-revertable database changes
- Always backup before doing dangerous things
- Decent knowledge of Excel
- Decent knowledge of DNS, SSL, HTTP, how web functions in general
- Git, Github and understand how to work with branches, releases, pull requests, etc.
Optional:
- PostGIS and working with geo data in general, understanding how coordinates, geometry and geography are stored and processed by machines
- Basic front-end, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to make usable UI for tools you and others use
- Docker
- HerokuPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Django,                     Microsoft Excel,                     PostgreSQL Programming,                     Python,                     SQL            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Airtable Chrome Extension Needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Airtable-Chrome-Extension-Needed_%7E012ff0ba2f6aedf996?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a Chrome EXT. that is able to connect data to Airtable
Must be able to look up and see if the record already exists in Airtable.
If record doesnt already exist it needs to be able to pull relevant data into a new Airtable card.
Example of some fields:
URL
First Name
Last Name
Company 
Email Address
Phone
etc.
Please provide hourly rate, ETA, and sample of a similiar project you have worked on.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        Chrome Extension,                     Data Extraction            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Automated billing process - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Automated-billing-process_%7E0168735953e019cfd2?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking to automate our billing process. I would like to using the Rossini&amp;rsquo;s API and google drive to automatically read PDFs invoices and extract the data into a cvs and then use the QuickBooks sdk for desktop to batch enter the payables into QuickBooks. I would need to be able to add data to the cvs file to code the payables.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Courseware Management System - Design and Build using MS Dynamic! - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Courseware-Management-System-Design-and-Build-using-Dynamic_%7E0142d616a5a500c8d6?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for a MS Dynamic developer/designer to built one of the most robust and comprehensive Courseware Management System. High level design document in excel format is included with this posting. This will be a cloud based application and I will provide and clarify any details based on the attached document.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        ASP.NET,                     Microsoft Dynamics Development,                     Microsoft SQL Server Reporting Services            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>AutoLISP developer needed for custom tool to write and extract data - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/AutoLISP-developer-needed-for-custom-tool-write-and-extract-data_%7E017d27b345bf0df69d?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking to build a custom AutoLISP tool that will automate the process of labeling items in our shop drawings and recording that information in an external database.
The tool will ideally be an interactive script which is capable of recording and retrieving multiple pieces of data from user input and from drawing elements selected by the user, recording that data in an external database, synthesizing data from the external database and user input, and creating MTEXT objects in the drawing.
Currently, the exact nature of the external database is unknown. In the long term, we expect to use an SQL or Access database, but at the moment CSV or XLS files might be a stopgap solution. We are eager to begin work on this project even before this uncertainty is settled.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Engineering &amp;amp; Architecture &amp;gt; 3D Modeling &amp;amp; CAD
Skills:        AutoLISP            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior Geospatial Data Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-Geospatial-Data-Engineer_%7E01a444f0f826fa6c17?source=rss</link>
    <description>This is a full-time role in Downtown Houston, Texas.
You must be willing to relocate full-time or commute weekly to Houston.
You must show experience coding and automating end-to-end spatial data ETL pipelines.
You must be able to start work full time no more than 4 weeks after an offer is accepted.
Do not apply to this job if any of the three statements above are not true for you.
We will consider sponsoring candidates who are already eligible to work in the U.S. if you live in or will relocate to Houston.
Overview
Sourcewater, Inc. (www.sourcewater.com), based in downtown Houston, provides water market intelligence to the upstream energy industry, the first-ever Internet water marketplace, and other oilfield water data analytics and optimization services. We are inventing the data science to answer complex questions in the energy industry and the widely-recognized leader in oilfield water data services.
We are seeking a Senior Geospatial Data Engineer with outstanding technical and optimization skills to create and lead the design and implementation of our database architecture and data pipelines as we expand our analytics capabilities to tackle complex market intelligence challenges. You are a methodical high performer with a passion for efficiency, and accuracy, and wrangling complex data at high velocity. You specialize in architecting geospatial databases, automating geospatial ETL, designing and implementing frameworks to manage complex workflows, and monitoring data quality. You are excited about the opportunity to create and lead industry-defining data architecture, collection, automation and analytical systems.
What you&amp;rsquo;ll do
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Architect our spatial databases
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Design, develop, and support our data infrastructure to process diverse geospatial data, using technologies such as SQL, Python, and AWS.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Design, build and deploy automated GTL/ETL pipelines that are scalable, efficient, reliable, fault-tolerant, and easy to operate.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Work with geospatial and market data from multiple sources, such as state government regulatory data, satellite imagery, our online marketplace, and outbound data collection programs.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Enhance, standardize, and join different data sets to achieve data science and analytics objectives.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Research and build efficient and scalable data storage and retrieval systems that enable interactive reporting on high dimensional data.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Optimize processing times and deliver information in real time.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Build libraries and frameworks to empower the team to work effectively with our data.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Collaborate with our team to create solutions for diagnostic and predictive analytics.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Work with team members to prioritize tasks and ensure that assigned projects are completed on schedule and with strong attention to detail.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Maintain accurate, complete, and current documentation.
What we&amp;rsquo;re looking for
Requirements
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proven experience architecting complex spatial databases
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proven experience developing efficient, scalable end-to-end data pipelines
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Expert knowledge of data integration/conflation and spatial ETL processes
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with scripting for ETL development and automation; obsessed with optimizing data transfer and ETL
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience in the development and implementation of data warehouses, including architecture and infrastructure
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Advanced knowledge of a programming languages such as Python, Java, or Scala
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Proven experience at an expert level with PostgreSQL and PostGIS and query optimization
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Enjoy working with all kinds of data, including clean, dirty, unstructured, semi-structured, relational, and geospatial
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Advanced geo-processing knowledge
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Understanding of NoSQL, Spark, Hadoop, Elasticsearch
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with AWS RDS
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Familiarity with graphical spatial ETL tools such as FME
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Familiarity with data science and frontend development tools and processes
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience supporting self-service reports using tools such as Tableau, Power BI, Spotfire, etc.
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience with tools such as Git, Jenkins, Jira, IntelliJ
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s with equivalent experience
You are
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A high performer with a strong customer service orientation and an optimistic personality
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Naturally meticulous, with a passion for process optimization
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Always learning and developing new skills
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Logical, efficient, and flexible
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Highly self-motivated and proactive
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A collaborator
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Able to exercise independent judgment and act on it
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Adept at prioritizing and executing while under pressure
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Energized by a fast-paced environment where collaboration is key and focus can change frequently
&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excited about the opportunities and challenges of working at a startup in Houston, ready to bring your resourcefulness and drive to do amazing work with an amazing teamPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Extraction / ETL
Skills:        Amazon Web Services,                     Data Engineering,                     Data Warehousing,                     &amp;quot;Extract, Transform and Load (ETL)&amp;quot;,                     Geospatial,                     PostGIS,                     PostgreSQL Administration,                     PostgreSQL Programming            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Simple Data Extraction from Website - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Simple-Data-Extraction-from-Website_%7E015f87aa0f40bd1d60?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking to collect information on people attending an event. Their contact information is listed on the website and must be copied into a spreadsheet. There is a daily limit on the number of emails we can view, but we have three separate accounts to use each day until the job is complete. I will provide a template on what information we&amp;#039;d like to have from the website.Budget: $75
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Big data analytics needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Big-data-analytics-needed_%7E01a9bcb6d1059c1811?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a huge database of user ways within the app.
I need to extract the ways which leads to purchases. I need to find cases. Common things. Dependencies. Number of launches before buying. Such kind of things. The more data you can extract the more usefull it will be. If you&amp;#039;ll be able to visualize data it it would be great. But it will enough to provide most common user ways which leads to purchases. Percentiles. Etc.
the data looks like the attachBudget: $100
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Other - Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics
Country: Russiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 10:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>data entry copy write - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/data-entry-copy-write_%7E01cc28648d1e5c60e8?source=rss</link>
    <description>i have a excellent knowledge of ms excel with excellent typing speed.i can assist you with any kind of data entry work.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;data entry copy write and trannscriptionBudget: $9
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Writing &amp;gt; Copywriting
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Word,                     Writing            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need a virtual Assistant (long term) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-virtual-Assistant-long-term_%7E01b515f86b7daf129d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Social Gain Marketing is looking for a virtual assistant with Social Media knowledge to complete clerical projects that are anticipated to require around 5-10 hours per week. The work will include the following tasks:
âƒ	Respond to emails and phone calls
âƒ	Schedule meetings
âƒ	Manage a contact list
âƒ	Prepare customer spreadsheets and keep online records 
âƒ	Organize manager&amp;rsquo;s calendars 
âƒ	Create presentations, as assigned
Following Skills are a must:
âƒ	Proven experience as a Virtual Assistant or relevant role
âƒ	Great communication skills via phone, email, and chat
âƒ	Solid organizational skills
âƒ	Excellent time management skills
âƒ	Excellent phone, email and instant messaging communication skills 
âƒ	Knowledge of online calendars and scheduling (e.g. Google Calendar)
âƒ	Experience with word-processing software and spreadsheets (e.g. MS Office)Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Data Entry,                     Email Handling,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 02:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Sales and Marketing - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Sales-and-Marketing_%7E015999245377d43098?source=rss</link>
    <description>Bus Conversion Magazine - Sales Representative Position 
Bus Conversion Magazine has established itself as an authority in the arena of bus conversion publications for the past 26 years.
Not only does it provide interesting topics about bus conversions, but it also features information about events taking place in the converted bus world, therefore giving its readers a heads up on how to convert and repair their buses with access to the right information. 
We are currently looking for a results driven sales representative to actively seek out and engage prospects. You will provide complete and appropriate solutions for every advertiser in order to boost top line revenue, growth and profitability.
Responsibilities:
&amp;bull;	Present, promote and sell Bus Conversion Magazine&amp;rsquo;s digital advertisements using solid arguments to existing and prospective customers
&amp;bull;	Establish, develop and maintain positive business and customer relationships
&amp;bull;	Reach out to customer leads through cold calling
&amp;bull;	Expedite the resolution of customer concerns to maximize satisfaction
&amp;bull;	Achieve agreed upon sales goals and outcomes within schedule
&amp;bull;	Coordinate sales efforts with publisher and office team members 
&amp;bull;	Analyze the market&amp;rsquo;s potential and track sales 
&amp;bull;	Supply management with reports on customer needs, problems, interests, competitive activities, and potential for new products and services
&amp;bull;	Keep abreast of best practices and promotional trends
&amp;bull;	Continuous quality improvement through feedback 
Requirements:
&amp;bull;	Proven work experience as a sales representative
&amp;bull;	Excellent knowledge of MS Office Outlook, Excel, and Word
&amp;bull;	Highly motivated and target driven with a proven track record in sales
&amp;bull;	Excellent selling, communication and negotiation skills
&amp;bull;	Prioritizing, time management and organizational skills
&amp;bull;	Ability to create and deliver presentations tailored to the audience needs
&amp;bull;	Relationship management skills and openness to feedback
This is an independent contractor, freelance, commission only position. Bus Conversion Magazine offers a competitive commission plan, with a potential annual salary of $40,000 to $60,000, working flexible hours. Home office required.Budget: $50,000
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Display Advertising
Skills:        Sales Strategy            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Amazon PPC Expert / Specialist Needed - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Amazon-PPC-Expert-Specialist-Needed_%7E0137e12efb0047328b?source=rss</link>
    <description>Amazon PPC Manager Responsibilities
Include:
* Launching and optimizing PPC campaigns
* Monitoring budgets and overseeing search platform accounts
* Tracking KPIs and producing useful reports for management
Job brief
We are looking for a PPC (Pay Per Click) Manager to run PPC campaigns and monitor paid search budgets.
In this role, you should be well-versed in principles of search engine marketing (SEM) including search engine optimization (SEO.) You should also be analytical and good with numbers.
Your goal will be to ensure our online marketing efforts have the highest possible return on investment (ROI.)
Responsibilities
* Participate in forming effective paid search strategies
* Launch and optimize various PPC campaigns
* Oversee accounts on search platforms (e.g. Google AdWords, Bing)
* Be involved in keyword selection and audience targeting
* Monitor budget and adjust bids to gain better ROI
* Track KPIs to assess performance and pinpoint issues
* Produce reports for management (e.g. dashboards)
* Write attractive and concise copy for adverts
* Suggest and develop new campaigns across multiple channels
* Maintain partnerships with PPC ad platforms and vendors
* Find ways to reduce risk of click fraud
* Keep abreast of PPC and SEM trends
Requirements
* Proven experience as a PPC Manager or&amp;nbsp;Digital Marketing Specialist
* Experience in data analysis and reporting
* Knowledge of SEO and digital marketing concepts
* Familiarity with multiple platforms (e.g. AdWords, Facebook, Yahoo) is preferred
* Working knowledge of analytics tools (Google Analytics, Tableau, WebTrends etc.)
* Understanding of HTML and XML is a plus
* Proficient in MS Office (particularly Excel)
* Excellent communication skills
* Analytical thinking with strong math skillsPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; SEM - Search Engine Marketing
Skills:        Amazon PPC,                     Internet Marketing,                     Pay Per Click,                     Search Engine Marketing (SEM),                     SEO Keyword Research            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 20:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Jenkins developer needed to support a Jenkins Cloud plugin. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Jenkins-developer-needed-support-Jenkins-Cloud-plugin_%7E012862a1d021fb6a69?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for support / pair programming partner for Jenkins Plugin Cloud API.
I am developing a Jenkins Cloud Plugin. But I am not familiar with the Jenkins Plugin API for Cloud.
I am looking for somebody that helps me doing the first steps.
I am a (good) Java developer with some experience developing Jenkins plugins. But not familiar with the specifics related to the Jenkins Cloud API.
I am looking for a experienced Jenkins Plugin developer that has already developed a Cloud Plugin. You have to know the specifics of &amp;amp;quot;hudson.slaves.Cloud&amp;amp;quot; and how to start/stop slaves dynamically.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Groovy,                     Java,                     Jenkins            Country: Germanyclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>CREATE MICROSOFT ACCESS FILE AND IMPORT JSON DATA - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/CREATE-MICROSOFT-ACCESS-FILE-AND-IMPORT-JSON-DATA_%7E018f1311f6af82fc0e?source=rss</link>
    <description>I have a 1GB JSON file and need to convert the data with over 1.8Million records into an access database.
I will supply the JSON file, I just need you to send back the MS Access file in table format.
Attached is a small example of the file structure.
Please reply with &amp;amp;quot;I can convert&amp;amp;quot; at the top of your proposal. All other proposals will be ignored.Budget: $50
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Machine Learning
Skills:        Access VBA,                     Excel VBA,                     JSON,                     Microsoft Access Administration            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 11:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>$500 monthly, Data Entry - accounting assistant - Ukraine / E Europe - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/500-monthly-Data-Entry-accounting-assistant-Ukraine-Europe_%7E01cbc2bf93e650d9a5?source=rss</link>
    <description>** This job is for those in Ukraine only **
This is a Data Entry position
- Must be able to work at least 35 hours a week, more time is possible
- pat is $500 USD monthly
- Times are flexible, must be able to communicate with company during United States morning hours, with notice beforehand
- Chats will be held using text chat, not verbal / phone
- MS Excel required
- Light MS Excel experience preferred
- Accounting experience a plus, not required
To start:
We have a test job, that is one hour max
If interested please message me, and we can start the test jobPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Skills:        Accounting,                     Accounts Payable Management            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 07:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Associate - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Associate_%7E01b62f5990a0f9343c?source=rss</link>
    <description>Job Description:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Peak Support is a customer service and business process outsourcing company.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are seeking Email/Chat/Phone Support representatives from the Philippines to join our growing team.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Some requirements for this position:
- Strong verbal and written English skills 
- Someone who enjoys working with others on a team
- Experience in a Customer Support environment
- Vast Experience in Email/Chat Support 
- Research-oriented and Process-Oriented
- Can work with minimal supervision
- Above Average MS Excel Skills
Technical Requirements:
- Good computer setup with Chrome browser
- minimum of 8gb RAM
- minimum processor:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;i5 4th Generation, AMD A8 5000 series, or higher
- Stable high-speed internet connection (at least 5-10 Mbps) 
- A stable power supply in your area&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
- Noise cancellation headset 
- Skype accountPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Customer Service &amp;gt; Customer Service
Skills:        Customer Service,                     English,                     English Grammar,                     Salesforce.com            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>DevOps and SRE Engineer using Kubernetes - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/DevOps-and-SRE-Engineer-using-Kubernetes_%7E015860776bdf3c12b8?source=rss</link>
    <description>REQUIRED: Can demo in production like environment
Kubernetes/Docker
Rancher
Helm
AWS, GCP, and Azure
Jenkins
New Relic, etc. 
Terraform, Ansible, Saltstack, etc. 
-Microservices
Preferred:
Prior experience developing a PaaS
Node.js
Java (Spring)
SQL/NoSQLPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Ansible,                     AWS ECS,                     DevOps,                     Docker,                     Jenkins,                     Kubernetes,                     Microservices,                     Network Administration,                     Rancher,                     SaltStack            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 17:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Customer Service Oncall Supervisor - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Customer-Service-Oncall-Supervisor_%7E018064bd8e2bce02e2?source=rss</link>
    <description>DELSUITES, a division of TRIDEL, is a young and dynamic company rapidly growing to become the largest and most highly recognized corporate housing provider in Toronto, Canada. DelSuites manages extended stay furnished condominiums as a hotel-alternative in residential buildings across Toronto, please visit www.delsuites.com. 
General duties include, but are not limited to: 
&amp;bull;	Supervise 2 Upwork Customer Service Oncall Team members on a day to basis.
&amp;bull;	Scope of work will include interviewing and hiring.
&amp;bull;	Train 2 Upwork Customer Service Oncall Team.
&amp;bull;	Plan work for 2 Upwork Customer Service Oncall team members.
&amp;bull;	To manage a busy inbox and ensure all e-mail filing is up-to-date.
&amp;bull;	To respond to and manage reservation requests via e-mail, phone, 3rd party websites and the website.
&amp;bull;	To be fully conversant with all services and facilities offered by DelSuites, and to have the ability to sell the DelSuites difference to prospective clients/guests.
&amp;bull;	To promptly follow up on client/guest comments and complaints.
&amp;bull;	Respond to Client request using Bold Chat.
&amp;bull;	Respond to all after hour reservation calls.
&amp;bull;	Respond to all Inhouse Guest Calls.
&amp;bull;	Respond to all emergency calls.
&amp;bull;	Trouble shoot all duty managers calls.
Qualifications
&amp;bull; MUST have good command in spoken English with clear accent. 
&amp;bull; MUST have Supervisory experience. 
&amp;bull; MUST own all necessary equipment: computer with Windows 10, digital camera &amp;amp;amp; microphone. 
&amp;bull; MUST have&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;a Download minimum speed of 25 Mbps and Upload minimum speed of 15 Mbps
&amp;bull;MUST have good 
&amp;bull; Must have UPS or Generator to have 100% electricity and connectivity at all times.
&amp;bull; Minimum of 3 years&amp;rsquo; experience in international virtual customer service
&amp;bull; High school graduation required
&amp;bull; Superior communication skills - verbal and written
&amp;bull; Results oriented and can work in a fast paced environment
&amp;bull; Proven track record of customer service excellence
&amp;bull; Strong MS Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, Powerpoint) experience 
&amp;bull; Ability to learn quickly and navigate in a multi-application environment
&amp;bull; Highly analytical with a high degree of attention to detail to ensure 100% accuracy in all 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;transactions
&amp;bull; Type 30 WPM.
&amp;bull; Highly developed sense of integrity and commitment to customer satisfaction.
&amp;bull; Excellent interpersonal and organizational skills, ability to multi-task.
&amp;bull; High personal standard of excellence, sense of urgency and demonstrated initiative.
&amp;bull; Work effectively with limited need for direction or supervision.
&amp;bull; Willingness to be a self-learner and take full ownership of work
&amp;bull; Flexible work style to accommodate changing priorities with ability to meet deadlines is 
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;essential.
&amp;bull; Flexibility to work overtime to meet business and departmental requirements.
**Maximum $1000 USD per month, 12 days paid vacation, yearly bonus.
** Work schedule Monday to Friday 4:30 PM EST to 12:30 AM EST or 12:30 EST to 9:30 ESTPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Customer Service &amp;gt; Customer Service
Skills:        Administrative Support,                     Chat Support,                     Customer Experience,                     Customer Support,                     Email Handling,                     Hospitality,                     Management Skills,                     Phone Support,                     Telephone Handling,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>V.A. needed for site, data entry, send emails, web scraping, SEO, creating and posting content. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/needed-for-site-data-entry-send-emails-web-scraping-SEO-creating-and-posting-content_%7E010f0006e8be38d5ef?source=rss</link>
    <description>Web scrape and clean lists in .xls format.
Create, edit, and prep new content in Html for posting and emailing marketing.
Content posting on social media sites and website
Web research and scraping of relevant info.
This is a job for someone who understands web scraping (Parsehub, web scraper, for example.), list management and databasing in Excel, mass email marketing, and social media marketing. 
Detailed oriented person needed. CONSISTENT. Must be skilled in office applications (Google, MS), web development (wordpress), and able to communicate with team leader via IP phone for activity review and revision. 
We&amp;#039;re a new company with Big ideas and would love to have you be a part of the team. Looking forward to hearing from you.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        CSS,                     Data Entry,                     HTML5,                     Internet Marketing,                     Internet Research,                     Search Engine Optimization (SEO),                     Web Scraping,                     WordPress            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 17:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Data entry - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Data-entry_%7E018a58d9a6970d6545?source=rss</link>
    <description>One day to one&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;week to data entry from website into ms excellBudget: $100
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Database Administration
Skills:        Data Entry,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Virtual Assistant            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 05:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Virtual Office Administrative Assistant needed for Ecommerce Business - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Virtual-Office-Administrative-Assistant-needed-for-Ecommerce-Business_%7E010d4831133062b5e7?source=rss</link>
    <description>The Virtual Office Administrative Assistant position is a satellite/home based position.
Minimum Technical Skills: Experience working with eCommerce brands and customer service jobs, familiar or expert at MS office MS word, Excel, Powerpoint, and Google products/apps.
MUST BE Fluent in reading and writing English to apply for this job.
Minimum Technical requirements: the applicant should have a Computer/laptop, MS office installed, Internet access, Google Drive for PC, and a headset with microphone.
Responsibilities:
We&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone who is fluent in English - We need a minimum of 80% fluency level.
Answer customer service request emails in a timely manner 
Must be able to handle customer concerns or questions
Give customers updates on their orders by making sure their order is on the way using their tracking number, and then follow up and give them the tracking number.
Must be able to calm down angry customers who are asking for a refund
Handle Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence Mail and Email
Experience with Shopify&amp;rsquo;s backend to lookup customer information
Ability to stay calm and keep customers calm while their order is on its way
Use techniques and creativity to help calm customers down and turn a customer service request into a sale, and keep the customer happy
Please answer the following questions below with as much detail as you can:
1. Where are you from? Which city? Country? Time zone? What is it like where you live? Describe in as much detail as possible.
2. How accessible is a computer and internet access to you?
3. What are your preferred methods of communication?
4. Tell me about a professional setting you&amp;rsquo;ve worked in where people had different communication styles.
5. Let&amp;rsquo;s say your inbox is flooded with messages. How do you prioritize which ones to respond to first?
6. Let&amp;rsquo;s say you have a deadline and your computer suddenly crashes. What do you do?
7. Tell me about a time you proactively addressed a client&amp;rsquo;s need. 
8. What are your hobbies outside of your job? What do you like to do with your free time?
9. What is your biggest goal in life right now?
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve answered those questions with detail, please respond to the following final qualification:
Describe the job that you will be doing and why you are the best candidate for this position with as much detail as possible in 10 sentences minimum.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 23:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Financial Advisor Assistant - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Financial-Advisor-Assistant_%7E01e74b347e7f5cb092?source=rss</link>
    <description>Seeking long term, part-time, virtual assistant for financial advisor serving multi-generational families.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Must pass criminal and credit back ground check and be fingerprinted!! Will assist with on boarding new clients, opening accounts, CRM maintenance, social media management, transcribe meeting notes, document scanning, schedule meetings, and archiving statements and documents.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Must be proficient with MS Word, Excel and Power Point.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Will prepare client reports &amp;amp;amp; presentations in financial planning software. Will maintain records for compliance, advertising and monthly logs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Must be extremely customer service oriented, organized, with attention to detail and excellent phone etiquette.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Must be able to compose letters and client communications with impeccable grammar and punctuation.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Assisting families and their love ones with their goals and finances requires signing a confidentiality agreement and the ability to maintain a kind and professional attitude at all times.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Must be a motivated, self starter.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Will also be responsible for projects, documenting processes and work flows.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Will assist in marketing and branding design projects.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Content Writing,                     Customer Service,                     DocuSign,                     Email Handling,                     eMoney Advisor emX,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Outlook            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 21:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Billing Specialist (USA or CanadÃ¡) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Billing-Specialist-USA-Canad_%7E01e50a81225d0e9689?source=rss</link>
    <description>Receiving and sorting incoming payments with attention to credibility
Managing the status of accounts and balances and identifying inconsistencies
Issuing bills, receipts and invoices
Job brief
We are looking for a competent Billing specialist to undertake a variety of financial and non-financial tasks in order to help guarantee the company&amp;rsquo;s revenues. You will handle the processing of incoming payments along with the issuing of necessary paperwork.
Responsibilities
Assume the responsibility of receiving and sorting incoming payments with attention to credibility
Manage the status of accounts and balances and identify inconsistencies
Issue and post bills, receipts and invoices
Check the validity of debit accounts
Update accounts receivable database with new accounts or missed payments
Ensure all clients remain informed on their outstanding debts and deadlines
Provide solutions to any relative problems of clients
Write thorough reports on billing activity with clear and reliable data
Requirements
Proven experience as billing specialist
Adherence to laws and best practices in regards to dealing with customers and data
Comfortable dealing with numbers and the processing of financial information
Excellent knowledge of MS Office (particularly Excel) and ER software (JDE or other)
Proficiency in English
Results-driven and patient
High degree of attention to detail and trustworthiness
BSc degree in Finance, Accounting or BABudget: $5,000
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Accounting &amp;amp; Consulting &amp;gt; Accounting
Country: Brazilclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch job management utility development. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-job-management-utility-development_%7E011e1b511b174a21d5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for a developer with skills in C#, SQL database and web browser interface.
The project involves developing&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;a batch job management&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;utility.
We have a Microsoft SQL Server database with a list of jobs that need to be started,
monitored and reported. The database has a basic winform interface. We have updated
the database and plan to use webui based interface.
Project involves 
1. creating webui forms for interaction with this database. We expect 7 different forms needed
to manage inputs for the database.
2. Write new SQL functions to support reports and status generation. Reports will be both tables and charts. We expect 6-7 reports to be generated with table and charts.
3. Create batch job commands, launch, monitor and report status on webui..
We are looking for a developer with experience in
SQL, C# and web development with charting functions.
Will provide a detailed design document once candidate is selected.
We will provide the database script to selected candidate along with winform snippet.Budget: $150
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        .NET Framework,                     C#,                     HTML5,                     Microsoft SQL CE            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 07:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Python code to upload data from Excel to MS SQL (follow-up: build Django app) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Python-code-upload-data-from-Excel-SQL-follow-build-Django-app_%7E01fb77dead53fc50b6?source=rss</link>
    <description>**Caveats &amp;ndash; please read first**
1.	Although this project is narrowly focused around one task, what you build here will be part of a full-blown web application with which we&amp;#039;ll also need help. And we&amp;#039;d like to keep working with the same person or team all the way. For this reason, in addition to qualifications determined by this project, we need someone with demonstrated success developing Django apps working with MS SQL server on AWS. The app will be fairly basic, for internal use only, and we&amp;#039;ll make it as easy as possible to develop it, but nonetheless we need someone who did it before.
2.	Once deployed, this web app will be a mission-critical component of our business, and so, in a way, will be person who built it. For this reason, continuity is very important. Ideally, we&amp;#039;d prefer a team. An individual freelancer will be considered if he has at least 3 years&amp;#039; worth of consistent (full-time) experience and reasonable expectation of availability in the future (e.g. we don&amp;rsquo;t need a current student who will graduate and get a full-time job in 6 months).
**Specification**
We enter financial data into Excel (3-4 years&amp;#039; worth of quarterly data for&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;~130 metrics for ~1000 companies) and need a script which will upload it to MS SQL DB. &amp;amp;quot;Metric&amp;amp;quot; refers to a financial metric such as revenue, total debt etc., a scalar value with 2 decimal places. Excel file has metrics in rows and quarters in columns. Quarters are strings (e.g. &amp;amp;quot;Sep&amp;#039;18&amp;amp;quot;) with no datetime characteristics and are not aligned for all companies (most companies report Mar, Jun, Sep, Dec, others can do Jan, Apr, Jul, Oct). DB is already built, with schema matching Excel sheets but transposed, i.e. DB has metrics in columns, and every quarter will be a row. You will be able to tweak DB schema and interface, if needed. DB will be on AWS.
The reason we need a custom script, as opposed to using off-the-shelf SQL functionality, is that we need to add some conflict-resolution logic. Roughly speaking, once the data is uploaded from Excel, every time we try to change it, this system, let&amp;#039;s call it &amp;amp;quot;bridge&amp;amp;quot;, should throw a warning and require the user to enter a comment as to why the change is made. Two examples help clarify this:
Normal scenario: company A reports quarterly financial results, we create a new *column* in Excel and manually type in about 20 metrics, and the bridge uploads this first batch. This creates a new *row* in DB with new unique ID (say ID 1). Usually within a week or so, the company files full report with ~130 metrics, and our data provider fills them in the same Excel book (fully populating the column which we manually created a week before). This is the second, and almost always, final, upload &amp;ndash; with initial 20 metrics potentially overwritten and new ~110 ones added. When this second batch gets pushed to DB, it creates a new row (say ID = 2), and row with ID1 gets deactivated (via a boolean field). Since time delta between row 2 and row 1 does not exceed threshold of say 10 days, the bridge simply pushes up the data without regard to existing values.
Exception scenario: while researching company B, we find out that it had made an acquisition 5 months ago, such that its financial condition is affected, so we need to adjust historical data for the company. In Excel, we change 10 metrics for each of the most recent and previous 4 quarters. Since time delta for at least one of target columns exceeds threshold, the bridge shows an error and requires the user to enter a comment. The bridge creates 5 new rows, deactivates 5 old ones (via boolean field) and adds user comment to the deactivated rows. Note that all conflicts pertaining to the same ticker within the same time period (all changes to Q1&amp;#039;18, for example), will be collapsed into one warning and comment.
The bridge works one way &amp;ndash; only upload.
If more information is needed, don&amp;#039;t hesitate to ask.
**Deliverables**
A Python class (compatible with 3.6), with complete docstrings and with full test coverage (pytest).Budget: $600
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        AWS CodeDeploy,                     Django,                     Microsoft SQL Server Programming,                     Python            click to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Python code to upload data from Excel to MS SQL (follow-up: build Django app) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Python-code-upload-data-from-Excel-SQL-follow-build-Django-app_%7E01fb77dead53fc50b6?source=rss</link>
    <description>**Caveats &amp;ndash; please read first**
1.	Although this project is narrowly focused around one task, what you build here will be part of a full-blown web application with which we&amp;#039;ll also need help. And we&amp;#039;d like to keep working with the same person or team all the way. For this reason, in addition to qualifications determined by this project, we need someone with demonstrated success developing Django apps working with MS SQL server on AWS. The app will be fairly basic, for internal use only, and we&amp;#039;ll make it as easy as possible to develop it, but nonetheless we need someone who did it before.
2.	Once deployed, this web app will be a mission-critical component of our business, and so, in a way, will be person who built it. For this reason, continuity is very important. Ideally, we&amp;#039;d prefer a team. An individual freelancer will be considered if he has at least 3 years&amp;#039; worth of consistent (full-time) experience and reasonable expectation of availability in the future (e.g. we don&amp;rsquo;t need a current student who will graduate and get a full-time job in 6 months).
**Specification**
We enter financial data into Excel (3-4 years&amp;#039; worth of quarterly data for&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;~130 metrics for ~1000 companies) and need a script which will upload it to MS SQL DB. &amp;amp;quot;Metric&amp;amp;quot; refers to a financial metric such as revenue, total debt etc., a scalar value with 2 decimal places. Excel file has metrics in rows and quarters in columns. Quarters are strings (e.g. &amp;amp;quot;Sep&amp;#039;18&amp;amp;quot;) with no datetime characteristics and are not aligned for all companies (most companies report Mar, Jun, Sep, Dec, others can do Jan, Apr, Jul, Oct). DB is already built, with schema matching Excel sheets but transposed, i.e. DB has metrics in columns, and every quarter will be a row. You will be able to tweak DB schema and interface, if needed. DB will be on AWS.
The reason we need a custom script, as opposed to using off-the-shelf SQL functionality, is that we need to add some conflict-resolution logic. Roughly speaking, once the data is uploaded from Excel, every time we try to change it, this system, let&amp;#039;s call it &amp;amp;quot;bridge&amp;amp;quot;, should throw a warning and require the user to enter a comment as to why the change is made. Two examples help clarify this:
Normal scenario: company A reports quarterly financial results, we create a new *column* in Excel and manually type in about 20 metrics, and the bridge uploads this first batch. This creates a new *row* in DB with new unique ID (say ID 1). Usually within a week or so, the company files full report with ~130 metrics, and our data provider fills them in the same Excel book (fully populating the column which we manually created a week before). This is the second, and almost always, final, upload &amp;ndash; with initial 20 metrics potentially overwritten and new ~110 ones added. When this second batch gets pushed to DB, it creates a new row (say ID = 2), and row with ID1 gets deactivated (via a boolean field). Since time delta between row 2 and row 1 does not exceed threshold of say 10 days, the bridge simply pushes up the data without regard to existing values.
Exception scenario: while researching company B, we find out that it had made an acquisition 5 months ago, such that its financial condition is affected, so we need to adjust historical data for the company. In Excel, we change 10 metrics for each of the most recent and previous 4 quarters. Since time delta for at least one of target columns exceeds threshold, the bridge shows an error and requires the user to enter a comment. The bridge creates 5 new rows, deactivates 5 old ones (via boolean field) and adds user comment to the deactivated rows. Note that all conflicts pertaining to the same ticker within the same time period (all changes to Q1&amp;#039;18, for example), will be collapsed into one warning and comment.
The bridge works one way &amp;ndash; only upload.
If more information is needed, don&amp;#039;t hesitate to ask.
**Deliverables**
A Python class (compatible with 3.6), with complete docstrings and with full test coverage (pytest).Budget: $600
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        AWS CodeDeploy,                     Django,                     Microsoft SQL Server Programming,                     Python            click to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Lead Generation Services Needed --- Phone Data Validation - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Lead-Generation-Services-Needed-Phone-Data-Validation_%7E017587bbe37847cdd6?source=rss</link>
    <description>*I&amp;#039;m looking specifically for people in the following countries:
-Australia
-US
-UK
Our company is in the business of selling security cameras and surveillance software that brings together different security video feeds. I need to build a list of decision-makers and influencers for our sales team to utilize. 
This project is split into two jobs, with this posting focusing on calling contacts to verify their contact information and role. I would like to verify these contacts for a list of cities in several different countries, some of which do not have English as a primary language. Our current industry focuses are traffic management (which are often departments of transportation) and law enforcement (police departments). 
The tasks will include the following: 
- Call a list of contacts to verify their job role and contact information (a script will be provided)
- For organizations without known contacts, call to identify the correct person to speak with, and gather their contact information
- Collect and verify the following information via research : Name, official title, phone number, email address
- Gather and submit the report through MS Excel 
Skills Needed: 
- Previous experience cold calling
- Previous experience working for similar projects
- Understanding of the surveillance industry (beneficial)
- Conversational in one or more of: English, Arabic, Chinese, Mandarin, Spanish, Turkish
Requirements: 
- Phone access
- Internet access
I intend to hire 5 or more people for this job. The cities will be split between people based on languages spoken. I will incorporate at least one milestone to track progress against. The input to this project will be from my other project, which involves research to identify the contacts.
I am looking to complete this project in four to six weeks.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Sales &amp;amp; Marketing &amp;gt; Telemarketing &amp;amp; Telesales
Skills:        Cold Calling,                     Lead Generation,                     Telemarketing            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 19:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Batch file - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Batch-file_%7E01a23168804e3226f7?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;batch file as follows;
Move all sub folders in folder
I want to make sure that when it moves it. It&amp;rsquo;s also deleting the files from the original folder.
This job was posted from a mobile device, so please pardon any typos or any missing details.Budget: $40
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 16:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>DevOps - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/DevOps_%7E010bc2d08ea7588bc1?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for experienced devops contractor to manage&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;server on AWS.
Experience required with: Python, Jenkins, AWS, EC2, RDS, S3, WHMCS, Github.
Must have exposure to the above. Work will include managing a few website under one server. Establishing developer server with Jenkins pipeline and secure sites from threats.
Python/Django experience is also required to be able to create environments and fix issues.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>DevOps Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/DevOps-Engineer_%7E013d477d41f00ce036?source=rss</link>
    <description>About the job:
Ever been challenged to see endless possibilities and embrace DevOps in an Agile Environment working alongside innovative developers and architects? This is where you see value being added and your feedback being really taken seriously as a DevOps Engineer driving down the highway with docker, kubernetes, jenkins, Nexus with a complete Continuous Integration / Continuous Deployment (CI/CD) pipeline, with a fully Dockerized environment with Microservices based API and load-balancing, network uptime and system performance monitoring being of utmost importance, using in premise servers, AWS, Google Cloud, Azure and Oracle Cloud. 
Role: 
Role will be of DevOps Engineer reporting to Head of Engineering
Location: Bangalore 
Reporting To:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Head of Engineering
Must&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Have :
â—	Familiarity with DevOps concepts and techniques.
â—	Expertise in at least one of bash, python, perl, javascript (node.js) and familiarity with at least two others.
â—	Good Linux administration skills.
â—	Working knowledge of networking, DNS, firewalls etc.
â—	Knowledge of internet domain name administration
â—	Strong architecture &amp;amp;amp; design experience of Deploying Enterprise applications on AWS, monitoring and performance tuning of deployed applications on AWS.
â—	Knowledge of CI tools like Jenkins and repository management via tools like Nexus.
â—	Ability to learn on the go and use new devops tools and concepts (see Desirable section)
â—	Should have been responsible for at least one security audit of the systems being managed
â—	Should have worked on at least two of the following : in house servers, AWS, Azure, Google Cloud Platform, Oracle Cloud
Desirable
â—	Knowledge on Docker and Docker orchestration tools like kubernetes
â—	Experience on databases like Oracle, SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB. 
â—	Basic hands on commands in any of the relational and non relation databases. 
â—	Experience with System Health Monitoring (Nagios, Zabbix, MUNIN, Prometheus, Kibana, Sysdic, logz.io)
Responsibilities:
Primary Responsibilities: 
â—	Maintain and improve the CI/CD pipeline
â—	Docker base image creation, kubernetes orchestration
â—	Network and system performance monitoring using tools.
â—	Automate administration tasks using scripting
â—	Automate deployments so that it is easy to switch hosting environments
Project Management:
â—	Discuss with Developer and understand the project details and tools and need to deploy the application and document the same.
â—	Create and Improve Standard Operating Procedures (SOP) so that the system is amenable to audit
Others:
â—	Travel to client location, both in India as well as overseas, for understanding client requirements.
Accountability :
â—	 Adherence to the expected roles and responsibilities w.r.t ISMS, QMS and SOC standards&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Required Skills:
Primary Skills: DevOps concepts, Shell scripts, Docker, Docker orchestration like kubernetes.
Secondary Skills: Linux administration skills, System Health Monitoring, Jenkins. 
Organizational Support:
We can ensure that you will experience an exceptionally warm hearted workplace and a big scope for career growth with extraordinary learning about testing tools. Your careers will soar to skies by working with us to realize our dream of building a world class center of excellence for automation.
Our experienced architects will step in to help finalize and propose architecture and framework aspects. Our full-fledged process department provides timely guidance on processes. L&amp;amp;amp;D department helps filling up any gaps related to soft-skills and technical training. 
In rare cases, if there is guidance required on people management front, experienced HR team will always be available.
Future road map for this role: 
We would like to plan that out with you when we reach that stage during our discussions. 
Educational Qualifications ,Certifications &amp;amp;amp; Experience :
â—	BE, MCA
â—	Ideal Experience Range: Ideally, you should have spent between 3 to 4 years in IT industry to have first-hand experience of above mentioned responsibilities; however, Sigma is open to consider bright persons with lesser experience.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        DevOps            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Assistant - Production Design Set Up - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Assistant-Production-Design-Set_%7E0146ed0c81659fe47a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Job Description for Production Design Set Up Assistant-&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We are looking for someone who can review orders and then place artwork files on a production template that matches up with these orders.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This set up process is done in photoshop with scripts and actions and we will provide the steps on how to do this.
The files will be available in batch folders to be set up on the template. Since the files are photos, graphic images, or stylized text the person needs to have some graphic design experience to be able to visualize and scale and/or edit the images for printing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This job is basically order set up with some image editing applied when needed and will be an ongoing job.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The hours at the beginning will vary depending on the number of orders we receive and will increase during the holiday season.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We are looking for someone who is interested in building a working relationship with our US based design team with a turnaround time of 12 hours for us to receive the completed files.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The order set up is a seasonal business, so the demand will increase substantially October through December.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Requirements-
Photoshop CC using scripts and actions, clipping images, and editing images when needed.
Basic photo editing skills - brightness, contrast, and color balance 
Graphic design experience
Fluent in English and complete understanding of English grammar
Attention to detail is a must
Ability to follow written directions and a quick learnerPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Illustrator,                     Adobe Photoshop,                     Graphic Design,                     Photo Editing,                     Print Layout Design            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for a Senior Backend Developer / Team Lead - Long-Term contract - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-Senior-Backend-Developer-Team-Lead-Long-Term-contract_%7E01192aa3dd0a144e24?source=rss</link>
    <description>Pleexy (USA) is looking for a Senior Developer to join our product development team.
Pleexy(pleexy.com) is an integration platform between project/task management tools (Trello, Evernote, Outlook, OneNote, Todoist, Wunderlist, JIRA, Github, Basecamp and so on). Its two-way synchronization unlocks integration scenarios that are not available through other workflow-products. 
The system is based on microservices architecture and uses node.js and go as primary development languages.
We are looking for an experienced developer who is not only capable of implementing most complex parts of the product but can also lead a small team of developers.
Requirements:
- Strong computer science skills (algorithms, data structures), ability to write efficient code
- String experience in implementing backend services 
- Knowledge of javascript. Experience with nodejs is a plus.
- Understanding of front-end development. Experience with angular or react will be a plus
- Understanding of microservice architecture
- Team leadership experience
- Experience in working with QA and releasing software
- Good understanding of DevOps
- Experience with Docker/Go/Kubernetes is a plus
- At least 7 years of experience in software development
- English &amp;ndash; ability to communicate.
Responsibility:
-	Development and support of product architecture. Technical decision making
-	Managing tasks and work of development team
-	Implementation of most complex backed services and key components.
-	Help in supporting of project environment (Google Cloud, Kubernetes,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Jenkins, Spinnaker, ELK)
-	Participation in product definition
We offer:
- Full-time remote job with flexible working hours
- Long-term project
- Ability to participate in a product definition
- Cutting-edge technologies
- Stock option package
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, please send us your resume, and your expectations for an hourly rate.
Join us, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be fun!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        Golang,                     Kubernetes,                     Node.js            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 18:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior DevOps - with experience in Azure and Python - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-DevOps-with-experience-Azure-and-Python_%7E012f6d249ad9048f1c?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking for an experienced &amp;amp;quot;DevOps&amp;amp;quot; resource, potentially for long term with below expertise:
&amp;amp;gt; DevOps with experience in Jenkins, Azure/AWS, Docker, Kubernetes.
&amp;amp;gt; Must have development background and desire is to have experience in Python, Ansible, and Groovy
&amp;amp;gt; 30+ hours per week
&amp;amp;gt; Must be available to work with onsite team between 8.30 pm - 11.30 pm IST
&amp;amp;gt; Very good communication skills are required
&amp;amp;gt; $15/hour for long term project (6+ months)Budget: $2,400
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Ansible,                     Microsoft Azure App Services,                     DevOps,                     Groovy,                     Jenkins,                     Python            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>AWS serverless deployment - setup serverless pipeline using codebuild codepipeline on AWS - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/AWS-serverless-deployment-setup-serverless-pipeline-using-codebuild-codepipeline-AWS_%7E01cf9ec0df83fa5b6e?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi I need help setting up a serverless pipeline on amazon web services.
I have a repository of code, I am setting up codepipeline but its kind of new to me as this is the first serverless pipeline I have setup.
I have lots of experience with jenkins and other CI/CD orchestration servers but this is the first with all serverless, so looking for someone who has done this before.
application stack to deploy is all node.js which deploys lambda functions, so experience with lambda a must.
I wouldnt expect this would take more than a day (8-10 hours)
feel free to ask any further questions but essentially need an AWS guru and CI/CD guru in the devops world.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon EC2,                     Amazon Web Services,                     AWS CodeDeploy,                     AWS Lambda,                     Continuous Integration,                     Linux System Administration,                     Node.js,                     Ubuntu            Country: Australiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 15:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>CI/CD Devops Professional - For deployment on Jenkins, Docker&amp;amp;amp; Kubernetes with AWS background - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Devops-Professional-For-deployment-Jenkins-Docker-amp-Kubernetes-with-AWS-background_%7E010153132d4bb1ae22?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need some one who is very good with hands on experience on CI/CD using Jenkins and who can integrate micro service tools like Docker and Kubernetes to the pipe line with AWS cloud background. 
Preferably with ELK knowledge is a plus.
If you are with this specific skill set pl reach out to me.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        Docker,                     Elk,                     Jenkins,                     Kubernetes            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 22:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Full-service Wordpress Development - theme customizations and basic web design - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Full-service-Wordpress-Development-theme-customizations-and-basic-web-design_%7E01654eaee255ecbb01?source=rss</link>
    <description>## About Us
We are a cybersecurity assessment and penetration testing company focused on providing highly technical security engagements to our clients. For the security layman, we research and use the offensive capabilities of hackers to identify security weaknesses in client corporate networks - before the bad guys can find and use them.
Culturally, we are a very technical group of hackers and builders who love what we do - whether researching new security vulnerabilities, developing new tools, or just automating internal tasks. We prioritize (and invest in) constant education, research, and pushing the envelope with technology. 
## What It&amp;rsquo;s Like to Work with us
Everything we do is team-oriented, Agile, and fast-paced, and our wordpress development process is no exception. Collaboration, communication, and quick turn-around times are absolutely essential.
You&amp;rsquo;ll collaborate with an internal project manager, as stay in regular contact with focals in sales, design, leadership, and devops. Slack is a mainstay of our communication process, supplemented by voice/video calls and screen shares. Even as an &amp;amp;quot;external&amp;amp;quot; firm, we expect that you&amp;#039;ll interact closely with us on a regular basis.
All development projects, Wordpress included use an Ansible+Jenkins continuous integration and deployment setup. Access to these, as well as issue trackers, test servers, and other common resources are accessible over the company&amp;rsquo;s secure LAN via VPN.
## What We Need
We&amp;#039;re looking for a full-service Wordpress development firm (or individual contractor) to take over the ongoing development of our main business website.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This will include:
* Developing new features (whether theme-based or plugin-based) to further improve our website.
* Support integrations with Hubspot, Sumo, and other popular marketing tools
* Collaborating on and implementing design improvements to the website.
* Ongoing consultation, management, advice, maintenance, patching, and incremental improvements to our Wordpress site and overall web-based brand and presence.
In broader terms, we&amp;#039;re looking for a long-term partner in the form of a team of experienced professionals who can help us build and maintain a high-quality, cutting-edge website which properly represents our brand to the world.
## Requirements
* Demonstrated excellence in web design in general, and Wordpress development in particular.
* Your team should be based in the USA, able to significantly overlap with normal business hours (PST)
* Able to commit to a long-term, ongoing engagement with us
* Willing to work with us on a consulting/per-hour basis
* Full complement of in-house personnel for project management, development, and design
* Able to converse fluently and clearly on both technical and non-technical issues.
* Fully available for Slack conversations or phone calls during normal business hours, and able to make significant overlap with Pacific time.
* Willing to participate in and contribute to regular voice/video/screenshare calls with the team to discuss requirements and goals, report on progress, and collaborate on new feature proposals.
* Comfortable working in a fast-paced work environment with weekly builds, constant collaboration, and rapid feedback.
* Write clean code with commenting where necessary.
* Create and implement beautiful, user-friendly, and beautiful interfaces and other web-based design components.
* Manage your own team&amp;#039;s time and priorities within the scope provided by project leads and client focals.
## Previous Work
Please provide at least two examples of previous work that you have done, ideal projects which demonstrate your team&amp;#039;s excellence and full range of design and development capabilities.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        CSS3,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript,                     PHP,                     Responsive Web Design,                     Web Design,                     Website Development,                     WordPress            Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Freelance/Part-time DevOps requirement with a leading AI Start-up in Switzerland - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Freelance-Part-time-DevOps-requirement-with-leading-Start-Switzerland_%7E01b1b3522f219c1b53?source=rss</link>
    <description>About Enterprise Bot:
Enterprise Bot is an Artificial Intelligence company that provides white-labeled cognitive solutions. Our out-of-the-box AI chatbots are designed to improve customer service by providing 30 times faster and high-quality responses at 30% of the cost creating operational efficiency for the large financial companies that we cater to.
Our technology enables high-quality responses, improved productivity and a digital assistant available 24/7 on all preferred platforms be it an in-app experience, website or social media channels.
Role:
We need a technical resource in Switzerland who can do on-premise deployments and documentation in Switzerland. The resource will be required to 1-3 days in a month and will be primarily responsible for installations and DevOps work at client&amp;rsquo;s location in Switzerland (mostly around Zurich).
You must be strong in all of the following disciplines and technologies: -
&amp;bull;Have excellent written and verbal communication skills with proficiency in English (candidates with proficiency in German/Swiss-German language will be preferred)
&amp;bull;Demonstrate a current knowledge of latest DevOps tooling and practices
&amp;bull;Experience of deploying on premise Data centers
&amp;bull;Experience of automated software configuration
&amp;bull;Preference for skills in networking / routing / load balancing and VPN configuration
&amp;bull;Strong system administration skills on both Windows and Enterprise Linux systems
&amp;bull;Strong scripting skills Bash, python
&amp;bull;Experience of using automated environment build tooling
&amp;bull;Experience deploying Nodejs, Python web applications
&amp;bull;Experience in documentation such as drawing architecture and understand process flows is mandatory
Specific skills required are: -
&amp;bull;deploying and managing multiple servers
&amp;bull;DB technologies like Mongo/Redis/Elastic search
&amp;bull;Linux Red hat
&amp;bull;CI (Jenkins preferably)
&amp;bull;Documentation experience such as drawing architecture and understand process flows is mandatory
What we offer:
&amp;bull;First-hand experience with AI and NLP
&amp;bull;Opportunity to work with the best clientele in Switzerland
&amp;bull;An opportunity for fast growth within the company and ownership of projects
&amp;bull;Contact with international stakeholders and clients from well-known companies and corporations
&amp;bull;Opportunity to develop a professional networkBudget: $1,200
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        Bash,                     DevOps,                     Elasticsearch,                     Linux System Administration,                     Load Balancing,                     Python            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 14:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Lambda_DynamoDB - Parsing 100 web pages/sec - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Lambda_DynamoDB-Parsing-100-web-pages-sec_%7E018a85a248083b00f5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi! Please read the below RFP carefully. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to include answers to most of the most popular questions
END RESULT: 
web-based solution that 
1.	parses batches of web pages (1000-2000&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;random domain/urls each) via AWS Lambda script
2.	loads all text from the web page into AWS DynamoDB at 100 pages/sec
3.	shows keyword count and stored page text preview and counts keywords in each of the pages behind the URL
The faster the better. Not using third party services that can be banned, stopped or restricted or which are paid (other than AWS).
FRONT END GUI: 
Page 1: 
Input fields
-	Field where a user pastes the list of URLs (1000-2000 at a time)
-	Field where user pastes a string of keywords&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(same for each URL)
Page 2: End result 
2 frame Page with 
Left Frame: a table, showing the parsing results featuring the following fields
-	URL that was parsed (clickable as link)
-	Title of the page behind the URL
-	Status of parsing: success, not-parsed &amp;ndash; Error, not-parsed timed out
Controls: URL.onMouseOver =Load Text To Right Frame From Dynamo AND highlight all words typed in the Keywords text field
Fields:
-	Text field where a string of keywords can be entered 
Right frame
-	Text stored from the page behind the URL
-	Keywords in that text highlighted with different colors (one per keyword)
Example of the URL list. See attached. Assume it can be a random set of any URLs
HOSTING ENVIRONMENT
Amazon AWS Lambda, Dynamo DB (S3 if needed)
USER ENVIRONMENT
This is a boutique solution for a small company. 2-6 users at a time doing several batches in parallel
Browser support: Firefox or Chrome
Mobile support - no
PROPOSAL REQUIREMENTS
Please provide with your answer
- your full fee and time for completion including 
a) development debugging and Q&amp;amp;amp;A. 
b) implementation and support for a couple of weeks on my hosting platform. (Can write it on your premises, but then show it works on my server). Server comes &amp;ldquo;clean&amp;rdquo;, so if you want to the tool to run on some specific libraries or modules &amp;ndash; expect to bring them on with you.
- proposed solution architecture &amp;ndash; language, libraries, etc&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;(VB.NET developers are welcome, but optional)
- your experience in similar tasks. Specifically with Amazon EC2 and Windows based hosting environment
- your resume with qualifications: web development tenure in years, languages fluent in, formal education, etc.
COLLABORATION REQUIREMENTS
Start: At the start of the project please be ready to provide a high-level workplan with key milestones and deadlines and be ready to meet them
Mid: if we agree that delivery takes more than one day - provide progress update (all work in progress materials) at the end of each day
End: put it on my server yourself, configure, debug and start, then support for a couple of weeks
(not just send file with the Lambda code)
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY REQUIREMENTS
End product should include full source code of the project
By agreeing to deliver this project you agree to give up all the intellectual property rights for the end product of your work within this project
Happy to answer questions that are not covered above
Deadlines: fee and deadline is not negotiable after contract signing. Be careful with committing to the deadline. If we agree on a deadline and you do not deliver full scope - you do not get paid!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Data Science &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;gt; Data Mining &amp;amp; Management
Skills:        AWS Lambda,                     Python,                     Web Scraping            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 07:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>develop overview and tutorial of current software development tools - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/develop-overview-and-tutorial-current-software-development-tools_%7E016958dcc551c1f86b?source=rss</link>
    <description>I would like to find someone who can create an overview of current software development tools and platforms for web-serviced cloud architectures.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
The person I am looking for will have solid understanding of (best case: experience with) tools like SPARC, Postman, Jenkins, hyperledger, kuberneties, Hadoop, apogee (and/or kong), etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
I&amp;#039;d like to create an inventory of popular tools, describe what each are good for, create an ontology, and map them to contemporary software development flows.
This is as much for me as for potential clients.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;It will be an interactive assignment (I could do this myself if I had time, but there are some tools I do not know).Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Software Architecture            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 11:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer needed for an application 1) maintain a database 2)generate files in the required format - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developer-needed-for-application-maintain-database-generate-files-the-required-format_%7E0197271ef8f3999486?source=rss</link>
    <description>Background:
1.	Our accounting system (Xero) cannot generate Zengin file (banking payment file, containing Japanese characters) which can be uploaded to Japanese online banking system for batch payments. 
2.	Xero can generate payment list in excel file, but the list doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain all information required for Zengin file. (sample export from Xero uploaded)
3.	We would like to develop an application to convert payment list from Xero to Zengin format. (sample Zengin file uploaded)
Purposes of the application: 
1)	Maintain vendor bank account information for each client
2)	Generate standard Zengin file with payment list from Xero and vendor list 
Function / Workflow
- Maintain vendor bank account information
ïƒ˜	Review/export vendor list for each client with details
ïƒ˜	Manually add / revise / delete vendor for each client
ïƒ˜	Import vendor list (xlsx, csv, etc.) to the application (run error checking on the file before importing)
- Generate standard Zengin file
1)	Upload Xero data (payment amount and identifier) to the application
2)	Map vendor bank information to each transaction using an identifier
3)	Generate standard Zengin file (csv file) which can be exported from the application.
Requirements:
1)	English interface
2)	The application should be able to handle Japanese Katakana (half-width)
3)	The application can transfer small ãƒ¤ã€ãƒ¦ã€ãƒ¨, etc. to big ones (bank requirements) and remove any full-width blanks between characters when generating Zengin file.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Country: Japanclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 05:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Fix our Jenkins - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Fix-our-Jenkins_%7E0194c5bba2a8636e62?source=rss</link>
    <description>Our Jenkins is no longer automatically publishing our github to our test server. It seems to not find the source. Thanks for fixing it ;-)Budget: $50
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon EC2            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 15:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Dev Ops Engineer position for workforce management platform with over 300,000 daily users - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Dev-Ops-Engineer-position-for-workforce-management-platform-with-over-300-000-daily-users_%7E01eff5ef9db15a0b51?source=rss</link>
    <description>Level: Intermediate
Technologies: 
&amp;bull;	Experience or working knowledge in configuring and maintaining CI servers 
(preferably Jenkins)
&amp;bull;	Hands-on experience in configuring and working with Windows Server
&amp;bull;	Hands-on experience with Windows installers
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of scripting (Windows batch scripting, Powershell etc.)
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of container technologies like Docker
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of using &amp;amp;amp; integrating versioning systems like Git, BitBucket, SVN etc.
(Preferably also RoundTable SCM versioning system)
&amp;bull;	Knowledge of 3-tier architecture, incl. Relational databases and application servers (webservices and webportals, IIS/Tomcat, windows services) 
&amp;bull;	Configuration management knowledge (Chef, Ansible, Terraform etc.)
&amp;bull;	Knowledge about container management tools like Rancher or Kubernetes
Start date: ASAP 
Duration: Current tasks are estimated at 200 - 300 hours; could grow into a much longer engagement. This will depend on delivery and client satisfaction.
Project description and details:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;existing workforce management platform with over 300,000 daily users 
&amp;bull;	Extend continuous integration architecture based on Jenkins
&amp;bull;	Automate code checking actions in repositories like bitbucket to integrate with test automation efforts and updating task mgmt system (JIRA)
&amp;bull;	Automate deployments into a MS Windows server / Docker setup 
&amp;bull;	Manage relevant notifications via Jenkins upon various events
&amp;bull;	Modernize product installers
Work allocation: F/T = 40 hours/week 
Work location:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Working with the team in our office in Bucuresti is preferable.
However, remote work is acceptable. Person will need to be willing to travel to Bucuresti for ramp up and occasionally for team meetings.
Team location and setup: English speaking mixed team in Denmark and Bucuresti.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Country: Romaniaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 11:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need Dev ops for job support. (Indian Preferred.) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-Dev-ops-for-job-support-Indian-Preferred_%7E012fcaf524070c06b1?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are looking for an Indian Developer who can work with us as devops. 
Timings: At least 2 hours, Between 5 AM To 9 AM(Flexible, but only in the morning)
You must be having a good hands-on all dev ops tools. It will be good If you will be able to show me some of your work. 
Note: We have multiple projects on other technologies as well(Angular, React, java, dot net, full stack, mulesoft, python, Qa testing, devops, ). If you are expert in any other technology and looking for freelancing work. Please ping me.
Below is the description for this project. If you feel, you are 70-80% okay with the above requirements. please ping me.
Experience in Hybrid Cloud Architectures, Cloud brokering solutions or Cloud Management Solutions
Experience with Infrastructure Automation, Infrastructure capacity monitoring and automated scaling solutions
 Linux systems administration preferably with public/private cloud
AWS experience
working in Enterprise DevOps model - Automation of application code deployment (Jenkins, Maven, Git, Nexus etc)
Experience in Scripting Python, Perl, Bash
Experience with automation/management frameworks (Puppet, Chef, Ansible, SaltStack)
Experience supporting applications in a UNIX environment
Knowledge of UNIX Shell and Korn scripting for automation of tasks.
Good Understanding of database concepts
Experience with Autosys job management for scheduling, monitoring, and reporting.
If you feel, you are 70-80% okay with the above requirements. please ping me.Budget: $250
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        Apache Maven,                     AWS ECS,                     Bash,                     Bash Shell Scripting,                     DevOps,                     Jenkins,                     Perl,                     Python,                     Unix,                     Unix Shell            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 15:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior Devops Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-Devops-Engineer_%7E01b05268e4a8a22f29?source=rss</link>
    <description>You&amp;rsquo;ll be working with our development and operation team for the whole CI/CD process and you&amp;rsquo;ll be working to build, automate and secure application configuration, auto deployment and provisioning services.
Our requirements: 
 Strong at continuous integration and deployment automation tools such as jenkinx+&amp;nbsp;Kubernetes +Helm&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&amp;bull; 3+ years&amp;rsquo; of experience in DevOps or Linux administration
&amp;bull; Good Linux skill set
&amp;bull;Experience with Continuous Integration using Jenkins
&amp;bull; Experience with Docker containers
&amp;bull; Microservices and container-based stacks like Kubernetes
&amp;bull; Bash, Python, Ruby or other similar scripting languages
At SuperWinWin we believe in continuous innovation and development and we have a large team of business analysts, developers and testers working tirelessly to work on iterations, adding features and improvements to previous builds. Quick iterative releases also encourage the collaboration with the customers for the feedback for continuous improvement. Our development lifecycle is designed to adapt to evolving business requirements and have meaningful milestones, delivering real business value and realistic customer expectations. We are proficient with popular agile methods such as Extreme Programming (XP) and Scrum.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon Web Services,                     Network Security            Country: Ukraineclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Trainer Needed for devops - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Trainer-Needed-for-devops_%7E01f650cbef2ddb8474?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi Thanks for viewing my requirement, i am looking for the training on devops, i am looking for the below tools as part of dev-ops
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1. JENKINS (integration with selenium/JMeter with continuous development) 2. :&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ANSIBLE 3. DOCKERS 4. VAGRANT 5. CHEF&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6. PUPPET 7. GIT 8. AWS 9. WIndows and Linux Server Administration.Budget: $210
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon EC2,                     Amazon Web Services,                     DevOps,                     Network Administration,                     Network Security            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Development/Release Manager - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Development-Release-Manager_%7E01d83025186b1227b6?source=rss</link>
    <description>Looking to hire a full time Development/Release manager to work closely with the VP of Software Engineering to perform the following tasks:
- Convert requirements into user stories
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Enter them as issues in GitLab
- Work with developers to schedule release milestones
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- Setup up release milestones in GitLab
- Maintain app versioining
- Generate release notes
- Provide weekly dev reports
- Maintain release notes email in mailchimp
- Perform release QA
- Plan for release downtime and notifications
- Monitor build and release
- Perform post release QA
- Maintain UI Mockups
Must understand Git branching and Jenkins.
Technologies: nodejs, mongodb, electron, AWS, Google Cloud, Azure
Budget: $30-32. Increases based on timed reviews.
Long term opportunity.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        AngularJS,                     DevOps,                     JavaScript,                     Jenkins,                     Node.js,                     Python,                     Ruby on Rails            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 21:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Freelance Devops Training - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Freelance-Devops-Training_%7E01916783e9306da13a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Simplilearn is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading certification training providers. We partner with companies and individuals to address their unique needs, providing training and coaching that helps working professionals achieve their career goals.
Based in San Francisco, California and Bangalore, India, we have helped over 500,000 professionals and companies across 150+ countries get trained, acquire certifications, and upskill their employees.
We are looking out for freelance instructors who can provide training (both virtual and classroom) to our customers. Please let me know a good time and your contact number to reach you at to discuss about this opportunity in detail
Freelance Instructor Role - Devops Practioner
ï‚· Deliver and facilitate product training without supervision.
ï‚· Participate in client solution calls for customizing the outline to meet the deliverables
ï‚· Lead training using approved materials to comprehensively cover the course material without significant variation to
ensure a consistent customer experience.
ï‚· Coach participants through lab exercises and troubleshoot any issues that arise.
ï‚· Travel, as needed, for onsite, private training classes.
ï‚· Learn new features and training materials that correspond with each major product release.
ï‚· Contribute toward Simplilearn blogs and postings.
Requirements
ï‚· Strong knowledge and expertise in DevOps solution strategy and delivery
ï‚· Working experience on Linux, Ansible, Chef, Puppet, Jenkins, Docker, AWS
ï‚· Experience with automated deployment, continuous integration, release engineering and associated tools
ï‚· Broad knowledge of software development and software testing methodologies and processes along with change and
configuration management practices
ï‚· Executive presence is required; must present outstanding interpersonal skills and teaching ability.
ï‚· Excellent written and oral communication skills and the ability to impart knowledge through formal and informal methods
are critical.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Location Requirement: Only freelancers located in the United States may apply.
Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 21:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Sonar Qube increase code coverage - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Sonar-Qube-increase-code-coverage_%7E0147b40575393ab791?source=rss</link>
    <description>Must be able to update pom with dependencies And run the pipeline ,Which picks test cases And give us the code coverage And also exclude files from that to imporve coverageBudget: $40
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Other - Software Development
Skills:        DevOps,                     Jenkins,                     SonarQube            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 18:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Looking for &amp;amp;quot;DevOps for Developers&amp;amp;quot; Online Trainer (part time) - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Looking-for-quot-DevOps-for-Developers-quot-Online-Trainer-part-time_%7E01e050aa7c3ddcff2e?source=rss</link>
    <description>Currently we are Looking for &amp;amp;quot;DevOps for Developers&amp;amp;quot; Online Trainer (part time), who like to work with us for online training assignments. Our students are located across the globe, we facilitate individuals and corporate to meet their training needs.
Below is complete offer :
Position : Part Time Trainer
Course Duration: 30 Hours
Course Content: http://www.bisptrainings.com/course/DevOps-for-Developers
-Feedback and quality guidelines
-Scheduling of demo class &amp;amp;amp; regular classes.
-Technical Support Activities.
-Software licenses to connect to the students
Requirements/Trainer should have
-Good internet connection to deliver the classes.
-Required environment to demonstrate the software to the students.
-Very good communication skills.
-Good knowledge of the respective Subject.
Trainer&amp;#039;s Availability.
-As we work primarily for US client, the trainer should be available between 6:00 AM to 9:00 AM IST
Prerequisite.
i) Good internet connection.
ii) Strong knowledge in your respective technology.
iii) Training delivery contents [However our support team will facilitate and assist you]
iv) Strong desire to teach people and build relationship
About US: BISP is an IT Training and Consulting Company. We are Subject Matter Experts for DHW and BI technologies. We provide Live virtual Online global IT support and services like online software training, live virtual online lab services, virtual online job support with highly&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;intellectual professional trainers and skilled resources , predominantly In Oracle BI, Oracle DataIntegrator, Hyperion Product stack, Oracle Middleware solution, Oracle SoA, AIA Informatica, IBM Datastage and IBM Cognos. BISP has footprints virtually across USA, CANADA, UK, SINGAPORE, SAUDI ARABIA, AUSTRALIA and more by providing live virtual support services from India for fresh graduates, opt students, working professionals etc. Being a live virtual online training the support , training and service methodology is just click away considerably reducing your TIME,INFRASTRUCTURE and Cost effectiveBudget: $150
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        Bash Shell Scripting,                     CloudLinux,                     Docker,                     Git,                     Jenkins,                     Mavenlink,                     Puppet            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 04:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need hands on experience on Git Jenkins chef and Ansible. - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-hands-experience-Git-Jenkins-chef-and-Ansible_%7E016bb8aaa5e9a2c31d?source=rss</link>
    <description>Not looking for a tutor, need some one to show me those tools in a real time work environment on how to create different branches in git, jenkins (Andible and Maven) chef with Ruby and Ansible with yum
Need someone in Hyd to show me how the tools are used in a real time projectPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon EC2,                     CentOS,                     Linux System Administration,                     Python,                     Ruby,                     Ubuntu            Country: Canadaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 22:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Build/ Release Engineer for US based client, Need full timer, Freelancer who can work from Noida 62 - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Build-Release-Engineer-for-based-client-Need-full-timer-Freelancer-who-can-work-from-Noida_%7E010bccadbcea68419a?source=rss</link>
    <description>Need Full timer/freelancer who can work from Noida 62 office. Job description and role and responsibilities attached.Budget: $10
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Amazon Web Services,                     Bash Shell Scripting,                     Git,                     Jenkins,                     Linux System Administration,                     Python            Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 13:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>CI/CD consulting - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/consulting_%7E0155454a03ca7a3400?source=rss</link>
    <description>The deliverable is a list of CI/CD services sorted by relevancy and compatibility with our operation. 
We could then move to choosing one of those and have you set up the build &amp;amp;amp; deployment jobs for all our repos.
We&amp;#039;d probably start with a conference call to see if there&amp;#039;s a good matchPosted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Other - IT &amp;amp; Networking
Skills:        DevOps,                     Jenkins,                     Linux System Administration            Country: Israelclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Developer needed to build a farmers registry application - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Developer-needed-build-farmers-registry-application_%7E0110fdfd3ae5ea9b95?source=rss</link>
    <description>Accurate data about farms is critical for an evidence-based development program. A government-updated list of farmers is a critical tool for the UN to provide protections and services to farmers. By directly collecting data from farmers and agricultural communities themselves, the farmers&amp;rsquo; registry initiative will increase the capacity of the Ministry and UN to best serve the Palestinian agricultural sector. 
-	Developer must have 4+ years of functional programming experience and be a reputable company with prior rich experience in the field of data science
-	Proven knowledge of web development experience in Java, J2EE, Spring, JMS and Java related build and deployment tools, Python, Scala, or R for large scale data analysis
-	2+ years of experience with D3 or other JavaScript libraries for visualizing data
-	2+ years of experience in Cloud Technologies such as Amazon Web Services.
-	Development of REST web services using either Play Framework or Akka HTTP Server (preferred)
-	Strong database skills with MySQL, PostgreSQL, etc.
-	DevOPs and Continuous Delivery tools &amp;ndash; Jenkins, TravisCI, Docker container repositories
-	Experience working with HTML5 and CSS3
-	Experience working with NodeJS/React/Angular and VueJs.
-	Build automation with Simple Build Tool (SBT)
-	Automated testing with either ScalaTest or Specs2
-	Familiarity with functional design patterns &amp;ndash; using monads, chaining operations, case classes, and comprehensions.Budget: $18,000
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Web Development
Skills:        AngularJS,                     JavaScript,                     PHP,                     Vue.js,                     Website Development            Country: Israelclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 11:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>I need a Jenkins Pipeline that will use terraform to build cloud-based infrastructure - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/need-Jenkins-Pipeline-that-will-use-terraform-build-cloud-based-infrastructure_%7E01ecc05958bc6ae937?source=rss</link>
    <description>Outcomes:
- A Jenkinsfiles that is portable and will set up the environment with no host requirements
- A Jenkinsfiles that will prepare the jenkins workspace, install terraform, clone terraform repository and run the init, plan and apply tasks
- A Jenkins pipeline that can be reused for a number of other terraform projects
Acceptance Criteria:
- The job will be considered complete when a terraform task can be executed successfully in my Jenkins build environment running against the Google Compute Platform.
Constraints:
- Debugging terraform specific issues is not in the scope of this task
- The pipeline must be independent of Jenkins configuration, if this is not possible then documentation for Jenkins setup will be an additional requirement
Dependencies:
- None
Reference Articles:
- https://objectpartners.com/2016/06/01/automating-terraform-projects-with-jenkins/Budget: $200
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Cloud Computing,                     DevOps,                     Infrastructure as Code,                     Jenkins,                     Linux System Administration,                     Terraform            Country: New Zealandclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 06:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Jenkins Dashboard View - Multiple Servers - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Jenkins-Dashboard-View-Multiple-Servers_%7E01e949640deb84e81f?source=rss</link>
    <description>I want to see all my Jenkins servers in one dashboard screen.
Be able to see the relevant info about each one of them (STATUS/BRANCH...) from the last couple of running tasks. I want custom easy and eye-catch monitor that can be controlled.
The one who take this job will have to show it to me on 2-3 Jenkins servers that are not mean Jenkins then tell me how to make it works on my serversBudget: $80
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Microsoft Windows Server            Country: Israelclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 04:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Senior CI/CD DevOps Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Senior-DevOps-Engineer_%7E0118e02080f29c19b5?source=rss</link>
    <description>Come be the engineer who leads us on the journey to best practice CI/CD engineering! It&amp;rsquo;s time for us to step up a gear change or two. We&amp;rsquo;re looking for that thought leader, someone who is a champion for best practice in Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery and who has an eye for high-performance systems.
Our business grew rapidly as a startup, it passed through the scale-up phase, and now we are a large multinational business that&amp;rsquo;s still rapidly expanding. The time has come for us to switch from the ad hocery of &amp;ldquo;start-up mode&amp;rdquo; to a company that&amp;rsquo;s grounded itself in the best engineering practices.
A key part of that is the transition to a CI/CD model of delivery and deployment. We&amp;rsquo;re also undertaking a transformation of our back-end systems to JVM-based microservices in a service mesh, building advanced data analytics and ML/AI in Python and deconstructing our legacy PHP systems into React on the front-end and Kotlin on the back. We&amp;rsquo;re investing heavily in our platform, team and future; and our automation framework will be the solid foundation on which we&amp;rsquo;re building everything else.
We currently use a mixture of some automation with Jenkins (back-end) + Selenium (front), though we are not necessarily particularly attached to those. We currently rely upon a heavy utilisation of subject matter domain experts for manually testing, but that&amp;rsquo;s not a scalable solution and our plans for new market offerings&amp;mdash;particularly driven by an internal product incubator and additional country penetration&amp;mdash;mean that we must eliminate this manual component almost entirely. The Technology team will approach this by harnessing automated Quality Assurance across all the components of our architecture, for which the input from the CI/CD perspective will be the most vital part.
The aim is to keep the code in a deployable state at any given time. That&amp;rsquo;s a key enabler for our growth so that we can push dozens of releases to production&amp;mdash;risk-free&amp;mdash;each day. That best-practice Continuous Delivery experience, with the use of cutting-edge technology, will empower our e-commerce organisation to the next level.
This will shift the role of the domain experts from manually testing to verifying that the functional features they had requested meet their expectations and to suggesting how the implemented features could be further enhanced. This enables growth and stimulates iterative product and service innovation. This role will have a huge impact on the organisation.
For the person we are looking for, this will be a &amp;lsquo;dream job&amp;rsquo;: a green fields leadership position to show us exactly how this should be done and support a hundred million Euro business to become a billion Euro one.
You will need:
-- Experience in a workplace that has transitioned through CI and Continuous Deployment to full-blown Continuous Delivery as well
-- Experience with multiple different automation frameworks and the ability to identify the strengths and weaknesses of each
-- A strong affinity for doing things right the first time but, paradoxically, the flexibility to experiment, fail fast and converge on the optimal solution
-- To be a leader who can balance leading and educating the Technology team on best practice, as well as having the stakeholder management skills to understand business drivers and revenue objectives to ensure we stay business deliverable-focused at all times
-- Well-connected into the DevOps community, preferably recognised as a thought leader in this space
We offer the opportunity to fully engage your passion for CI/CD/CD, to work in a great environment of open-minded and creative individuals and a compensation and relocation package that recognises your excellence.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Skills:        Automated Testing,                     Continuous Integration,                     DevOps,                     Google Cloud Platform            Country: Netherlandsclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Spring Batch and Java based  Back-End Utility - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Spring-Batch-and-Java-based-Back-End-Utility_%7E01ff2c8513a55145f8?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need a very small Java/Spring Batch based utility that can read .csv and .xml files from an input directory and perform 2 step validation on the data read from the .CSV and XML and finally write the records to a report into an output directory. Those records that fail the validation only should go into the output report. Need unit tests and production level coding with clean comment and formatting.
Prefer using latest technologies like: Spring batch for csv processing, Jackson for xml, Java8 features.Budget: $60
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Scripts &amp;amp; Utilities
Skills:        J2EE,                     Java,                     Spring Framework            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>(JS/React) SVG exporter for Illustrator that lives in the browser - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/React-SVG-exporter-for-Illustrator-that-lives-the-browser_%7E01a969c72539a88a5e?source=rss</link>
    <description>I need help to build an awesome export script for Illustrator. Mission is to generate optimized and clean SVG with one click, and show it as a gallery in HTML. For Mac.
1.) Saves out all artboards as SVGs with names. The extension needs one button &amp;amp;quot;Export&amp;amp;quot;.
2.) Batch renames the filenames (Illustrator adds an annoying prefix)
3.) From there the browser opens with a preloader. We optimize SVG code using SVGOMG service.
https://jakearchibald.github.io/svgomg/
https://github.com/svg/svgo/blob/master/docs/how-it-works/en.md
4.) In the same browser window and when done processing, we show a gallery layout in HTML of all the exported SVGs, with buttons to download/show code.
5.) The gallery will have a button to download the whole set.Budget: $300
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Web, Mobile &amp;amp; Software Dev &amp;gt; Desktop Software Development
Skills:        CSS,                     HTML5,                     JavaScript            Country: Swedenclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 12:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into Romanian - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-Romanian_%7E018a18548ef129da92?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into Romanian. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Two basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: Romanian ( bilingual is preferred: Romanian and English)
2. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to Romanian.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Film Dubbing,                     Music,                     Poetry,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English Romanian            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Need professional translators from English into French - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Need-professional-translators-from-English-into-French_%7E01c27961099f1c7b8c?source=rss</link>
    <description>We have a project which needs professional translators from English into French. 
Subject: Christian books, sermons, testimony articles and gospel movie scripts, lyrics
Rate: always negotiable, depending on the quality and service provided
Mode: Distribute articles to different translators batch by batch
Deadline: Flexible for each batch
Three basic requirements of the translators:
1. Mother tongue: French ( bilingual is preferred: French and English)
2. The translators should be French natives who can speak standard French.
3. Rich experiences of religious translation from English to French.
Please fill the attached CV if you are interested in our project, so that we could also know which job may be suitable for you.Budget: $500
Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Translation &amp;gt; General Translation
Skills:        Christian Theology,                     Editing,                     Music,                     Proofreading,                     Reviews,                     Scripting,                     Translation,                     Translation English French            Country: Franceclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Wanted:	Bada$$	Virtual Assistant	with	Real	Estate Experience - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Wanted-Bada-Virtual-Assistant-with-Real-Estate-Experience_%7E019a978fc00b5c4965?source=rss</link>
    <description>I&amp;rsquo;m	a	looking	for	a	full-time	VA	to	help	with	my	real	estate	business.		
**	Responsibilities	Include	**	
Screening	buyer	&amp;amp;amp;	seller	leads	daily
Addressing,	stamping,	and	stuffing	batches	of	100	mailers	on	a	regular	basis
Running	comparable	sales	and	determining	value
Understanding	my	buying	criteria	&amp;amp;amp;	recommending	a	course	of	action
Receiving	inbound	calls	and	making	outbound	calls	(I&amp;rsquo;ll	provide	the	call	script)
Coordinating	paperwork	and	closings
**	Must	Have	**
Hawk-like	attention	to	detail
Dog-like	dependability
Ox-like	work	ethic
Cat-like	reflexes
Please	respond	with	your	availability,	samples	of	past	work,	and	favorite	&amp;lsquo;80s	movie.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Personal / Virtual Assistant
Skills:        Internet Research,                     Virtual Assistant            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Burmese Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Burmese-Reading-Audio-Review_%7E01785ced4855cdb7dc?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are launching Burmese Christian Narration Project and hope to hire some excellent Burmese native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Burmese audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Burmese Yangon Standard Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Background Music: overall tone and the volume of the soundtrack need to be compatible with the related content, and quieten people&amp;rsquo;s heart to ponder over the words.
NOTE: we just accept Unicode Font (Myanmar 3).
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Admin Support &amp;gt; Data Entry
Skills:        Audio Production,                     Burmese,                     English,                     Microsoft Excel,                     Microsoft Word,                     Translation English Burmese            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Civil Maps is Hiring for freelance consultant - DevOps Engineer - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Civil-Maps-Hiring-for-freelance-consultant-DevOps-Engineer_%7E019e79d6f1ec4273af?source=rss</link>
    <description>Hi ,
We are Civil Maps .
Civil Maps, provider of 3D mapping technology for fully autonomous vehicles, has raised a $6.6 million seed funding round from Ford Motor Company, Motus Ventures, Wicklow Capital, StartX Stanford and Yahoo cofounder Jerry Yang&amp;rsquo;s AME Cloud Ventures.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; mission is to make it possible for fully autonomous vehicles (SAE Levels 4-5) to drive anywhere smoothly and safely. Through artificial intelligence and vehicle-based local processing, Civil Maps converts sensor data into meaningful map information built specifically to direct fully autonomous vehicles. The company will use the seed investment to accelerate product development and deployment with a number of leading automotive companies and technology partners.
Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; artificial intelligence software aggregates raw 3D data from LiDAR (high-resolution laser imaging), camera and other sensors onboard autonomous vehicles and organizes the information into machine-readable maps. The information is vastly more actionable information than today&amp;rsquo;s mapping systems and requires a fraction of the data storage and transmission for existing technologies. Thanks to this light data footprint, Civil Maps&amp;rsquo; spatial information is far less costly to transmit over cellular networks, enabling the company to more easily crowdsource, update and share road data in real time&amp;mdash;a major improvement over the lengthy processes that require human annotation in current use. As a result, the company can quickly generate and maintain maps that give fully autonomous vehicles the comprehensive and precise knowledge to autonomous operate safely and smoothly on all roads.
About the Opportunity : 
This is an opportunity to work on some of the most exciting problems in the autonomous vehicle industry. Civil Maps is looking for a Devops engineer to grow its overall infrastructure. You will be interacting with a completely custom-made distributed computing framework, handling terabytes and petabytes of machine vision data, and millions of requests from robotic platforms.
In our interdisciplinary teams, you will get acquainted with the many facets of 3D map creation: data collection, geospatial registration, feature extraction, auditing.
Come work on novel challenges, learn and grow while helping Civil Maps achieve on-demand perception of the world around us.
We are hiring the professionals for the below skills:
Work Location&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;: Hyderabad
Job Description for DevOps Enginner:
Experience : 3-15 yrs 
Responsibilities : 
Deliver next generation distributed applications using a variety of tools to include Kubernetes, Ansible, RHEL, Openshift, Atomic, Mesos, Openstack and Docker.
Build solutions and provide a framework for Microservices and DevOps.
Bring knowledge and help with continuous integration, deployment and security.
Automating the Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment environment with relative tools.
Troubleshooting Build &amp;amp;amp; Deployment issues.
Experience with the following : 
Deploy, manage Continuous Integration tools (Jenkins, Travis etc..).
Cloud-based deployments (AWS, Azure, OpenStack).
Linux administration, usage, and bash scripting (Bash, Batch, Powershell)
Deploying MEAN stack applications.
Security tools like Fortify, Nessus.
Network architecture (routing, load balancing, firewalls, VLANs).
Virtualization (VMWare, XEN, KVM, Openstack).
Container technologies (Mesos, Docker, Rocket, etc.).
Experience in setting up backup and restore mechanism for the DB and other relevant systems.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: IT &amp;amp; Networking &amp;gt; Network &amp;amp; System Administration
Country: Indiaclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Photoshop editor for repeated work adding text using actions - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Photoshop-editor-for-repeated-work-adding-text-using-actions_%7E01956d4abb6db9599d?source=rss</link>
    <description>I am looking for entry level Photoshop editor with basic Photoshop skills. We are developing a portfolio of imagines where we require to do following:
Change text in the photo using action script (around 30-40 different photos)
Adjust the text in the imagine to suit the text box.
Save the file using batch function as .jpg.
Scripts and necessary instructions will be provided.
The job may require basic editing skill like removing trade names adding light to the imagine...
You should be familiar with design and good feel for colour composition.
I am looking for fast worker, and&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;quick learner since the time to perform the job will be limited.
We will post the Photoshop projects on the shared drive like onedrive. After the job is done the ready photo will be uploaded to the same share drive by you.
Required number of hours weekly is min 30.
I am looking for freelancers with the lowest rates
Pay is $3 an hour.Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Graphic Design
Skills:        Adobe Photoshop,                     Photo Editing            Country: United Kingdomclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 22:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
  <FeedItem>
    <title>Dutch Christian Reading Audio Review - Upwork</title>
    <link>https://www.upwork.com/jobs/Dutch-Christian-Reading-Audio-Review_%7E01602c2b88ee568672?source=rss</link>
    <description>We are launching Dutch Christian Reading project and hope to hire some Dutch native speakers to check the audios one by one or batch by batch. The audios range from about 15 to 50 minutes. The reviewer needs to check Dutch audio against the script, then write down comments/suggestions on the mistakes of the audio in English. 
Here is the range of audio review, which means reviewers need to check these points.
1. Accent: should be a Standard Dutch Accent which can be accepted by most local people.
2. Added words, incorrect words, missing words, pronunciation mistakes, pause error and so on.
3. Reading Style: the tone needs to be suitable for the content, and the pace can quiet your heart to ponder over the words while listening.
4. Post-production: if vocals and reverberation are pleasant to hear; if the overall tone and the volume of the background music is soft, and will not impair people&amp;rsquo;s ability to hear God&amp;rsquo;s words.
If you have any interest, please contact us with CV. Thank you!Posted On: October 20, 2018 21:36 UTCCategory: Design &amp;amp; Creative &amp;gt; Other - Design &amp;amp; Creative
Skills:        Audio Engineering,                     Audio Production,                     Dutch,                     English,                     Voice Over Dutch            Country: United Statesclick to apply</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
  </FeedItem>
</ArrayOfFeedItem>